
[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Audio File: ..\..\..\..\Desktop\[DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][12][x264_aac].mkv
Video File: ..\..\..\..\Desktop\[DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][12][x264_aac].mkv
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 2
Video Position: 31288
Video Color Matrix: BT.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.93,0:21:49.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由動漫國字幕組和輕之國度字幕組聯合製作\N僅供試看,請支持購買正版音像製品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.13,0:21:52.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻譯:栗花落&槍叔&Cosmo  校對:娜娜莉  時間:Rodax  後期:sora  MKV:烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.19,0:00:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光天化日之下对女性品头论足的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.12,0:00:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是艳福不浅
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.23,0:00:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.81,0:00:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.08,0:00:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我们是初次见面对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.00,0:00:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 正是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.08,0:00:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 为什么知道我的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.52,0:00:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有必要回答你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.08,0:00:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不是对女生品头论足的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.92,0:00:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来找我何事?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.62,0:00:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于姬小路秋人表现出的态度
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.88,0:00:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从心底里感到吃惊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.39,0:00:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是普通的男孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.79,0:00:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不可能在我面前如此心平气和回答我问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.55,0:00:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时我就觉得…「真不爽」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.40,0:00:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.11,0:00:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是童贞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.27,0:01:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,童贞 在这情况下用英语说就是Cherry boy
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.27,0:01:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,438)\fs23}处男
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.94,0:01:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟某部位发育未成熟毫无关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.31,0:01:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.89,0:01:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带一提 我是处女
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.04,0:01:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶！处…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.06,0:01:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是肆无忌惮的打探我的隐私
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.31,0:01:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你也要贡献自己的隐私
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.75,0:01:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…你怎么这么不讲理
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.65,0:01:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.60,0:01:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 对不起 我听不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.61,0:01:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…CHU男啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.07,0:01:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样低头嘟囔我怎么听得清
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.18,0:01:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你 到底有没有想和我认真交谈
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.74,0:01:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,童贞…我是童贞行了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.69,0:01:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要让我说几遍才好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.84,0:01:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 对不起 我听的不是很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.04,0:01:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你这句话肯定是骗我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.59,0:01:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我说的你肯定是听的一清二楚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.92,0:01:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…不知道为什么总有些紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.54,0:01:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴里说出的尽是些荡漾的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.21,0:01:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有个洞我都想钻进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.03,0:02:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是那须原安娜使塔希亚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.64,0:02:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 童贞君
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.45,0:02:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里…做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.95,0:02:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.59,0:02:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我将在今年春天转入这个学校就读
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.74,0:02:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提前过来熟悉下环境
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.38,0:02:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么 所以你才在这里观赏女子田径部的训练啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.12,0:02:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了将年轻的女孩子们的水灵灵的娇体
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.21,0:02:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深深的刻在脑海里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.29,0:02:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从紧身衣开始美味的吃掉那样…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.13,0:02:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.79,0:02:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么样总是想损我几句
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.37,0:02:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我看着你的时候 就特别想捉弄你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.88,0:02:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 要是没有什么要事的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.39,0:02:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想继续参观学校了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.07,0:02:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.53,0:02:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.39,0:02:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在没有任何监视措施的情况下让你乱走
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.32,0:02:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一要是闹出什么事来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.91,0:02:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是要负起的责任的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.42,0:02:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀我都说啦 你那个是误会我了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.27,0:03:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 如果你还是想在校园里四处看看的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.14,0:03:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也必须跟你一起走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.76,0:03:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 也就是说 你愿意带我逛这个学园
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.46,0:03:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以这么理解
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.89,0:03:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看我这样 其实也是在反省的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.96,0:03:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反省？反省什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.92,0:03:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的形象 感觉变得很是胡搅蛮缠了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.12,0:03:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你这么自觉 那就不能拿出点实际行动吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.11,0:03:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 只有这点 希望你能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.01,0:03:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家…非常的紧张…的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.31,0:03:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.25,0:03:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 在你面前 总是的感到特别紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.79,0:03:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且总说奇怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.56,0:03:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说完全看不出来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.61,0:03:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表情也没太大变化 声音也挺普通
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.82,0:03:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要无论如何都无法相信的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.38,0:03:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让你拿着我刚脱下的内衣回家哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.32,0:03:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白为什么会转到那个话题上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.81,0:04:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请容我敬谢不敏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.39,0:04:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不可思议
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.66,0:04:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了我的内衣不惜生命的人可多的是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.75,0:04:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却放任这个机会溜走
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.29,0:04:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从紧张的人嘴里蹦出这种话 不奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.22,0:04:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若你死不信我说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.63,0:04:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么现在你就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.19,0:04:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上我脱下的内衣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.91,0:04:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 先不说这 你能继续为我介绍校园么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.98,0:04:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.61,0:04:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说这是我提议的 不过你要我继续陪着的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.18,0:04:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会被我戏弄的更惨哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.80,0:04:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要逃趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.41,0:04:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随意了 你的那些我都习惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.80,0:04:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许还说不上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.48,0:04:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你那些我大概都理解了 无需担心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.84,0:05:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.18,0:05:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是笑嘻嘻的看什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.57,0:05:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在想象凌辱我的场面 然后偷着乐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.35,0:05:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你心里到底把我当成多变态的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.52,0:05:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原安娜史塔希亚哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.05,0:05:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字 那须原安娜史塔希亚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.47,0:05:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.23,0:05:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.43,0:05:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也可以叫我安娜哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.56,0:05:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安娜呐 了解
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.25,0:05:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然管女人叫穴 你还真是个糟糕的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.25,0:05:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(366,438)\fs23}安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.25,0:05:53.66,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注:老梗了…= =日语里面「穴」和「安娜」同音
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.84,0:05:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种文字游戏能别玩了么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.99,0:06:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就此姬小路秋人 转入圣莉莉安娜学园了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.01,0:06:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且因此 我也很幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.46,0:06:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我不但有姬小路秋子这样的美丽的朋友在身边
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.80,0:06:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还和她的哥哥成为了朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.79,0:06:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起度过了很多愉快的时光
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.82,0:06:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸福 对 这应该是愉快并且幸福的才对
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.11,0:06:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让我成为你的女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.07,0:06:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原同学 那须原同学喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.89,0:06:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.11,0:06:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是「怎么了」吧 今天的那须原同学有点怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.47,0:06:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 人家没啥奇怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.11,0:06:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 别想瞒过我的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.94,0:06:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成你想今晚夜袭哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.49,0:06:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该不是这样的吧 这样不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.61,0:06:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的贞操是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.09,0:06:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为她第六感很敏锐的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.03,0:07:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在却说出前言不搭后语的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.41,0:07:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个好玩的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.98,0:07:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之你有什么麻烦的事 尽管找我商量
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.95,0:07:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都是一个学生会的同伴嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.58,0:07:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不劳你费心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.87,0:07:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你这么说 跟你商量一下也不是不行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.55,0:07:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我仔细听好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.74,0:07:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说不知道为啥突然这么盛气凌人的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.80,0:07:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 想商量什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.25,0:07:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入某天你没穿可穿的内裤的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.96,0:07:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正一筹莫展的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.51,0:07:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你准备如何度过危机？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.45,0:07:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个提问有什么意义 心理测试么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.86,0:07:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么意义 我只是想听听你的意见哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.75,0:07:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.01,0:07:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的话就会就近找个便利店
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.26,0:08:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买件适当的内裤穿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.01,0:08:02.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先蒙混过关
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.30,0:08:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 为什么这种表情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.27,0:08:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了什么奇怪的话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.43,0:08:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不用在意给我继续
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.99,0:08:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他还有比如有没洗的内裤的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.98,0:08:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就拿来洗完后用吹风机吹干再穿上的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.25,0:08:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有干脆就找一个可以替代内裤的东西怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.40,0:08:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如运动短裤 学校泳衣之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.76,0:08:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我有说什么奇怪的话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.39,0:08:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我就承认你所说的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.66,0:08:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是可以被采用的优秀的提案吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.59,0:08:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错嘛 姬小路同学
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.32,0:08:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种程度的事被夸也完全高兴不起来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.89,0:08:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如说有种被当作笨蛋的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.61,0:08:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路同学 我不知道有没有注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.86,0:08:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从你出现后 我的人生从各种意义上来说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.54,0:09:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都发生了巨大的变化
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.32,0:09:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而现在的你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.58,0:09:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更是一个和我争夺同一个男人的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.49,0:09:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生真的是变幻莫测呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.51,0:09:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.53,0:09:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为小小谢礼的一个吻
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.25,0:09:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这…这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.12,0:09:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果什么也没发现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.83,0:09:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 也想到是这么回事了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.37,0:09:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能会有妖怪什么的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.34,0:09:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.48,0:09:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要在安心的一瞬间干性骚扰这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.59,0:09:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人哥哥 会长姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.18,0:09:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙 银兵卫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.04,0:09:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.69,0:09:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人互相乱摸了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.61,0:09:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能会
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.40,0:09:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互摸？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.78,0:10:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下就是秋子和那须原同学了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.03,0:10:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.13,0:10:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半夜迷路真的是太可怕了 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.77,0:10:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是新的玩法还是什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.52,0:10:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你们有看到什么可怕的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.10,0:10:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 没看到什么特别的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.65,0:10:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这边也没什么异常
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.88,0:10:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是 看走眼了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.65,0:10:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哭 亚里沙确确实实看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.61,0:10:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的声音是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.21,0:10:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.51,0:10:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往这边来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.34,0:10:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人君 还有大家也在
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.60,0:10:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神野小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.90,0:10:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 妖怪骚乱的原因是神野小姐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.43,0:10:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是刚刚才到这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.09,0:11:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为一个人都没看到 觉得挺奇怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.18,0:11:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就这么到处晃了晃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.64,0:11:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚才到的？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.89,0:11:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那亚里沙看到的绿色发光物是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.69,0:11:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小猫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.54,0:11:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道这些都是你的孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.11,0:11:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银兵卫 这些小猫是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.39,0:11:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来就是那么回事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.38,0:11:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了呢哥哥 知道了绿色发光物是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.90,0:12:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 我是从一开始就知道会是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.03,0:12:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实从一开始就完全不觉得害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.70,0:12:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然姑且是装着很害怕的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.95,0:12:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙觉得哥哥挡在我们前面的样子非常帅呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.12,0:12:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是稍微有点无聊的结局
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.40,0:12:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事件解决了还是件很值得高兴的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.97,0:12:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱 虽然想就这么直接带回家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.34,0:12:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但房租会不会涨价啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.63,0:12:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么大家都在我的房间里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.84,0:12:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么为什么啊 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.62,0:12:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的哥哥也看到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.14,0:12:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人的话人家怎么睡的下嘛 秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.78,0:12:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然妖怪什么的不可能会有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.26,0:12:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不知道那是什么东西的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.43,0:12:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人睡是非常不明智的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.70,0:12:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 我是完全没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.97,0:12:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了配合大家而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.69,0:12:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的那个 嗯 为了夜袭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.05,0:12:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然乱交聚会什么的也是大欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.63,0:13:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就快睡等睁眼到早上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.94,0:13:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 为什么连神野小姐也
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.86,0:13:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人君 不要说些坏心眼的话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.27,0:15:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.15,0:15:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了吗 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.77,0:15:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么一回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.72,0:15:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 这到底是怎么一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.02,0:15:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 其实因为一直没有说的机会所以没说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.89,0:15:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙有裸睡的习惯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.92,0:15:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前总是一起睡的时候 早上肯定会脱得光光
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.84,0:15:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是一起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.45,0:15:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了早上肯定…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.34,0:15:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让人羡慕的下流就是指的这么回事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.28,0:15:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就给我交换
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.46,0:15:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔的妹控虽然不好 但萝莉控就更加糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.79,0:15:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺能干的嘛 鹰乃宫亚里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.36,0:15:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话我们也不能再这么放松警惕了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.84,0:16:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学…学生会长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.31,0:16:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都别傻愣着啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.84,0:16:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也都脱了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.81,0:16:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么连我也要脱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.73,0:16:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也要脱的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.28,0:16:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原安娜史塔西亚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.51,0:16:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「真空」 你还真是有一手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.48,0:16:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.40,0:16:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.79,0:16:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦~呀~
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.24,0:16:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是有爱 是妹妹就有问题的 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.80,0:16:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为太空军中的一员
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.56,0:16:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向着外太空探险搜索
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.14,0:16:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请三思啊 秋男哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.99,0:16:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 秋菜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.76,0:16:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.76,0:16:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果保卫地球是与保护你联系在一起的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.90,0:17:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥在宇宙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.13,0:17:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋菜在地球
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.98,0:17:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不准什么时候秋菜就会比哥哥年长了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.54,0:17:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是秋菜变为了姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.12,0:17:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有爱就没问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.26,0:17:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 我可以进来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.41,0:17:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.26,0:17:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么突然打扮成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.06,0:17:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正所谓人靠衣装
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.03,0:17:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.29,0:17:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了把我的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.67,0:17:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽可能正确的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.53,0:17:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.47,0:17:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个不得不向哥哥道歉的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.80,0:17:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道歉是指什么事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.09,0:18:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怀疑了哥哥这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.12,0:18:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六年前
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.29,0:18:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥曾说过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.27,0:18:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「总有一天会把你夺回来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.99,0:18:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我 要当个乖孩子」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.55,0:18:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我说过呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.89,0:18:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 最开始我深信不疑
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.44,0:18:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信哥哥很快会来接我的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.45,0:18:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.43,0:18:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论过了多久哥哥也没有来接我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.91,0:18:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.28,0:18:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连书信来往都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.50,0:18:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初的时候 明明整天满脑子都想着哥哥的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.16,0:18:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回过神来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.95,0:18:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经是 偶尔才会想起哥哥了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.41,0:18:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样一辈子不能与哥哥相见也是没办法的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.39,0:18:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渐渐开始这么想了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.27,0:18:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌无法止住这样的想法的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.64,0:18:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很不安…很害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.13,0:18:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.65,0:18:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.46,0:19:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是一切了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.37,0:19:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论到达这里前发生过什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.82,0:19:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.00,0:19:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.95,0:19:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.99,0:19:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子要是道歉的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.50,0:19:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不得不道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.50,0:19:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是不安的 却又无可奈何
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.25,0:19:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子真的等得下去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.25,0:19:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不好已经开始享受另一段人生了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.26,0:19:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就已经没有我出现的余地了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.80,0:19:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事才不会有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.71,0:19:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.87,0:19:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直坚信哥哥会来接我的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.99,0:19:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是艰难的学业
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.58,0:19:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是来自各方的压力我都坚持了下来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.72,0:19:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天要让哥哥看看这些成果
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.75,0:19:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.62,0:19:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 我遵守约定了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.93,0:19:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照哥哥的嘱咐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.95,0:19:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为一个乖孩子了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.88,0:20:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩 你已经做到了我叮嘱的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.94,0:20:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长成了一个乖孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.15,0:20:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.71,0:20:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是从以前就是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.25,0:20:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就更加优秀了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.13,0:20:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我引以为傲的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.24,0:20:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.01,0:20:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.43,0:20:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比以前更漂亮了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.12,0:20:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在…在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.57,0:20:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.23,0:20:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你老逼我说的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.91,0:20:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「夸我漂亮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.64,0:20:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夸我可爱吧」之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.88,0:20:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.13,0:20:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是出其不意会让我很困扰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.64,0:20:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.18,0:20:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我郑重的表示 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.36,0:20:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很感谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.85,0:20:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.31,0:20:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.22,0:20:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.26,0:20:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请接受我无尽的谢意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.17,0:21:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.79,0:21:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样有时代感的秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.97,0:21:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不让人有种想粗暴的使唤秋子了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.43,0:21:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧哥哥 来拽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.65,0:21:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拽是指什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.30,0:21:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是指和服腰带啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.14,0:21:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正所谓代官play嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.14,0:21:16.50,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注:代官:原指日本江户时代的幕府直属地方官
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.73,0:21:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥猛地一拽带子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.02,0:21:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就边叫「啊嘞！」边转圈圈了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.33,0:21:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊嘞！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.17,0:21:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住 手 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.54,0:21:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.06,0:21:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能这样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.07,0:21:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为难得你上钩了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.44,0:21:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}没想到居然是用来将妹妹我赶出屋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.03,0:21:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}我才不会善罢甘休呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.90,0:21:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与妹妹两人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.59,0:21:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过着平凡的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.32,0:21:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这个愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.23,0:21:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在来看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.16,0:21:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开门哇
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.79,0:21:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还暂且无法实现
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.33,0:21:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.64,0:21:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于无论是外表还是成绩都十分普通
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.81,0:21:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内心无丝毫杂念
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.39,0:22:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有天赋异禀的我来说
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.53,0:22:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很麻烦的事态呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.53,0:22:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男女通吃 肉食系的学生会长
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.76,0:22:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都一致认为 很胡搅蛮缠的副会长
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.89,0:22:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友情以上恋人未满的会计
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.21,0:22:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了年龄之外 皆为完美的管理人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.41,0:22:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.86,0:22:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一如既往的热情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.64,0:22:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别一天到晚甜甜蜜蜜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.76,0:22:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.78,0:22:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为书记的不肖吾妹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.83,0:22:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被这样华丽之极的人们包围着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.88,0:22:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想过普通人的生活那是痴人说梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.48,0:22:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但 从今往后要一直保护秋子这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.54,0:22:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都不会变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.97,0:22:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了这个
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.25,0:22:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有必要将可能会造成秋子危险的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.29,0:22:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个不留的逐一清除
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.79,0:22:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是我本人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.36,0:22:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}兄控是个性
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.66,0:22:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人自身也是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.43,0:23:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我也会被包含在危险因素中？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.06,0:23:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很简单啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.39,0:23:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我跟秋子之间其实并没有血缘关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.18,0:23:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.59,0:23:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路家错综复杂的状况
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.54,0:23:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就有机会再聊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.32,0:23:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没打算将这件事告诉秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.72,0:23:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是亲兄妹这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.92,0:23:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑且对秋子算个制动装置
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.99,0:23:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将这个障碍去除的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.09,0:23:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会造成什么样的后果
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.44,0:23:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一清二楚的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.02,0:23:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且再被更大胆的进攻的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.67,0:23:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的制动装置也会有问题的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.56,0:23:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天不知怎的被丢在一边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.43,0:23:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要更进一步的…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.82,0:23:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.03,0:23:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就把初夜
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.34,0:24:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来做夫妇最初的「那个」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.02,0:24:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.18,0:24:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是在说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.64,0:24:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我是有血缘关系的兄妹
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.07,0:24:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才总是说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.37,0:24:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.80,0:24:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有爱就没问题了对吧


