[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
Audio File: C:\Users\ikakun\Desktop\[DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][01][x264_aac].mkv
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.93,0:21:59.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由動漫國字幕組和輕之國度字幕組聯合製作\N僅供試看,請支持購買正版音像製品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:02.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻譯:栗花落&槍叔&Cosmo  校對:娜娜莉  時間:Rodax  後期:sora  MKV:烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.12,0:00:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天貌似神祭不搞了 真不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.91,0:00:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下站是目城 下站是目城
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.06,0:00:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要下車的旅客請準備好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.10,0:00:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.90,0:01:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.02,0:02:01.33,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南目城 派出所
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.67,0:02:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這兒吶 爬那個階梯一直往上走就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.93,0:02:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.96,0:02:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘了這個
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.37,0:02:12.26,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新宿區 織姬山公園
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.06,0:02:40.29,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2}聖莉莉安娜學園學生宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.67,0:03:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.44,0:03:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那個 很久…很久不見
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.59,0:03:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比預定到的要早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.80,0:03:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還在想差不多該去車站接你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.37,0:03:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是的 那個是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.70,0:03:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我決心提前兩小時動身的說…那個
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.94,0:03:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是很了不起的決心 不過有點太急了吶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.11,0:03:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 很抱歉 下次的話只提早十分鐘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.40,0:03:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那樣更好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.52,0:03:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的行李已經搬來了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.68,0:03:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說還在打掃中 總之先進來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.09,0:03:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.62,0:03:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不該是「打擾了」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.09,0:03:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.52,0:04:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我回來了 哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.80,0:04:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦 很合適哥哥你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.95,0:04:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.77,0:04:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟已經六年沒在一起的哥哥一起生活
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.32,0:04:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還特地轉學來我所就讀的學校
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.91,0:04:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥你能稍微拉一拉我的臉頰嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.90,0:04:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要啊 因為這一切不是幻想而是現實哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.38,0:04:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然過程相當辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.15,0:04:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是從今往後 就讓我們兩人一起生活吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.71,0:05:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 小女子不才請多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.64,0:05:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡才是 請多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.15,0:05:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 今天整理行李和打掃很累了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.37,0:05:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先去洗澡 早些睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.21,0:05:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗 洗澡！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.87,0:05:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你先進去洗也可以哦 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.97,0:05:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.35,0:05:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 那我就先進去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.33,0:05:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？那麼等會兒見
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.39,0:06:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好慢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.41,0:06:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 這到底是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.84,0:06:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.77,0:06:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 總之先穿衣服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.76,0:06:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要轉移對話 我在問這是怎麼一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.72,0:06:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 真抱歉 我做錯了啥…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.83,0:06:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明我入浴了 你為何不來偷窺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.82,0:06:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 你能再說一遍嗎 我貌似聽錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.52,0:06:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明我入浴了 你為何不來偷窺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.03,0:06:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒有和我一起入浴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.69,0:07:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是打算等我入浴了之後再來偷窺的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.12,0:07:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我沒有半點那種打算…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.81,0:07:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.80,0:07:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 這純潔無暇又光滑的皮膚 很漂亮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.93,0:07:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 確實很漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.76,0:07:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣啊 這可是我引以為豪的肌膚哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.80,0:07:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說偷窺 不如說該速推才是王道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.02,0:07:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不 不會不會
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.81,0:07:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為何
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.16,0:07:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說為啥 因為我們是親兄妹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.58,0:07:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄妹之前 我們只是男人和女人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.24,0:07:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是搞反了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.66,0:07:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在男女關係之前 我們可是兄妹哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.89,0:07:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我就再給你次機會
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.04,0:07:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,機會？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.96,0:07:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子現在要再入浴一次
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.15,0:07:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之後的不用我說 你懂的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.69,0:07:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別胡說了 偷窺自己妹妹入浴那種變態的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.58,0:07:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 在你偷窺之前我會一直待在浴室的 你明白了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.95,0:08:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七千一百三十七
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.05,0:08:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七千一百三十八
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.30,0:08:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七千一百三十九
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.55,0:08:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過分 真是太過分了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.53,0:08:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然真的不來偷窺什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.36,0:08:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子真的要生氣了 抽泣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.78,0:08:20.79,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs23}do re mi運輸公司
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.03,0:08:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是全部了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.56,0:08:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別還那麼不開心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.25,0:08:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就拿出點誠意來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.39,0:08:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說誠意是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.43,0:08:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚請和我一起睡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.89,0:08:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子 以前確實我們總是一起睡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.40,0:08:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但現在你和我都已經十六歲了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.37,0:08:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經不是還能一起睡的年齡了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.29,0:08:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.22,0:08:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分了解了 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.05,0:08:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理解我的意思了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.26,0:08:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.05,0:08:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從今天開始就又能和哥哥住在同一個屋簷下了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.78,0:08:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子我想盡可能地聽哥哥的話做一個乖孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.57,0:08:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以和哥哥一起睡的想法我放棄了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.36,0:09:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 想盡可能地滿足你的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.47,0:09:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但只是這個稍微有些…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.33,0:09:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了這句話就已經足夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.36,0:09:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時隔六年不見的哥哥還是一樣溫柔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.71,0:09:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子好高興
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.92,0:09:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 哥哥也變得大膽起來了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.11,0:09:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.09,0:09:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和哥哥相比 我還只是個小孩子而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.79,0:09:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是我的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.21,0:09:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初夜居然不是在被子裡 而是在外面什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.88,0:09:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然很害羞 不過我會加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.63,0:09:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然外面很冷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.40,0:09:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過沒關係 很快就會變得熱起來的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.75,0:09:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等等 你在說些什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.04,0:09:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初夜是指的什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.62,0:09:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相愛的男女迎來的第一個夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.60,0:09:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不知道你是哪裡搞錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.24,0:09:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是要一個人睡的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.98,0:09:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是騙人的吧 這是開玩笑的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.65,0:09:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可是時隔六年不見了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.37,0:09:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是時隔六十年我的回答也是一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.51,0:09:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我們是親兄妹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.90,0:10:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過分 都讓我一直期待到這個份上了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.63,0:10:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子明明都已經這麼興奮了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.99,0:10:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明不管是內心還是身體都已經做好準備了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.01,0:10:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.24,0:10:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 我準備睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.01,0:10:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一個人在我的房間裡睡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.30,0:10:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 肯定是我哪裡搞錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.35,0:10:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是太久沒有和哥哥見面 所以太激動了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.38,0:10:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.57,0:10:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種話我不會再說了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.17,0:10:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從今以後我會像姬小路家的孩子該有的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.52,0:10:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謹慎言行地生活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.44,0:10:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯 不錯的決心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.04,0:10:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也沒有那麼誇張啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.70,0:10:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 真心話是？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.80,0:10:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果哥哥無論如何也不肯坦率地面對我的話
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.76,0:10:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就等到夜深人靜的時候去夜襲…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.64,0:10:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為兄控是種個性
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.06,0:11:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Brother complex 那是只有血親之間才被允許的難得的愛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.22,0:11:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥首先必須要對那份重要性有所認識
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.54,0:11:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真美味啊 這個味噌湯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.12,0:11:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 這是專門為哥哥所做的自信之作
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.24,0:11:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不夠還能添哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.10,0:11:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就再來一碗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.81,0:11:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.47,0:11:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.92,0:11:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多吃一點
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.08,0:11:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼接著 兄控指的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.49,0:11:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個泡菜也很美味呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.81,0:11:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哇
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.56,0:11:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個也是專門為了哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.54,0:11:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而在很早之前就準備好的醃製的醬
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.83,0:11:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合你口味嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.90,0:11:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學會做飯了呢 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.20,0:11:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力地學習過了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.23,0:11:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 兄控指的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.19,0:11:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真亮啊 這燈 果然還是新的好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.32,0:11:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從剛才開始就完全沒有想聽我說話的意思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.15,0:11:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是非常重要的話
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.01,0:11:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 確實那也是不能就這麼放著不管啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.45,0:11:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來將要一起生活的妹妹的性癖
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.76,0:11:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性癖什麼的請不要這麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.58,0:11:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是個性 個性
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.93,0:11:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子的個性
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.93,0:11:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(470,432)\fs23}identity
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.02,0:11:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說到底 你是想說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.27,0:11:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早做了非常可口的早餐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.17,0:11:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是作為獎賞請抱我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.03,0:12:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你腦袋裡到底變成什麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.47,0:12:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥真的變得擔心起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.11,0:12:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 秋子有些得意忘形了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.01,0:12:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道就好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.54,0:12:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱抱就算了 親我一下就足夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.61,0:12:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難度不是越來越高了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.04,0:12:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是抱我一下就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.32,0:12:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才你指的不是單純的抱抱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.39,0:12:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是男女之間的那種關係吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.43,0:12:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 我只要能從哥哥那裡得到獎賞就滿足了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.92,0:12:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼就是不明白呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.57,0:12:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還想發飆呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.27,0:12:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只要能和哥哥卿卿我我就滿足了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.88,0:12:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來哥哥還沒有察覺到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.28,0:12:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是繼續這種沒營養的對話
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.38,0:12:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就已經算是進入了卿卿我我的範圍裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.45,0:12:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果現在的場景被誰看到的話
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.94,0:12:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個人肯定會這樣想的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.73,0:12:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這倆人還真相親相愛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.45,0:12:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就連已經陷入了我的圈套裡都沒有發現
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.49,0:12:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還擺著一副平和的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.32,0:13:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥還真是個可愛的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.91,0:13:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味噌湯再來一碗 超級美味的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.55,0:13:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！再多吃點哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.11,0:13:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好天氣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.47,0:13:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是這時候哥哥能給我來一個膝枕的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.17,0:13:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可就真是無話可說了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.60,0:13:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話先說在前面 我不會幹的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.14,0:13:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是哥哥能給我來一個膝枕的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.70,0:13:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就死而無憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.58,0:13:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下子就變得這麼憂鬱了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.56,0:13:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟是已經建了七十年的房子了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.13,0:13:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屋簷的修理 牆壁的修補
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.43,0:13:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須做的事還有很多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.91,0:13:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼破真對不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.09,0:13:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子只要能和哥哥在一起的話無論哪裡都…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.65,0:13:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是洞窟也好橋下也好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.06,0:13:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝啦 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.93,0:13:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該說謝謝的應該是我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.29,0:13:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我從有栖川家接過來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.14,0:13:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憂鬱的話到此為止
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.03,0:13:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 來繼續收拾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.60,0:14:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗衣服能拜託秋子嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.41,0:14:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.59,0:14:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.56,0:14:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜歡哥哥了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.64,0:14:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也最喜歡秋子了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.97,0:14:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 秋子 沒事吧 振作一點
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.93,0:14:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}臉好紅 難道是發燒了嗎 你沒事吧 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.60,0:14:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和哥哥的兩人獨處的平凡生活
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.07,0:14:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子是幸福的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.78,0:14:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的彷彿在夢裡一般
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.21,0:14:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢裡一般
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.28,0:14:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本應該是和哥哥過著兩人獨處的平凡生活
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.26,0:15:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.20,0:15:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼會變成這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.70,0:15:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是哥哥 只要有愛的就沒關係了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.49,0:15:22.71,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2}聖莉莉安娜學園

Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.35,0:15:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是得要肉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.00,0:15:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牛肉火鍋什麼的怎樣

Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.98,0:15:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要吃龍蝦

Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.20,0:15:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們沒有那麼多預算啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.93,0:15:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能再提出些現實點的提案

Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.16,0:15:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣的話就只有飯糰了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.78,0:15:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有鹽和米飯的話總能有辦法的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.91,0:15:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學生會書記代理副助理
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.48,0:15:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣的話我也就用小龍蝦勉為其難地忍一忍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.72,0:16:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 你覺得什麼好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.91,0:16:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是稍微普通點的建議就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.50,0:16:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說得也是啊 魚料理之類的怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.31,0:16:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.34,0:16:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天商店街的魚類在搞促銷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.85,0:16:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是秋人 著眼點不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.23,0:16:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那就這麼定了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.70,0:16:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼今天的會議就到此為止
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.25,0:16:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.41,0:16:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼啦 姬小路秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.16,0:16:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可愛的臉蛋都糟蹋了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.62,0:16:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事也沒有

Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.68,0:16:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的學生會也真累人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.54,0:16:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那還真不可思議
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.83,0:16:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒看出學生會長像是幹過什麼工作的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.18,0:16:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹活的只有我們幾個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.33,0:16:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.36,0:16:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關心雞毛蒜皮的事的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.89,0:16:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是成不了我這樣的好女人的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.22,0:16:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧 姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.56,0:16:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 能不能稍微分擔一點呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.80,0:16:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.72,0:17:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算讓手無縛雞之力的弱女子拿沉重的東西嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.43,0:17:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手無縛雞之力…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.65,0:17:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作點兒啊 秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.71,0:17:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是這種時刻才輪到男人的出場不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.06,0:17:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話是這麼說啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.65,0:17:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒拿過比筷子更重的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.83,0:17:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是拿著包嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.10,0:17:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.40,0:17:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.25,0:17:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.16,0:17:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話秋人也會高興的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.04,0:17:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.63,0:18:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼需要幫忙的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.69,0:18:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飯菜幾乎都做完了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.48,0:18:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的就是擺放盤子了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.27,0:18:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.40,0:18:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.60,0:18:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.00,0:18:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 開飯了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.14,0:18:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去很好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.45,0:18:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了你下功夫做的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.23,0:18:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合你口味就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.26,0:18:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就趁熱…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.23,0:18:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.82,0:18:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開動之前 有一個必須要決定的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.52,0:18:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須要決定的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.24,0:18:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.43,0:18:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚要坐在誰的旁邊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.98,0:18:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰能餵食他那貪得無厭的嘴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.81,0:18:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.07,0:18:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那確實是個重要的問題呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.69,0:18:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.89,0:19:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想自己吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.97,0:19:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個貪得無厭的嘴 有什麼不願意的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.30,0:19:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那須原同學 那個啥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.93,0:19:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.59,0:19:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能稱呼我為「安娜」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.00,0:19:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我說幾遍你那不開竅的腦袋才能理解呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.79,0:19:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 安娜同學 那個啥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.24,0:19:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然用「穴」來稱呼女人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.78,0:19:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也真是了不得的男人吶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.65,0:19:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能請你別用這種語言套圈子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.19,0:19:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處男就給我閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.56,0:19:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.97,0:19:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該是處男才對呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.59,0:19:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請別說這麼失禮的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.69,0:19:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.74,0:19:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥是名副其實的處男
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.92,0:19:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且會以純潔無暇的樣子成為秋子的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.31,0:19:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.92,0:19:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要不要現在就讓你從處男畢業呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.56,0:19:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.34,0:19:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成為我的情人的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.02,0:19:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚就能畢業哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.82,0:19:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥是不會成為學生會長的情人的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.70,0:19:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥是我的…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.81,0:19:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處女也給我閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.98,0:19:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.68,0:20:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便一提我也是處女 所以我閉嘴了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.91,0:20:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不需要你的這個情報呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.48,0:20:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.83,0:20:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四個人都來做我的對手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.71,0:20:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是秋人要坐在誰身旁的話題呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.12,0:20:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來會有這種爭論本身就不正常了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.91,0:20:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥當然是我的東西啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.87,0:20:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.72,0:20:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 不 書記代理副助理請閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.59,0:20:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最為合適的當然是我了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.94,0:20:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能解說這個飯菜的只有我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.54,0:20:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好解說的話 能讓飯菜變得更為美味
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.07,0:20:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坐在秋人身邊是必然的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.08,0:20:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我才比較合適呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.20,0:20:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了讓今天的飯菜能更好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.17,0:20:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在祈禱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.30,0:20:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊 要是這麼說的話我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.28,0:20:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無謂的話就到此為止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.04,0:20:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經不能允許你們打擾我跟哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.65,0:20:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然微小但幸福的生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.05,0:20:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從一生下來 哥哥就是我的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.46,0:20:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就截止預定 不 截止發售了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.94,0:21:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在才說那種事情也沒有用…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.02,0:21:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.03,0:21:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.05,0:21:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底在說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.28,0:21:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是姬小路秋人的親妹妹嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.80,0:21:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會讓話題變複雜的 請閃一邊去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.27,0:21:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不分清楚立場的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.08,0:21:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.51,0:21:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能坐在身旁餵他的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.26,0:21:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和哥哥的愛是千真萬確的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.03,0:21:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在真愛面前禁忌是毫無意義的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.25,0:21:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣的話 就問問你哥哥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.87,0:21:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣最為省事了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.69,0:21:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥…哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.39,0:21:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子 你是個好孩子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.45,0:21:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.75,0:21:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論何時我都會珍惜你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.90,0:21:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥…哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.87,0:21:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愛你 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.64,0:22:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你幸福就夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.68,0:22:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倆人多般配啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.67,0:22:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然僅僅是作為妹妹哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.23,0:22:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說得也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.61,0:22:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.24,0:22:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.95,0:22:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有愛就沒問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.30,0:24:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.80,0:24:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翹首以盼的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.26,0:24:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依偎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.77,0:24:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.13,0:24:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.39,0:24:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.64,0:24:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.09,0:24:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礙事的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.35,0:24:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會插足進來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.79,0:24:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.13,0:24:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安靜
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.64,0:24:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親吻
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.88,0:24:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擁抱
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.19,0:24:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不論是私通
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.75,0:24:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是偷窺
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.16,0:24:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不論何時
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.45,0:24:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都有機會
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.82,0:24:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼前的肉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.16,0:24:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.50,0:24:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等著你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.91,0:24:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.45,0:24:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這回的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.85,0:24:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,般配
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.10,0:24:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二集
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.47,0:24:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要來看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.91,0:24:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多指教




