
[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Audio File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][08][x264_aac](C47993C5).mkv

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.93,0:21:59.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由动漫国字幕组和轻之国度字幕组联合制作\N仅供试看,请支持购买正版音像制品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:02.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻译:栗花落&枪叔&Cosmo  校对:娜娜莉  时间:Rodax  后期:sora  MKV:乌贼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.74,0:00:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别卖场在这边
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.78,0:00:04.26,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新式泳衣贩卖会
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.72,0:00:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该选哪件真是让人犹豫不决啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.95,0:00:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子姐姐的话 肯定全都合适
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.34,0:00:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 亚里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.97,0:00:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路同学无论穿那件都比不上我的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.05,0:00:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便选一选就好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.27,0:00:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多余的废话也谢了 那须原同学
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.54,0:00:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 亚里沙就不必担心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.61,0:00:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙的身子 对 正介于少女和女性之间的肌肤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.27,0:00:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与青涩果实般的肌肤相称的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.87,0:00:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 可是已经非常认真的为你挑选了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.12,0:00:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原同学 请分清场合再发情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.09,0:00:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过话说回来 现在这个时节竟然就卖泳衣了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.77,0:00:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就应该现在买到好泳衣 不然夏天可就都是别人挑剩下的了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.13,0:01:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳衣可是女人的战斗服呐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.81,0:01:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 各自选择试穿自己喜欢的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.56,0:01:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后开鉴赏会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.94,0:01:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如学生会长所说 泳衣是女人的战斗服
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.86,0:01:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要选能让哥哥与我跨过那一线的泳衣才行！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.70,0:01:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳衣…吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点太土气了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.77,0:01:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等 亚里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.08,0:01:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙穿比基尼还太早了 来 穿这件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.08,0:01:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再让我拜见你那楚楚可怜的泳装姿态
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.89,0:01:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 姬小路秋子 能来帮个忙么？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.11,0:01:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 会长
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.65,0:02:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部无论如何都塞不进去 能帮拉下后面么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.32,0:02:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种小东西怎么可能塞得下会长的胸部啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.74,0:02:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道在这放弃了就等于比赛结束了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.06,0:02:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.43,0:02:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 就是那样 更加用力
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.36,0:02:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 别舍不得啊 更加紧点 再紧点
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.61,0:02:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就…就算你这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.11,0:02:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来个人帮帮忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.57,0:02:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 秋子？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.56,0:03:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙同志 我说过你穿比基尼还太早了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.41,0:03:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是亚里沙想让秋人哥看看更多成熟女性的风范
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.57,0:03:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对这样的亚里沙 我送你一句话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.49,0:03:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各有千秋！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.38,0:03:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各有…千秋？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.84,0:03:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙 你总有一天会成长为完美女性的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.52,0:03:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将有许多男人拜倒在你的比基尼泳装之下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.57,0:03:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在的你只是天真烂漫的可爱少女
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.43,0:03:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么应该选则能将这少女性转化为武器的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.93,0:03:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是武器…吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.21,0:03:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是 而且现在穿这种泳衣也是为了你的将来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.90,0:03:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了将来？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.80,0:03:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请想象看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.60,0:03:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数年后看了身体发育成熟的亚里沙的泳装后阿秋会如何呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.94,0:04:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.39,0:04:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.89,0:04:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么闪耀的比基尼之姿 以前看亚里沙只感觉可爱而已
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.97,0:04:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为大人的亚里沙居然这么…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.68,0:04:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了将来比基尼装的能给他印象更深刻的冲击性效果
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.63,0:04:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还是穿连衣裙式吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.55,0:04:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聪明的小亚里沙应该明白的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.04,0:04:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢 安娜使塔希亚姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.39,0:04:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙会穿安娜史塔希亚姐姐选的这件泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.44,0:04:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.40,0:04:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部那儿稍微有点紧 看来又长大了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.58,0:05:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安娜史塔希亚姐姐的眼光很好 尺寸也刚好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.48,0:05:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.50,0:05:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得的泳衣 再多一些挑战性也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.16,0:05:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长你的也太过了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.72,0:05:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那样吐槽正中会长下怀哦 姬小路同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.21,0:05:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说刚看的泳衣中也没有贝壳式的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.46,0:05:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴露了吗 这个是我的私有物啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.14,0:05:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要把那种当做私有物带着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.56,0:05:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 银兵卫同学为什么不换泳衣呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.28,0:05:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 对我来说那是不需要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.98,0:05:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是明明这儿有那么多可爱的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.48,0:05:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟亚里沙你不同 我高中二年级还是这种幼齿体型
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.29,0:05:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该选哪种泳衣什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.05,0:05:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃了就比赛结束了！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.38,0:05:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.30,0:06:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.84,0:06:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比刚刚的那套泳衣的胸部显得更大了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.32,0:06:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小妮子用了什么魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.93,0:06:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要选择合适自己体型的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.49,0:06:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算穿很暴露的泳衣也能隐藏让自己感到自卑的部位
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.08,0:06:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吊带式比基尼的话 可以很自然的衬起胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.32,0:06:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缎带和装饰褶边可以显得胸部很有料哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.30,0:06:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有选带钢托的比基尼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.75,0:06:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加上胸垫的话 胸部会显得惊人的丰满
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.60,0:06:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想掩饰臀部的话 围上薄纱裙即可
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.89,0:06:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要向别人展示自己修长的双腿的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.65,0:06:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我推荐两边为系结的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.11,0:06:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来不仅仅是越性感越好呐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.99,0:06:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 秋子姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.10,0:06:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让身材看上去更加完美竟做了如此研究
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.73,0:07:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是三围都不如我的姬小路同学呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.44,0:07:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「真不愧」…你这完全不是在表扬我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.38,0:07:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都没说要表扬你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.67,0:07:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.25,0:07:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照秋子的建议来选泳衣的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.64,0:07:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的身材应该会显得好点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.17,0:07:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 百闻不如一见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.02,0:07:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等一等
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.51,0:07:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}这里的肉就这样「姆Q」的来弄
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.46,0:07:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像玩得蛮开心的 我都忍不住也参与进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.86,0:07:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}请不要碰奇怪的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.34,0:07:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想代替秋子去抚摸银银的各种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.35,0:07:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}别乱动 这一切都是为了银兵卫
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.24,0:07:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}好 再垫上胸垫
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.12,0:07:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.89,0:07:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒哦 银兵卫姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.68,0:07:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然还真显出了乳沟啊 你很有一套呢 姬小路秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.46,0:07:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来我是不会帮助陷入困境的对手的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.63,0:08:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要是不在一个起跑线上 连竞争都算不上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.58,0:08:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.91,0:08:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋…秋子姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.56,0:08:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 能帮亚里沙也选一件让胸部看上去大点的泳衣吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.99,0:08:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.46,0:08:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等 亚里沙和银银都无需做那些无谓的努力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.95,0:08:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是白费力气呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.52,0:08:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 就是白费力气的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.05,0:08:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在想起来了 最适合两位的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.47,0:08:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好的泳衣？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.61,0:08:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是 学校泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.83,0:08:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然选的是老式学校泳衣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.99,0:08:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能最大限度让两位的潜能激发出来的泳衣…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.06,0:08:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是学校泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.25,0:08:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准有异议
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.82,0:08:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我期待更可爱的泳衣 安娜史塔希亚姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.96,0:08:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也同意亚里沙刚才的意见
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.85,0:08:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么鹰乃宫亚里沙 这玩意儿怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.52,0:09:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就只是根绳子嘛！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.18,0:09:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种东西给亚里沙穿可是犯罪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.08,0:09:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 那么换个就给银银绑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.91,0:09:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是这样！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.48,0:09:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}不要这么小气嘛 银银
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.94,0:09:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}我的话就合法了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.34,0:09:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}你就忍一下嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.13,0:09:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件泳衣 哥哥喜欢就好呐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.86,0:09:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}这可是性骚扰啊！让我穿这个绝对是性骚扰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.77,0:11:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等不及夏天了X2
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.23,0:11:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就想穿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.65,0:11:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是举行刚购入的泳衣发布大会
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.20,0:11:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有个悲惨少女…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.16,0:11:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等不及夏天了X2
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.57,0:11:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就想穿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.99,0:11:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是举行…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.05,0:11:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 不是没听见啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.21,0:11:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是听见却理解不了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.14,0:11:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都想让秋人看看今天买的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.43,0:11:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 不过你们泳衣买的还真早呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.67,0:11:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是这样呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.48,0:11:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道吗秋人 现在不入手好泳衣的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.80,0:11:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到夏天的话就剩下挑剩的了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.41,0:11:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子还真辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.19,0:11:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大会的目的极其单纯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.63,0:11:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是看姬小路秋人最中意谁的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.48,0:12:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.44,0:12:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银兵卫姐姐不参加这个大会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.89,0:12:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.00,0:12:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要一直等到夏天来临呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.17,0:12:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银银的泳衣造型我倒是有些等不到夏天呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.54,0:12:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真对不住
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.22,0:12:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有把你的愿望一同考虑进去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.78,0:12:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 参加与否
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.02,0:12:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在听了优胜奖励之后再决定也无妨嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.83,0:12:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窃窃私语中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.24,0:12:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲怆？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.60,0:12:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是这样的合格奖励
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.32,0:12:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来到了我发挥真正实力的时刻了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.23,0:12:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙也要竭尽全力加油了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.27,0:12:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.22,0:12:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不得不参加了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.95,0:12:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.91,0:12:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就全员参加了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.96,0:12:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发布会现在开始！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.86,0:12:48.49,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.70,0:12:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们各自在自己的房间里等着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.61,0:12:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就按顺序到各房间中审查泳衣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.76,0:13:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别的人先不提
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.97,0:13:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙的泳衣应该没什么问题的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.54,0:13:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.34,0:13:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.28,0:13:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.86,0:13:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊 打扮成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.20,0:13:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安娜史塔西亚姐姐说了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.05,0:13:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个对于亚里沙来说最合适
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.20,0:13:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对翅膀也是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.70,0:13:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了亚里沙而特意准备的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.91,0:13:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.46,0:13:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙太温柔了才会被弄成那样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.76,0:13:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.08,0:13:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又为了这样的东西而动用了老家的力量吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.55,0:13:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原同学…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.42,0:13:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.20,0:13:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.98,0:13:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.17,0:13:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对那样的打扮做出爱意的评价
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.34,0:13:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有各种各样的问题呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.02,0:14:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别！好可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.38,0:14:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙真的是不管穿什么都好可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.29,0:14:10.02,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安娜·史塔西亚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.48,0:14:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原同学
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.76,0:14:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于亚里沙的泳衣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.78,0:14:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.17,0:14:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请称呼我为安喵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.97,0:14:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说几遍你才能明白喵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.03,0:14:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说这小聪明有些过头了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.90,0:14:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.69,0:14:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你能别这么说喵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.48,0:14:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是耍小聪明呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.51,0:14:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手别用这种方式伸进去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.15,0:14:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.17,0:14:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个穿着泳衣的安娜人偶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.67,0:14:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你特意制作的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.07,0:14:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是喵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.13,0:14:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个猫状物安娜人偶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.13,0:14:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那须原重工技术精髓凝结成的特制品
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.73,0:14:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大到宇宙船 小到门把手的螺丝钉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.75,0:14:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向世界输出几乎全部的工业制品的大企业
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.22,0:14:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要把技术的结晶浪费在这种无谓的东西上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.27,0:14:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是喵须原…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.63,0:14:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.46,0:15:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原同学是那须原重工的千金啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.52,0:15:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢你细致的解说喵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.72,0:15:08.70,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.39,0:15:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.13,0:15:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.49,0:15:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.95,0:15:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到连你也参加了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.65,0:15:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,优胜奖励就这么有魅力吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.17,0:15:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 差不多就是那样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.95,0:15:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.07,0:15:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.10,0:15:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长同学真是让人伤脑筋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.20,0:15:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.30,0:15:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.08,0:15:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.57,0:15:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是觉得没有比得不到回报的努力更可悲的了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.67,0:15:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 来喝些茶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.24,0:15:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.23,0:15:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.34,0:15:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杯垫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.35,0:15:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.39,0:15:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是茶水的杯垫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.66,0:15:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 说的是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.87,0:15:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.31,0:16:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.87,0:16:12.56,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.77,0:16:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个是会长吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.20,0:16:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.36,0:16:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该说是在开门之前就感到了无比的压力呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.53,0:16:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 来得真晚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.86,0:16:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.35,0:16:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.49,0:16:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 怎么了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.64,0:16:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还问我怎么了 你那不是什么都没穿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.67,0:16:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好穿着呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.35,0:16:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹控看不到的泳衣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.42,0:16:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是妹控
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.35,0:16:50.07,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 大家都懂的 捏他「皇帝的新装」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.19,0:16:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 请快穿上些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.46,0:16:57.06,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.43,0:16:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子 我进去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.13,0:17:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿 怎么样啊哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.38,0:17:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.69,0:17:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.06,0:17:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能被哥哥这样普普通通地夸奖
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.38,0:17:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于察觉到秋子的魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.30,0:17:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而下定了跨过那一线的决心了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.91,0:17:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不啊 谁也没下那样的决心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.35,0:17:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.54,0:17:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然普通的才是最好的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.14,0:17:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.52,0:17:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥！说我的泳衣普通是怎么一回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.32,0:17:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是因为呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.81,0:17:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都不是单单穿上泳衣就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.10,0:17:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是费尽心思加上一些意想不到的东西出来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.52,0:17:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 我也这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.08,0:17:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个已经见过了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.92,0:17:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这个怎么样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.63,0:17:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个也已经见过了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.87,0:17:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那干脆就…脱光了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.61,0:17:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个也见过了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.49,0:17:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么一回事啊！哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.48,0:18:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅是个观赏泳衣姿态的活动
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.97,0:18:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会搞的我这么累啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.21,0:18:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边是空房间的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.63,0:18:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是猫什么的跑进去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.16,0:18:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.62,0:18:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也受到了会长同学的邀请
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.28,0:18:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想来参加泳衣大赛的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.48,0:18:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近刚买了泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.44,0:18:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要快一点穿上…的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.66,0:18:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.89,0:18:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公布冠军是谁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.29,0:18:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没法决定
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.78,0:18:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是优柔寡断
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.02,0:18:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 虽然也猜到你会这么说了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.27,0:18:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次明明觉得我一定能赢呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.84,0:18:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.84,0:18:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了许多事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.78,0:18:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就泳衣而论 大家都很合适啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.56,0:18:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.41,0:18:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着输给某人的泳衣去大海的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.41,0:18:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心情也会不爽的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.82,0:18:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.82,0:18:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这样的话就可以接受了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.63,0:18:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.75,0:18:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.06,0:19:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次是全员获胜就行了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.55,0:19:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉那样就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.59,0:19:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼哼哼哼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.72,0:19:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选出姬小路秋人穿着的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.79,0:19:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是获胜奖励
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.65,0:19:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当然会穿所有人的泳衣了对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.01,0:19:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.82,0:19:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.93,0:19:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上这个泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.22,0:19:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起到沙滩上欢快的追逐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.89,0:19:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我生活在一起的阿秋土得掉渣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.67,0:19:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选了一件稍微华丽些的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.69,0:19:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人游泳很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.55,0:19:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得竞技泳衣很不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.13,0:19:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.56,0:19:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愿意和亚里沙穿情侣装吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.61,0:19:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.07,0:19:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然也准备了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.45,0:19:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.36,0:19:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才不是泳衣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.93,0:19:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在意细微的地方啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.83,0:19:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快穿上试试看哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.03,0:19:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.60,0:19:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这里把衣服脱了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.30,0:19:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还准备了不同的颜色哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.42,0:19:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也穿一次我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.40,0:19:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尺码可能有点小
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.61,0:19:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但应该是没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.87,0:20:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.95,0:20:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个泳衣也是哥哥在鹰乃宫家中时的东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.25,0:20:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许稍微有些小了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.16,0:20:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请试穿一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.07,0:20:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿这个你不满意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.76,0:20:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.99,0:20:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有工作
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.37,0:20:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃走了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.84,0:20:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.68,0:20:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.31,0:20:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃跑也是没用的！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.12,0:20:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.69,0:20:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.47,0:20:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会放跑你的啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.08,0:20:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我站住
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.92,0:20:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买了泳衣就应该大胆穿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.76,0:21:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看招
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.84,0:21:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.98,0:21:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来 哥哥也来一起玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.03,0:21:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了 容我敬谢不敏
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.20,0:21:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家为什么要穿着泳衣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.48,0:21:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为夏天还没到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.44,0:21:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易买了泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.46,0:21:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放着不穿泳衣会寂寞的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.27,0:21:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概就是这么回事 我也打算奉陪一阵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.40,0:21:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.31,0:21:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 我还有工作…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.21,0:21:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.34,0:22:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好秋人君
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.84,0:22:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原稿我拜读过了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.14,0:22:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禁忌之爱的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.51,0:22:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄妹合体Akingelion#亚金艾里翁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.66,0:22:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写的太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.84,0:22:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢夸奖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.50,0:22:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然只是高中生
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.10,0:22:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乘上巨大机器人作战的兄妹的苦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.98,0:22:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赌上性命的战斗中 不断加深的兄妹的禁断之爱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.87,0:22:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又有了新点子了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.52,0:22:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是后半部分产生了力量失衡了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.23,0:22:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个也让我很在意呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.59,0:24:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绞尽脑汁的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.14,0:24:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行为
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.47,0:24:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银银
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.99,0:24:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追逐
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.40,0:24:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.83,0:24:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赌上
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.29,0:24:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢乐的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.77,0:24:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stop
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.33,0:24:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.70,0:24:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶搞剧透
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.28,0:24:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.80,0:24:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勉勉强强
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.99,0:24:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一次
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.46,0:24:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预告
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.86,0:24:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.31,0:24:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绞尽脑汁的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.72,0:24:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行为
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.10,0:24:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银银
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.54,0:24:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追逐
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.99,0:24:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.46,0:24:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赌上
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.96,0:24:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stop
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.42,0:24:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和刚才
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.93,0:24:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一样
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.35,0:24:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.84,0:24:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶搞剧透
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.35,0:24:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.84,0:24:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄控
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.28,0:24:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第九话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.69,0:24:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥-哥-


