
[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Audio File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][11][x264_aac](1E127165).mkv
Video File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][11][x264_aac](1E127165).mkv
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 2
Video Position: 5061
Video Color Matrix: BT.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.93,0:21:59.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由動漫國字幕組和輕之國度字幕組聯合製作\N僅供試看,請支持購買正版音像製品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:02.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻譯:栗花落&槍叔&Cosmo  校對:娜娜莉  時間:Rodax  後期:sora  MKV:烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.77,0:00:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是惹人恥笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.60,0:00:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是深受聖莉莉安娜學園學子們的尊崇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.12,0:00:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界上有名的那須原重工的繼承人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.73,0:00:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精英里的精英…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.79,0:00:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那須原安娜使塔希亞的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.72,0:00:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真傷腦筋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.61,0:00:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能找的地方都已經找了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.45,0:00:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.10,0:00:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脫下的衣服要疊好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.02,0:00:35.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,東西用過之後要放回原地
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.64,0:00:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我這身子 說實話…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.92,0:00:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是腦子裡明白
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.71,0:00:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是辦不到的事就是辦不到
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.78,0:00:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 那須原安娜使塔希亞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.01,0:00:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是家事無能的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.06,0:00:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然可以讓阿秋來收拾屋子就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.93,0:00:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但總不是長遠之計
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.82,0:00:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說 真是傷腦筋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.85,0:00:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.33,0:01:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出浴之後 居然找不到內衣了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.92,0:01:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要在這堆衣服裡面找出內衣是根本不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.11,0:01:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脫下的內衣一定是已經…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.60,0:01:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在洗衣機裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.50,0:01:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.09,0:01:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天只好就這樣渡過一天了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.86,0:01:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是亞里沙的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.96,0:01:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能丟車保帥了…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.55,0:01:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等著我 亞里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.82,0:01:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在就過去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.85,0:01:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次第 怎一個涼字了得
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.95,0:03:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙 怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.21,0:03:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那裡 好像有什麼東西…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.94,0:03:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼東西在那裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.50,0:03:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難不成是癡漢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.91,0:03:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要真的是癡漢 看來膽子不小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.67,0:03:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色狼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.46,0:03:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看的不是很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.71,0:03:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閃爍著好多綠色的光 還發出沙沙的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.05,0:03:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像在那邊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.36,0:03:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綠色的光？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.96,0:03:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.13,0:03:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得好嚇人…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.46,0:03:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜視鏡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.21,0:03:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難不成…是那個？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.56,0:04:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「那個」…是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.11,0:04:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個自然是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.62,0:04:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然說了是「那個」 當然就是… 對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.48,0:04:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論是什麼情況都要藉機性騷擾一番
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.85,0:04:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋還真是一如既往的色膽包天呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.92,0:04:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像你們非常失禮的誤會了我什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.28,0:04:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之不是那樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.62,0:04:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有那種意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.76,0:04:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你說說 是哪個「那個」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.53,0:04:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是…「那個」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.24,0:04:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漸漸的夏天也快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.24,0:04:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是出現也不會很奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.85,0:04:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道說…秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.47,0:04:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲 咕咚咕咚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.81,0:04:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙你的 開玩笑的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.77,0:04:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.19,0:04:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這世上是不存在什麼魑魅魍魎的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.55,0:04:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就…就是說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.71,0:04:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別嚇人家嘛 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.98,0:04:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是就是 太不科學了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.66,0:04:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都高二了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.33,0:04:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還說的像是妖怪真實存在一般…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.91,0:04:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實在是可悲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.75,0:04:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說的這話真是太愚昧無知了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.54,0:04:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所謂的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.18,0:05:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過是人類心理陰暗面孕育出的假象而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.78,0:05:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是從心理學角度去研究這個現象的話倒還罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.39,0:05:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然當做它真的存在去討論…呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.80,0:05:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.64,0:05:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒…沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.15,0:05:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 大家都冷靜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.44,0:05:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不愧是會長 臨危不亂好鎮靜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.21,0:05:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然 只有女人小孩才會害怕妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.82,0:05:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.76,0:05:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去轉轉 看看哪些地方有什麼奇怪的變化
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.48,0:05:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我倒是可以去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.13,0:05:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長你不和我一起去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.82,0:05:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜 這種情況下…學生會長就應該坐鎮指揮
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.14,0:05:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去搜索打探的任務
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.19,0:05:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該由你這個打下手的去做
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.88,0:05:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴上是說的很勇敢 但是實際上卻…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.39,0:05:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的腳好像在篩糠子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.77,0:05:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你別說傻話了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.68,0:05:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家哪裡發抖了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.46,0:05:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來會長也害怕妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.66,0:06:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都說我不害怕啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.80,0:06:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快給我去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.11,0:06:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.54,0:06:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.70,0:06:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.00,0:06:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 我相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.68,0:06:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 阿秋一定會活著回來的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.29,0:06:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我稍微去轉一轉就回來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.40,0:06:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有誰要和我一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.46,0:06:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來是不能指望了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.84,0:06:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是…難得的機會
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.34,0:06:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在漆黑的深夜裡與哥哥的二人世界
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.60,0:06:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要和哥哥一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.51,0:06:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你膽子真大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.53,0:06:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.21,0:06:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 要是哥哥害怕的話請不要客氣儘管抱著我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.28,0:06:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在這之前 我們先牽著手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.01,0:06:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你內心想什麼都一目瞭然了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.05,0:06:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.92,0:06:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是常說要患難與共嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.03,0:06:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是千載難逢的機會
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.83,0:06:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 讓秋人一個人去也太可憐了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.50,0:06:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.85,0:07:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還可以稍微讓你一覽裙底風光哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.33,0:07:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前言收回
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.53,0:07:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了防止阿秋做出性騷擾舉動
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.28,0:07:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有必要監視你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.38,0:07:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是那樣的話我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.77,0:07:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔細一想的話
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.04,0:07:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是推倒秋人絕佳的機會啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.55,0:07:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請等一等 亞里沙 亞里沙也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.58,0:07:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 我們都一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.56,0:07:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.93,0:07:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你指的是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.78,0:07:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請不要發出奇怪的聲音 嚇死人的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.19,0:07:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是說我嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.07,0:07:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.63,0:07:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你聽錯了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.49,0:07:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀…再怎麼說這個不會聽錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.23,0:08:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒看到什麼可疑的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.15,0:08:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.45,0:08:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 剛才開始草就好紮腳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.75,0:08:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 大家要不要再過一會就回去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.40,0:08:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙不擅長待在這種地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.01,0:08:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 你的建議不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.38,0:08:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 從剛才就這樣 到底怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.43,0:08:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是我的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.43,0:08:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到底是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.54,0:08:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把耳朵豎尖點好好聽聽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.71,0:08:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.39,0:08:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連隻蟲的聲音都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.17,0:08:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處女是聽不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.97,0:08:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.67,0:08:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處女
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.69,0:08:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.86,0:08:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便一提 我也是處女 所以什麼也沒聽到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.20,0:08:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便一提 我也是處…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.25,0:08:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻過這裡 應該就是回到宿舍的近路了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.22,0:08:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺翻牆有點不容易的樣子哇
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.55,0:09:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 我有個好想法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.57,0:09:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想法？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.70,0:09:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要哥哥能讓我騎在脖子上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.79,0:09:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能很簡單的上去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.60,0:09:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 騎脖子啊 是很不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.40,0:09:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我贊成
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.56,0:09:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙也贊成 和秋人哥哥騎脖子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.83,0:09:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也贊成
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.56,0:09:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長你自己能夠上去的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.51,0:09:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的假設只是咱倆交換位置來著的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.25,0:09:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 副會長
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.04,0:09:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騎脖子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.36,0:09:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？你怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.97,0:09:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒…沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.54,0:09:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 哥哥的騎脖子到底是時隔多少年沒有感受到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.90,0:09:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經沒有什麼遺憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.75,0:09:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也太誇張了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.98,0:09:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙太幸福了 已經不想從這裡下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.38,0:09:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣的話還是有點…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.34,0:10:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會重很嗎 秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.24,0:10:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不會啊 不如說是輕過頭了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.34,0:10:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要多吃點才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.42,0:10:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是說我成長的太慢了的意思嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.61,0:10:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請…請快點下去 會長
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.54,0:10:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不要這麼見外嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.58,0:10:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也來吧 那須原同學
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.34,0:10:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚥口水…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.48,0:10:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那須原同學？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.49,0:10:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要上了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.70,0:10:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼好像後腦勺有種特殊的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.90,0:10:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 我們走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.08,0:11:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微慢點 會長
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.60,0:11:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人都去哪裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.88,0:11:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 能鬆手嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.63,0:11:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以不用那麼客氣的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.12,0:11:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不會呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.10,0:11:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說你啊 那種程度就嚇得亂跑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.50,0:11:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的有蛋嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.51,0:11:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先開跑的人是會長吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.21,0:11:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才沒有跑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.34,0:11:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.64,0:11:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹…幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.35,0:11:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還以為能就這麼順勢推倒你的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.69,0:12:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是太掃興了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.99,0:12:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.24,0:12:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.28,0:12:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我等下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.40,0:12:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能再稍微隔開一點嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.06,0:12:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.01,0:12:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 銀兵衛姐姐 大家都不知去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.81,0:12:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 我們也快點回宿舍吧 亞里沙君
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.00,0:12:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的已經受不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.46,0:12:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀兵衛姐姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.88,0:12:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才十二歲 就和我有差不多的乳量
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.66,0:12:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事怎麼可能
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.61,0:12:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.01,0:12:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.20,0:12:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之先回宿舍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.30,0:12:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這邊吧 不對 是那邊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.66,0:13:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 這樣走起來很累
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.96,0:13:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不介意的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.71,0:13:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很介意的說
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.36,0:13:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 那須原同學 發生了什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.51,0:13:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚 感覺你的表情一直都很生硬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.45,0:13:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還發出了很怪的聲音 難道是身體不舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.39,0:13:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路同學 我和平時一樣是正常體溫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.40,0:13:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,體重 體溫 血壓也都是非常健康的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.61,0:13:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的我有表情生硬的需要嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.95,0:13:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…只是不知為何覺得是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.57,0:13:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知為何
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.43,0:13:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說你沒有任何根據就說我和平時不一樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.83,0:13:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我就覺得是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.85,0:13:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真服了你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.14,0:13:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是考試成績不如我在學校裡人氣也不如我的你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.06,0:13:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是無法理解我這種等級比你高的存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.78,0:14:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又把以前的舊事拿出來說
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.54,0:14:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且成績和選美什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.47,0:14:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟我根本就什麼差別吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.33,0:14:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.23,0:14:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總是欺負幹什麼都比不上我的你也不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.90,0:14:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼 我的人生目標又不是要贏那須原同學
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.28,0:14:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我人生目標全是只為了深愛的哥哥一人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.77,0:14:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能和哥哥結婚的話 我就能成為絕對的贏家
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.10,0:14:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿足的享受今後的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.19,0:14:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢 和有著血緣關係的哥哥結婚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.02,0:14:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能的話就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.83,0:14:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑了吧 你嘲笑我了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.33,0:14:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也就只有現在能這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.49,0:14:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總有一天我要成為這個國家的首相
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.97,0:14:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頒布一條有血緣關係的兄妹也能結婚的法律
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.91,0:14:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那時你想反悔也沒用了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.03,0:14:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.03,0:14:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.83,0:14:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又這樣把我當笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.23,0:14:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才沒有把你當笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.50,0:15:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 從來沒有把你當作笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.03,0:15:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六年前 從與你見面的第一天開始
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.25,0:15:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到現在一直
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.62,0:15:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉安娜學園小學
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.74,0:15:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五年級的時候的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.35,0:15:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好 初次見面 我是姬小路…不對 有棲川
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.26,0:15:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有棲川秋子 因為各種事 轉學到這裡來了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.50,0:15:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請大家從今天開始多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.44,0:15:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.10,0:15:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和人偶一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.61,0:15:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那須原同學比誰更可愛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.81,0:15:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾想 這是何等…何等可愛的女孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.83,0:15:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像要被吸走一般烏黑的秀髮
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.03,0:15:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那堅強 而又溫柔的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.74,0:16:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.14,0:16:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白瓷般的臉頰上所透出的微微紅暈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.71,0:16:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彷彿像是散落在初雪上的紅色花瓣一般
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.01,0:16:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.80,0:16:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那份美貌之下似乎隱約能看到一層陰影
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.97,0:16:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.36,0:16:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對她在意了起來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.85,0:16:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問 有什麼事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.13,0:16:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.17,0:16:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是看看你有沒有長痘痘
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.43,0:16:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年輕時的痘痘還是早點治療比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.71,0:16:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然會留下痕跡的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.70,0:16:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才盯著你的臉看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.34,0:16:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.44,0:16:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.44,0:16:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.69,0:16:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在自我介紹時說錯了姓氏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.82,0:16:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼隱情嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.75,0:16:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是很想要知道就是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.21,0:16:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 不想說就別說了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.18,0:16:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 沒關係的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.54,0:16:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是什麼要藏起來的事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.61,0:16:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 其實
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.13,0:17:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是 你說明了事情的原委
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.21,0:17:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雙親的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.63,0:17:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與哥哥分別被不同家庭收養的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.78,0:17:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 兄妹天各一方很寂寞呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.72,0:17:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 哥哥答應我了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.47,0:17:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總有一天一定會再和我一起生活
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.30,0:17:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 那還真不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.64,0:17:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.51,0:17:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信哥哥的話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.21,0:17:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我決心要成為一個好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.18,0:17:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了與哥哥重逢的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.94,0:17:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會令他感到失望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.67,0:17:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 你很喜歡哥哥嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.54,0:17:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 最喜歡哥哥了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.97,0:17:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個時候的我還完全無法想像
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.58,0:17:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然對有血緣關係的親哥哥的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.04,0:17:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是喜歡 而是愛情的愛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.04,0:17:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(366,438)\fs23}Like
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.04,0:17:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(486,438)\fs23}Love
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.07,0:17:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之後的六年
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.29,0:17:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我同她之間在某種意義上是互為對手的關係
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.75,0:17:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實我只是很普通的想跟她搞好關係而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.61,0:18:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.53,0:18:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我頗為傲嬌的性格也是個小問題啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.70,0:18:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於能跟哥哥一同生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.69,0:18:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真是可喜可賀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.19,0:18:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是你一直念叨著的夢想呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.45,0:18:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是很好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.63,0:18:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.51,0:18:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.37,0:18:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的哥哥 是什麼樣的傢伙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.04,0:18:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讓你不顧血緣關係而如此迷戀的人物
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.81,0:18:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是個相當好的男人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.75,0:18:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說是不是啊 副會長
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.82,0:18:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也有興趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.71,0:18:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.92,0:18:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不關我的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.97,0:18:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.09,0:18:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然很感興趣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.11,0:18:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.36,0:18:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想趁早見見呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.20,0:18:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我當然有興趣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.43,0:18:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把親哥哥作為戀愛的對象什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.77,0:18:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是何方神聖才能如此吸引著她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.85,0:19:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.97,0:19:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊是小學部
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.19,0:19:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊是初中部
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.70,0:19:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那對面有圖書館
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.06,0:19:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了嗎 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.14,0:19:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.37,0:19:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還不能全部記住呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.41,0:19:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.65,0:19:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥肯定很快就適應了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.13,0:19:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就能每天清晨與哥哥一起上學了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.60,0:19:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很期待
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.69,0:19:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我也很期待
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.48,0:19:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差不多該去學生會露個臉了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.16,0:19:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.91,0:19:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之後我會自己隨便逛逛的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.97,0:19:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起啊哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.40,0:19:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先走一步了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.21,0:19:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.14,0:19:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請給我送別的吻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.65,0:19:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會給你的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.02,0:19:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.49,0:19:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不 用常識想想啊 常識
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.81,0:19:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼噠 哥哥這個吝嗇鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.86,0:19:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之後即使再怎麼想親我也晚了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.33,0:20:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.11,0:20:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大白天就對女性品頭論足
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.92,0:20:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真有福氣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.13,0:20:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.86,0:20:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.82,0:20:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛出浴沒有換穿的衣服 真是悲哀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.41,0:20:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們結婚吧 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.61,0:20:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 結婚吧 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.09,0:20:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准你娶我了 謝恩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.40,0:20:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝主隆恩
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.57,0:20:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很開心哦 那須原同學
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.09,0:20:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.82,0:20:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵 秋人哥哥請跟我結婚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.96,0:20:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然可以啊 亞里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.35,0:20:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很樂意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.41,0:20:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 我會成為你的好媳婦的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.55,0:20:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 銀兵衛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.19,0:20:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也覺得自己會成為你的好丈夫的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.02,0:20:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人君 會討厭歲數比你大的老婆嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.50,0:20:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 怎麼會呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.37,0:21:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然歡迎之至了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.40,0:21:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今後也請多多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.40,0:21:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不論是公事還是私事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.48,0:21:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來來 大家一起迎接初夜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.36,0:21:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是鋪好床鋪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.70,0:21:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖~乖~
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.12,0:21:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵 睡得真香啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.49,0:21:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搖籃曲兒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.22,0:21:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖啦乖啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.01,0:21:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 這裡開著個洞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.70,0:21:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請進到裡面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.66,0:21:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都吃飽噯氣了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.96,0:21:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼認真地在吸著
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.01,0:21:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟昨晚的爸爸一樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.88,0:21:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請別這樣啦會長
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 你想稱呼我會長到什麼時候
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.53,0:21:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.47,0:21:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前的習慣總是改不了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.39,0:21:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嵐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.20,0:21:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.54,0:21:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子 亞里沙 銀 安娜 薰子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.44,0:21:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是世界上最幸福的男人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.18,0:21:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.32,0:21:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們來玩啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.83,0:22:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.05,0:22:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是長大了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.77,0:22:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟他爸爸長得一模一樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.21,0:22:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.21,0:22:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.26,0:22:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要尿尿嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.38,0:22:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要小便嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.50,0:22:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輪到爸爸出場了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.96,0:22:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 就交給我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.72,0:22:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先把…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.34,0:22:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 快饒了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.43,0:22:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是夢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.96,0:22:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊還在發燒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.86,0:22:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且差不多該要工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.38,0:24:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,季節
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.07,0:24:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交替
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.60,0:24:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.08,0:24:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告別
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.60,0:24:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.01,0:24:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相見之日
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.52,0:24:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屈指
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.96,0:24:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可數
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.47,0:24:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暫且
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.98,0:24:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結束
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.45,0:24:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.87,0:24:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.36,0:24:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淚水
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.83,0:24:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.23,0:24:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.69,0:24:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑起來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.10,0:24:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.62,0:24:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會更好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.12,0:24:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄控
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.58,0:24:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不覺
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.02,0:24:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.54,0:24:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.05,0:24:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.51,0:24:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咕嘿嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.97,0:24:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.53,0:24:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.01,0:24:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄愛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.46,0:24:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十二集
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.92,0:24:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.49,0:24:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜歡了


