
[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Audio File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][11][x264_aac](1E127165).mkv
Video File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][11][x264_aac](1E127165).mkv
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 2
Video Position: 31527
Video Color Matrix: BT.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.93,0:21:59.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由动漫国字幕组和轻之国度字幕组联合制作\N仅供试看,请支持购买正版音像制品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:02.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻译:栗花落&枪叔&Cosmo  校对:娜娜莉  时间:Rodax  后期:sora  MKV:乌贼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.77,0:00:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是惹人耻笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.60,0:00:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是深受圣莉莉安娜学园学子们的尊崇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.12,0:00:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界上有名的那须原重工的继承人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.73,0:00:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精英里的精英…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.79,0:00:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原安娜使塔希亚的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.72,0:00:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真伤脑筋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.61,0:00:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能找的地方都已经找了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.45,0:00:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.10,0:00:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱下的衣服要叠好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.02,0:00:35.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东西用过之后要放回原地
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.64,0:00:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我这身子 说实话…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.92,0:00:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是脑子里明白
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.71,0:00:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是办不到的事就是办不到
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.78,0:00:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 那须原安娜使塔希亚
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.01,0:00:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是家事无能的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.06,0:00:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然可以让阿秋来收拾屋子就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.93,0:00:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但总不是长远之计
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.82,0:00:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 真是伤脑筋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.85,0:00:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.33,0:01:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出浴之后 居然找不到内衣了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.92,0:01:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要在这堆衣服里面找出内衣是根本不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.11,0:01:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱下的内衣一定是已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.60,0:01:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在洗衣机里了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.50,0:01:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.09,0:01:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天只好就这样渡过一天了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.86,0:01:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是亚里沙的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.96,0:01:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能丢车保帅了…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.55,0:01:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着我 亚里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.82,0:01:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就过去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.85,0:01:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次第 怎一个凉字了得

Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.95,0:03:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.21,0:03:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那里 好像有什么东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.94,0:03:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么东西在那里？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.50,0:03:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成是痴汉？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.91,0:03:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要真的是痴汉 看来胆子不小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.67,0:03:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色狼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.46,0:03:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看的不是很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.71,0:03:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪烁着好多绿色的光 还发出沙沙的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.05,0:03:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像在那边…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.36,0:03:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绿色的光？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.96,0:03:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.13,0:03:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得好吓人…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.46,0:03:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜视镜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.21,0:03:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成…是那个？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.56,0:04:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「那个」…是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.11,0:04:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个自然是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.62,0:04:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然说了是「那个」 当然就是… 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.48,0:04:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是什么情况都要借机性骚扰一番
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.85,0:04:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋还真是一如既往的色胆包天呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.92,0:04:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像你们非常失礼的误会了我什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.28,0:04:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之不是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.62,0:04:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那种意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.76,0:04:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你说说 是哪个「那个」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.53,0:04:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是…「那个」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.24,0:04:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渐渐的夏天也快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.24,0:04:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是出现也不会很奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.85,0:04:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.47,0:04:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 咕咚咕咚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.81,0:04:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗你的 开玩笑的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.77,0:04:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.19,0:04:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这世上是不存在什么魑魅魍魉的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.55,0:04:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就…就是说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.71,0:04:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别吓人家嘛 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.98,0:04:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是就是 太不科学了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.66,0:04:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都高二了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.33,0:04:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说的像是妖怪真实存在一般…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.91,0:04:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是可悲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.75,0:04:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的这话真是太愚昧无知了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.54,0:04:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.18,0:05:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是人类心理阴暗面孕育出的假象而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.78,0:05:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是从心理学角度去研究这个现象的话倒还罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.39,0:05:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然当做它真的存在去讨论…呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.80,0:05:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.64,0:05:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.15,0:05:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 大家都冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.44,0:05:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不愧是会长 临危不乱好镇静
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.21,0:05:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然 只有女人小孩才会害怕妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.82,0:05:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.76,0:05:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去转转 看看哪些地方有什么奇怪的变化
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.48,0:05:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我倒是可以去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.13,0:05:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长你不和我一起去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.82,0:05:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜 这种情况下…学生会长就应该坐镇指挥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.14,0:05:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去搜索打探的任务
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.19,0:05:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该由你这个打下手的去做
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.88,0:05:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴上是说的很勇敢 但是实际上却…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.39,0:05:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的脚好像在筛糠子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.77,0:05:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你别说傻话了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.68,0:05:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家哪里发抖了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.46,0:05:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来会长也害怕妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.66,0:06:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说我不害怕啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.80,0:06:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快给我去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.11,0:06:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.54,0:06:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.70,0:06:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.00,0:06:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 我相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.68,0:06:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 阿秋一定会活着回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.29,0:06:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我稍微去转一转就回来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.40,0:06:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有谁要和我一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.46,0:06:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是不能指望了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.84,0:06:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是…难得的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.34,0:06:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在漆黑的深夜里与哥哥的二人世界
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.60,0:06:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要和哥哥一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.51,0:06:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你胆子真大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.53,0:06:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.21,0:06:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 要是哥哥害怕的话请不要客气尽管抱着我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.28,0:06:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在这之前 我们先牵着手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.01,0:06:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你内心想什么都一目了然了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.05,0:06:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.92,0:06:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是常说要患难与共嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.03,0:06:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是千载难逢的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.83,0:06:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 让秋人一个人去也太可怜了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.50,0:06:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.85,0:07:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还可以稍微让你一览裙底风光哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.33,0:07:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前言收回
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.53,0:07:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了防止阿秋做出性骚扰举动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.28,0:07:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有必要监视你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.38,0:07:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是那样的话我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.77,0:07:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细一想的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.04,0:07:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是推倒秋人绝佳的机会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.55,0:07:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请等一等 亚里沙 亚里沙也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.58,0:07:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 我们都一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.56,0:07:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.93,0:07:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你指的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.78,0:07:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要发出奇怪的声音 吓死人的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.19,0:07:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.07,0:07:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.63,0:07:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听错了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.49,0:07:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀…再怎么说这个不会听错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.23,0:08:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没看到什么可疑的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.15,0:08:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.45,0:08:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 刚才开始草就好扎脚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.75,0:08:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 大家要不要再过一会就回去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.40,0:08:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙不擅长待在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.01,0:08:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 你的建议不错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.38,0:08:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 从刚才就这样 到底怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.43,0:08:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是我的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.43,0:08:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到底是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.54,0:08:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把耳朵竖尖点好好听听
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.71,0:08:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.39,0:08:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连只虫的声音都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.17,0:08:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处女是听不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.97,0:08:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.67,0:08:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处女
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.69,0:08:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.86,0:08:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便一提 我也是处女 所以什么也没听到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.20,0:08:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便一提 我也是处…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.25,0:08:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻过这里 应该就是回到宿舍的近路了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.22,0:08:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉翻墙有点不容易的样子哇
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.55,0:09:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 我有个好想法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.57,0:09:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想法？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.70,0:09:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要哥哥能让我骑在脖子上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.79,0:09:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能很简单的上去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.60,0:09:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 骑脖子啊 是很不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.40,0:09:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.56,0:09:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙也赞成 和秋人哥哥骑脖子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.83,0:09:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.56,0:09:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长你自己能够上去的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.51,0:09:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的假设只是咱俩交换位置来着的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.25,0:09:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 副会长
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.04,0:09:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑脖子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.36,0:09:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.97,0:09:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.54,0:09:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 哥哥的骑脖子到底是时隔多少年没有感受到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.90,0:09:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经没有什么遗憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.75,0:09:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也太夸张了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.98,0:09:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙太幸福了 已经不想从这里下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.38,0:09:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话还是有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.34,0:10:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会重很吗 秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.24,0:10:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不会啊 不如说是轻过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.34,0:10:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要多吃点才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.42,0:10:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我成长的太慢了的意思吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.61,0:10:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请…请快点下去 会长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.54,0:10:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不要这么见外嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.58,0:10:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也来吧 那须原同学
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.34,0:10:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咽口水…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.48,0:10:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.49,0:10:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要上了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.70,0:10:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么好像后脑勺有种特殊的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.90,0:10:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.08,0:11:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微慢点 会长
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.60,0:11:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人都去哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.88,0:11:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 能松手吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.63,0:11:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以不用那么客气的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.12,0:11:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.10,0:11:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊 那种程度就吓得乱跑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.50,0:11:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的有蛋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.51,0:11:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先开跑的人是会长吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.21,0:11:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有跑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.34,0:11:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.64,0:11:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干…干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.35,0:11:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为能就这么顺势推倒你的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.69,0:12:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是太扫兴了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.99,0:12:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.24,0:12:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是这边
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.28,0:12:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.40,0:12:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能再稍微隔开一点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.06,0:12:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.01,0:12:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 银兵卫姐姐 大家都不知去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.81,0:12:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 我们也快点回宿舍吧 亚里沙君
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.00,0:12:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的已经受不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.46,0:12:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银兵卫姐姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.88,0:12:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才十二岁 就和我有差不多的乳量
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.66,0:12:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.61,0:12:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.01,0:12:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.20,0:12:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先回宿舍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.30,0:12:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这边吧 不对 是那边呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.66,0:13:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这样走起来很累
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.96,0:13:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不介意的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.71,0:13:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很介意的说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.36,0:13:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 那须原同学 发生了什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.51,0:13:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚 感觉你的表情一直都很生硬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.45,0:13:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还发出了很怪的声音 难道是身体不舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.39,0:13:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路同学 我和平时一样是正常体温
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.40,0:13:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体重 体温 血压也都是非常健康的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.61,0:13:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的我有表情生硬的需要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.95,0:13:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…只是不知为何觉得是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.57,0:13:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为何
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.43,0:13:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说你没有任何根据就说我和平时不一样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.83,0:13:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我就觉得是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.85,0:13:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真服了你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.14,0:13:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是考试成绩不如我在学校里人气也不如我的你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.06,0:13:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是无法理解我这种等级比你高的存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.78,0:14:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又把以前的旧事拿出来说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.54,0:14:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且成绩和选美什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.47,0:14:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟我根本就什么差别吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.33,0:14:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.23,0:14:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是欺负干什么都比不上我的你也不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.90,0:14:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 我的人生目标又不是要赢那须原同学
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.28,0:14:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我人生目标全是只为了深爱的哥哥一人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.77,0:14:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能和哥哥结婚的话 我就能成为绝对的赢家
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.10,0:14:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满足的享受今后的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.19,0:14:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢 和有着血缘关系的哥哥结婚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.02,0:14:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能的话就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.83,0:14:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑了吧 你嘲笑我了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.33,0:14:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也就只有现在能这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.49,0:14:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天我要成为这个国家的首相
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.97,0:14:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,颁布一条有血缘关系的兄妹也能结婚的法律
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.91,0:14:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那时你想反悔也没用了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.03,0:14:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.03,0:14:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.83,0:14:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又这样把我当笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.23,0:14:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有把你当笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.50,0:15:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 从来没有把你当作笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.03,0:15:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六年前 从与你见面的第一天开始
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.25,0:15:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到现在一直
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.62,0:15:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉安娜学园小学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.74,0:15:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五年级的时候的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.35,0:15:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好 初次见面 我是姬小路…不对 有栖川
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.26,0:15:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有栖川秋子 因为各种事 转学到这里来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.50,0:15:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请大家从今天开始多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.44,0:15:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.10,0:15:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和人偶一样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.61,0:15:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那须原同学比谁更可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.81,0:15:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾想 这是何等…何等可爱的女孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.83,0:15:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像要被吸走一般乌黑的秀发
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.03,0:15:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那坚强 而又温柔的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.74,0:16:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.14,0:16:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白瓷般的脸颊上所透出的微微红晕
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.71,0:16:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彷佛像是散落在初雪上的红色花瓣一般
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.01,0:16:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.80,0:16:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那份美貌之下似乎隐约能看到一层阴影
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.97,0:16:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.36,0:16:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对她在意了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.85,0:16:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问 有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.13,0:16:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.17,0:16:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是看看你有没有长痘痘
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.43,0:16:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻时的痘痘还是早点治疗比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.71,0:16:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然会留下痕迹的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.70,0:16:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才盯着你的脸看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.34,0:16:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.44,0:16:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.44,0:16:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.69,0:16:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在自我介绍时说错了姓氏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.82,0:16:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么隐情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.75,0:16:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是很想要知道就是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.21,0:16:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 不想说就别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.18,0:16:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.54,0:16:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是什么要藏起来的事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.61,0:16:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 其实
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.13,0:17:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是 你说明了事情的原委
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.21,0:17:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双亲的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.63,0:17:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与哥哥分别被不同家庭收养的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.78,0:17:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 兄妹天各一方很寂寞呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.72,0:17:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 哥哥答应我了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.47,0:17:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天一定会再和我一起生活
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.30,0:17:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 那还真不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.64,0:17:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.51,0:17:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信哥哥的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.21,0:17:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决心要成为一个好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.18,0:17:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了与哥哥重逢的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.94,0:17:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会令他感到失望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.67,0:17:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 你很喜欢哥哥吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.54,0:17:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 最喜欢哥哥了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.97,0:17:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个时候的我还完全无法想象
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.58,0:17:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然对有血缘关系的亲哥哥的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.04,0:17:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是喜欢 而是爱情的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.04,0:17:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(366,438)\fs23}Like
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.04,0:17:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(486,438)\fs23}Love
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.07,0:17:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后的六年
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.29,0:17:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我同她之间在某种意义上是互为对手的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.75,0:17:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我只是很普通的想跟她搞好关系而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.61,0:18:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.53,0:18:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我颇为傲娇的性格也是个小问题啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.70,0:18:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于能跟哥哥一同生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.69,0:18:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真是可喜可贺
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.19,0:18:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是你一直念叨着的梦想呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.45,0:18:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是很好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.63,0:18:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.51,0:18:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.37,0:18:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的哥哥 是什么样的家伙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.04,0:18:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让你不顾血缘关系而如此迷恋的人物
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.81,0:18:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是个相当好的男人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.75,0:18:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说是不是啊 副会长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.82,0:18:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也有兴趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.71,0:18:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.92,0:18:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不关我的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.97,0:18:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.09,0:18:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然很感兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.11,0:18:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.36,0:18:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想趁早见见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.20,0:18:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.43,0:18:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把亲哥哥作为恋爱的对象什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.77,0:18:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是何方神圣才能如此吸引着她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.85,0:19:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.97,0:19:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边是小学部
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.19,0:19:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边是初中部
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.70,0:19:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那对面有图书馆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.06,0:19:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.14,0:19:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.37,0:19:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还不能全部记住呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.41,0:19:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.65,0:19:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥肯定很快就适应了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.13,0:19:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就能每天清晨与哥哥一起上学了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.60,0:19:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很期待
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.69,0:19:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我也很期待
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.48,0:19:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差不多该去学生会露个脸了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.16,0:19:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.91,0:19:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后我会自己随便逛逛的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.97,0:19:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起啊哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.40,0:19:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先走一步了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.21,0:19:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.14,0:19:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我送别的吻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.65,0:19:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会给你的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.02,0:19:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.49,0:19:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不 用常识想想啊 常识
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.81,0:19:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哒 哥哥这个吝啬鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.86,0:19:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后即使再怎么想亲我也晚了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.33,0:20:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.11,0:20:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大白天就对女性品头论足
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.92,0:20:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真有福气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.13,0:20:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.86,0:20:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.82,0:20:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚出浴没有换穿的衣服 真是悲哀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.41,0:20:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们结婚吧 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.61,0:20:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 结婚吧 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.09,0:20:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准你娶我了 谢恩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.40,0:20:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢主隆恩
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.57,0:20:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很开心哦 那须原同学
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.09,0:20:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.82,0:20:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵 秋人哥哥请跟我结婚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.96,0:20:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以啊 亚里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.35,0:20:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很乐意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.41,0:20:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 我会成为你的好媳妇的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.55,0:20:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 银兵卫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.19,0:20:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也觉得自己会成为你的好丈夫的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.02,0:20:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人君 会讨厌岁数比你大的老婆吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.50,0:20:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 怎么会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.37,0:21:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然欢迎之至了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.40,0:21:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后也请多多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.40,0:21:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是公事还是私事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.48,0:21:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来 大家一起迎接初夜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.36,0:21:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是铺好床铺
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.70,0:21:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖~乖~
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.12,0:21:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵 睡得真香啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.49,0:21:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摇篮曲儿

Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.22,0:21:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖啦乖啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.01,0:21:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 这里开着个洞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.70,0:21:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进到里面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.66,0:21:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都吃饱嗳气了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.96,0:21:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么认真地在吸着
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.01,0:21:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟昨晚的爸爸一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.88,0:21:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请别这样啦会长
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 你想称呼我会长到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.53,0:21:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.47,0:21:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前的习惯总是改不了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.39,0:21:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.20,0:21:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.54,0:21:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子 亚里沙 银 安娜 薰子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.44,0:21:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是世界上最幸福的男人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.18,0:21:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.32,0:21:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来玩啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.83,0:22:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.05,0:22:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是长大了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.77,0:22:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟他爸爸长得一模一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.21,0:22:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.21,0:22:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.26,0:22:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要尿尿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.38,0:22:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要小便吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.50,0:22:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮到爸爸出场了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.96,0:22:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.72,0:22:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先把…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.34,0:22:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 快饶了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.43,0:22:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是梦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.96,0:22:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊还在发烧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.86,0:22:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且差不多该要工作了

Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.38,0:24:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,季节
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.07,0:24:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交替
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.60,0:24:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.08,0:24:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告别
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.60,0:24:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.01,0:24:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相见之日
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.52,0:24:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屈指
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.96,0:24:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可数
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.47,0:24:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂且
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.98,0:24:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.45,0:24:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.87,0:24:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.36,0:24:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泪水
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.83,0:24:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.23,0:24:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.69,0:24:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑起来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.10,0:24:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.62,0:24:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会更好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.12,0:24:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄控
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.58,0:24:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.02,0:24:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.54,0:24:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.05,0:24:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.51,0:24:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咕嘿嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.97,0:24:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.53,0:24:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.01,0:24:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄爱
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.46,0:24:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十二集
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.92,0:24:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.49,0:24:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢了


