[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Audio File: C:\Users\ikakun\Desktop\[DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][01][x264_aac].mkv

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.93,0:21:59.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由动漫国字幕组和轻之国度字幕组联合制作\N仅供试看,请支持购买正版音像制品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:02.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻译:栗花落&枪叔&Cosmo  校对:娜娜莉  时间:Rodax  后期:sora  MKV:乌贼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.12,0:00:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天貌似神祭不搞了 真不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.91,0:00:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下站是目城 下站是目城
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.06,0:00:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要下车的旅客请准备好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.10,0:00:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.90,0:01:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.02,0:02:01.33,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南目城 派出所
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.67,0:02:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这儿呐 爬那个阶梯一直往上走就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.93,0:02:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.96,0:02:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘了这个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.37,0:02:12.26,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新宿区 织姬山公园
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.06,0:02:40.29,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2}圣莉莉安娜学园学生宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.67,0:03:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.44,0:03:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个 很久…很久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.59,0:03:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比预定到的要早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.80,0:03:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在想差不多该去车站接你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.37,0:03:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是的 那个是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.70,0:03:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我决心提前两小时动身的说…那个
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.94,0:03:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是很了不起的决心 不过有点太急了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.11,0:03:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 很抱歉 下次的话只提早十分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.40,0:03:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那样更好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.52,0:03:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的行李已经搬来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.68,0:03:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说还在打扫中 总之先进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.09,0:03:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.62,0:03:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不该是「打扰了」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.09,0:03:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.52,0:04:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我回来了 哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.80,0:04:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦 很合适哥哥你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.95,0:04:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.77,0:04:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟已经六年没在一起的哥哥一起生活
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.32,0:04:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还特地转学来我所就读的学校
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.91,0:04:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥你能稍微拉一拉我的脸颊吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.90,0:04:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要啊 因为这一切不是幻想而是现实哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.38,0:04:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然过程相当辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.15,0:04:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是从今往后 就让我们两人一起生活吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.71,0:05:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 小女子不才请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.64,0:05:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里才是 请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.15,0:05:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 今天整理行李和打扫很累了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.37,0:05:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先去洗澡 早些睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.21,0:05:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗 洗澡！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.87,0:05:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你先进去洗也可以哦 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.97,0:05:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.35,0:05:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 那我就先进去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.33,0:05:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？那么等会儿见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.39,0:06:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好慢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.41,0:06:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 这到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.84,0:06:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.77,0:06:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 总之先穿衣服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.76,0:06:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要转移对话 我在问这是怎么一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.72,0:06:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 真抱歉 我做错了啥…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.83,0:06:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明我入浴了 你为何不来偷窥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.82,0:06:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 你能再说一遍吗 我貌似听错了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.52,0:06:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明我入浴了 你为何不来偷窥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.03,0:06:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有和我一起入浴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.69,0:07:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是打算等我入浴了之后再来偷窥的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.12,0:07:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我没有半点那种打算…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.81,0:07:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.80,0:07:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 这纯洁无暇又光滑的皮肤 很漂亮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.93,0:07:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 确实很漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.76,0:07:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样啊 这可是我引以为豪的肌肤哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.80,0:07:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说偷窥 不如说该速推才是王道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.02,0:07:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不 不会不会
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.81,0:07:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.16,0:07:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说为啥 因为我们是亲兄妹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.58,0:07:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄妹之前 我们只是男人和女人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.24,0:07:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是搞反了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.66,0:07:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在男女关系之前 我们可是兄妹哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.89,0:07:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我就再给你次机会
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.04,0:07:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机会？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.96,0:07:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子现在要再入浴一次
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.15,0:07:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后的不用我说 你懂的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.69,0:07:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别胡说了 偷窥自己妹妹入浴那种变态的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.58,0:07:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 在你偷窥之前我会一直待在浴室的 你明白了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.95,0:08:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七千一百三十七
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.05,0:08:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七千一百三十八
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.30,0:08:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七千一百三十九
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.55,0:08:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好过分 真是太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.53,0:08:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然真的不来偷窥什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.36,0:08:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子真的要生气了 抽泣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.78,0:08:20.79,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs23}do re mi运输公司
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.03,0:08:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是全部了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.56,0:08:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别还那么不开心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.25,0:08:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就拿出点诚意来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.39,0:08:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说诚意是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.43,0:08:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚请和我一起睡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.89,0:08:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子 以前确实我们总是一起睡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.40,0:08:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在你和我都已经十六岁了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.37,0:08:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不是还能一起睡的年龄了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.29,0:08:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.22,0:08:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分了解了 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.05,0:08:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理解我的意思了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.26,0:08:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.05,0:08:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今天开始就又能和哥哥住在同一个屋檐下了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.78,0:08:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子我想尽可能地听哥哥的话做一个乖孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.57,0:08:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以和哥哥一起睡的想法我放弃了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.36,0:09:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 想尽可能地满足你的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.47,0:09:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但只是这个稍微有些…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.33,0:09:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了这句话就已经足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.36,0:09:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时隔六年不见的哥哥还是一样温柔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.71,0:09:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子好高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.92,0:09:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 哥哥也变得大胆起来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.11,0:09:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.09,0:09:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和哥哥相比 我还只是个小孩子而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.79,0:09:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是我的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.21,0:09:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初夜居然不是在被子里 而是在外面什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.88,0:09:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很害羞 不过我会加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.63,0:09:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然外面很冷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.40,0:09:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过没关系 很快就会变得热起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.75,0:09:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等等 你在说些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.04,0:09:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初夜是指的什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.62,0:09:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相爱的男女迎来的第一个夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.60,0:09:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道你是哪里搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.24,0:09:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是要一个人睡的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.98,0:09:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是骗人的吧 这是开玩笑的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.65,0:09:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可是时隔六年不见了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.37,0:09:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是时隔六十年我的回答也是一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.51,0:09:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们是亲兄妹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.90,0:10:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好过分 都让我一直期待到这个份上了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.63,0:10:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子明明都已经这么兴奋了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.99,0:10:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明不管是内心还是身体都已经做好准备了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.01,0:10:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.24,0:10:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 我准备睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.01,0:10:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个人在我的房间里睡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.30,0:10:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 肯定是我哪里搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.35,0:10:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是太久没有和哥哥见面 所以太激动了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.38,0:10:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.57,0:10:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种话我不会再说了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.17,0:10:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今以后我会像姬小路家的孩子该有的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.52,0:10:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谨慎言行地生活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.44,0:10:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯 不错的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.04,0:10:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有那么夸张啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.70,0:10:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 真心话是？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.80,0:10:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果哥哥无论如何也不肯坦率地面对我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.76,0:10:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就等到夜深人静的时候去夜袭…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.64,0:10:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为兄控是种个性
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.06,0:11:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Brother complex 那是只有血亲之间才被允许的难得的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.22,0:11:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥首先必须要对那份重要性有所认识
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.54,0:11:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真美味啊 这个味噌汤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.12,0:11:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 这是专门为哥哥所做的自信之作
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.24,0:11:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不够还能添哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.10,0:11:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就再来一碗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.81,0:11:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.47,0:11:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.92,0:11:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多吃一点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.08,0:11:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么接着 兄控指的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.49,0:11:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个泡菜也很美味呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.81,0:11:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哇
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.56,0:11:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个也是专门为了哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.54,0:11:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而在很早之前就准备好的腌制的酱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.83,0:11:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合你口味吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.90,0:11:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学会做饭了呢 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.20,0:11:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力地学习过了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.23,0:11:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 兄控指的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.19,0:11:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真亮啊 这灯 果然还是新的好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.32,0:11:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从刚才开始就完全没有想听我说话的意思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.15,0:11:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是非常重要的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.01,0:11:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 确实那也是不能就这么放着不管啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.45,0:11:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来将要一起生活的妹妹的性癖
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.76,0:11:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性癖什么的请不要这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.58,0:11:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个性 个性
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.93,0:11:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子的个性
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.93,0:11:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(470,432)\fs23}identity
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.02,0:11:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底 你是想说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.27,0:11:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早做了非常可口的早餐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.17,0:11:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是作为奖赏请抱我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.03,0:12:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脑袋里到底变成什么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.47,0:12:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥真的变得担心起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.11,0:12:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 秋子有些得意忘形了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.01,0:12:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道就好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.54,0:12:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱抱就算了 亲我一下就足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.61,0:12:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难度不是越来越高了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.04,0:12:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是抱我一下就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.32,0:12:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你指的不是单纯的抱抱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.39,0:12:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是男女之间的那种关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.43,0:12:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 我只要能从哥哥那里得到奖赏就满足了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.92,0:12:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么就是不明白呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.57,0:12:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还想发飙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.27,0:12:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只要能和哥哥卿卿我我就满足了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.88,0:12:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来哥哥还没有察觉到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.28,0:12:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是继续这种没营养的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.38,0:12:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就已经算是进入了卿卿我我的范围里了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.45,0:12:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果现在的场景被谁看到的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.94,0:12:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人肯定会这样想的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.73,0:12:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这俩人还真相亲相爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.45,0:12:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连已经陷入了我的圈套里都没有发现
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.49,0:12:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还摆着一副平和的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.32,0:13:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥还真是个可爱的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.91,0:13:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味噌汤再来一碗 超级美味的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.55,0:13:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！再多吃点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.11,0:13:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好天气呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.47,0:13:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是这时候哥哥能给我来一个膝枕的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.17,0:13:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可就真是无话可说了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.60,0:13:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话先说在前面 我不会干的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.14,0:13:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是哥哥能给我来一个膝枕的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.70,0:13:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就死而无憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.58,0:13:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下子就变得这么忧郁了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.56,0:13:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是已经建了七十年的房子了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.13,0:13:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屋檐的修理 墙壁的修补
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.43,0:13:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须做的事还有很多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.91,0:13:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么破真对不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.09,0:13:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子只要能和哥哥在一起的话无论哪里都…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.65,0:13:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是洞窟也好桥下也好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.06,0:13:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢啦 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.93,0:13:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该说谢谢的应该是我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.29,0:13:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我从有栖川家接过来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.14,0:13:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忧郁的话到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.03,0:13:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 来继续收拾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.60,0:14:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗衣服能拜托秋子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.41,0:14:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.59,0:14:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.56,0:14:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢哥哥了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.64,0:14:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也最喜欢秋子了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.97,0:14:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 秋子 没事吧 振作一点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.93,0:14:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32}脸好红 难道是发烧了吗 你没事吧 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.60,0:14:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和哥哥的两人独处的平凡生活
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.07,0:14:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子是幸福的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.78,0:14:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的仿佛在梦里一般
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.21,0:14:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦里一般
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.28,0:14:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本应该是和哥哥过着两人独处的平凡生活
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.26,0:15:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.20,0:15:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.70,0:15:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是哥哥 只要有爱的就没关系了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.49,0:15:22.71,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2}圣莉莉安娜学园

Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.35,0:15:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是得要肉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.00,0:15:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牛肉火锅什么的怎样

Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.98,0:15:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要吃龙虾

Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.20,0:15:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没有那么多预算啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.93,0:15:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能再提出些现实点的提案

Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.16,0:15:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话就只有饭团了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.78,0:15:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有盐和米饭的话总能有办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.91,0:15:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学生会书记代理副助理
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.48,0:15:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话我也就用小龙虾勉为其难地忍一忍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.72,0:16:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 你觉得什么好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.91,0:16:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是稍微普通点的建议就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.50,0:16:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得也是啊 鱼料理之类的怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.31,0:16:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.34,0:16:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天商店街的鱼类在搞促销呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.85,0:16:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是秋人 着眼点不错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.23,0:16:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那就这么定了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.70,0:16:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么今天的会议就到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.25,0:16:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.41,0:16:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦 姬小路秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.16,0:16:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱的脸蛋都糟蹋了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.62,0:16:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事也没有

Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.68,0:16:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的学生会也真累人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.54,0:16:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还真不可思议
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.83,0:16:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没看出学生会长像是干过什么工作的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.18,0:16:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干活的只有我们几个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.33,0:16:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.36,0:16:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关心鸡毛蒜皮的事的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.89,0:16:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是成不了我这样的好女人的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.22,0:16:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.56,0:16:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 能不能稍微分担一点呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.80,0:16:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.72,0:17:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算让手无缚鸡之力的弱女子拿沉重的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.43,0:17:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手无缚鸡之力…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.65,0:17:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作点儿啊 秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.71,0:17:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是这种时刻才轮到男人的出场不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.06,0:17:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是这么说啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.65,0:17:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没拿过比筷子更重的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.83,0:17:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是拿着包吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.10,0:17:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.40,0:17:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.25,0:17:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.16,0:17:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话秋人也会高兴的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.04,0:17:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.63,0:18:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么需要帮忙的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.69,0:18:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饭菜几乎都做完了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.48,0:18:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的就是摆放盘子了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.27,0:18:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.40,0:18:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.60,0:18:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.00,0:18:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 开饭了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.14,0:18:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去很好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.45,0:18:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了你下功夫做的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.23,0:18:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合你口味就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.26,0:18:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就趁热…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.23,0:18:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.82,0:18:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开动之前 有一个必须要决定的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.52,0:18:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要决定的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.24,0:18:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.43,0:18:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚要坐在谁的旁边
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.98,0:18:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁能喂食他那贪得无厌的嘴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.81,0:18:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.07,0:18:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那确实是个重要的问题呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.69,0:18:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.89,0:19:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想自己吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.97,0:19:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个贪得无厌的嘴 有什么不愿意的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.30,0:19:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那须原同学 那个啥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.93,0:19:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.59,0:19:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能称呼我为「安娜」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.00,0:19:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我说几遍你那不开窍的脑袋才能理解呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.79,0:19:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 安娜同学 那个啥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.24,0:19:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然用「穴」来称呼女人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.78,0:19:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也真是了不得的男人呐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.65,0:19:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能请你别用这种语言套圈子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.19,0:19:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处男就给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.56,0:19:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.97,0:19:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该是处男才对呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.59,0:19:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请别说这么失礼的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.69,0:19:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.74,0:19:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥是名副其实的处男
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.92,0:19:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且会以纯洁无暇的样子成为秋子的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.31,0:19:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.92,0:19:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要不要现在就让你从处男毕业呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.56,0:19:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.34,0:19:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为我的情人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.02,0:19:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚就能毕业哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.82,0:19:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥是不会成为学生会长的情人的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.70,0:19:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥是我的…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.81,0:19:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处女也给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.98,0:19:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.68,0:20:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便一提我也是处女 所以我闭嘴了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.91,0:20:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不需要你的这个情报呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.48,0:20:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.83,0:20:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四个人都来做我的对手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.71,0:20:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是秋人要坐在谁身旁的话题呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.12,0:20:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来会有这种争论本身就不正常了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.91,0:20:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥当然是我的东西啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.87,0:20:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.72,0:20:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 不 书记代理副助理请闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.59,0:20:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最为合适的当然是我了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.94,0:20:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能解说这个饭菜的只有我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.54,0:20:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好解说的话 能让饭菜变得更为美味
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.07,0:20:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坐在秋人身边是必然的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.08,0:20:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我才比较合适呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.20,0:20:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让今天的饭菜能更好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.17,0:20:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在祈祷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.30,0:20:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊 要是这么说的话我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.28,0:20:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无谓的话就到此为止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.04,0:20:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不能允许你们打扰我跟哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.65,0:20:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然微小但幸福的生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.05,0:20:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从一生下来 哥哥就是我的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.46,0:20:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就截止预定 不 截止发售了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.94,0:21:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在才说那种事情也没有用…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.02,0:21:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.03,0:21:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.05,0:21:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.28,0:21:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是姬小路秋人的亲妹妹吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.80,0:21:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会让话题变复杂的 请闪一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.27,0:21:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不分清楚立场的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.08,0:21:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.51,0:21:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能坐在身旁喂他的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.26,0:21:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和哥哥的爱是千真万确的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.03,0:21:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在真爱面前禁忌是毫无意义的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.25,0:21:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 就问问你哥哥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.87,0:21:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样最为省事了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.69,0:21:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥…哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.39,0:21:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子 你是个好孩子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.45,0:21:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.75,0:21:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时我都会珍惜你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.90,0:21:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥…哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.87,0:21:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.64,0:22:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你幸福就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.68,0:22:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俩人多般配啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.67,0:22:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然仅仅是作为妹妹哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.23,0:22:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.61,0:22:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.24,0:22:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.95,0:22:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有爱就没问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.30,0:24:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.80,0:24:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翘首以盼的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.26,0:24:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依偎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.77,0:24:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.13,0:24:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.39,0:24:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.64,0:24:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.09,0:24:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碍事的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.35,0:24:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会插足进来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.79,0:24:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.13,0:24:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安静
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.64,0:24:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲吻
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.88,0:24:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥抱
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.19,0:24:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是私通
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.75,0:24:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是偷窥
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.16,0:24:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.45,0:24:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都有机会
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.82,0:24:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼前的肉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.16,0:24:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.50,0:24:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.91,0:24:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.45,0:24:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这回的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.85,0:24:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,般配
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.10,0:24:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二集
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.47,0:24:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.91,0:24:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教




