[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.0.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Collisions: Normal
Scroll Position: 6
Active Line: 13
Video Zoom Percent: 1
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 360
Video File: Y:\LK\ss\kami02.avs
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Position: 40435
Last Style Storage: Default
Audio URI: Y:\LK\ss\04.aac
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: 注释,方正隶变_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00793E9C,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,7,10,10,10,1
Style: opjp,ＦＡ ポップＢ,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H008C3EC4,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.5,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: staff,黑体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00DA54FD,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正少儿_MOD v2,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H008C3EC4,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,2,0,3,10,10,10,1
Style: title2,方正少儿_GBK,23,&H009440CE,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: title1,方正少儿_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H008E49D2,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 人物介绍,华康少女文字 - Kelvin,14,&H00352762,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.72,0:22:08.64,opjp,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.72,0:22:08.64,opcn,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.64,0:22:11.37,opjp,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! 弾み続けろ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.64,0:22:11.37,opcn,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! 繼續彈跳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.37,0:22:13.91,opjp,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.37,0:22:13.91,opcn,,0,0,0,,Rolling Rolling Growing!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.07,0:22:16.80,opjp,,0,0,0,,小学生は最高だぜっ！イェイ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.07,0:22:16.80,opcn,,0,0,0,,小學生最棒了！ YEAH!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.84,0:22:25.74,opjp,,0,0,0,,カラダもココロもSSだけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.84,0:22:25.74,opcn,,0,0,0,,只要身心都是SS
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.30,0:22:29.18,opjp,,0,0,0,,夢はLLだって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.29,0:22:29.18,opcn,,0,0,0,,就算夢想是LL
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.18,0:22:31.64,opjp,,0,0,0,,いいじゃん いいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.18,0:22:31.64,opcn,,0,0,0,,也没關係嘛 没關係嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.75,0:22:36.58,opjp,,0,0,0,,青春未満のお悩みいっぱい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.75,0:22:36.58,opcn,,0,0,0,,有著許多算不上青春的煩惱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.34,0:22:39.62,opjp,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.34,0:22:39.62,opcn,,0,0,0,,因为不是孤獨一人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.08,0:22:42.10,opjp,,0,0,0,,乗り越えられるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.08,0:22:42.10,opcn,,0,0,0,,所以能够解决
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.84,0:22:47.77,opjp,,0,0,0,,もっと(もっと)うまく(うまく)なりたいな!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.84,0:22:47.77,opcn,,0,0,0,,想變得更加（更加）厲害（厲害）！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.36,0:22:55.64,opjp,,0,0,0,,あなたの　(おぉ...)　　驚く　(スゴイ！)  顔が見たいの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.36,0:22:55.64,opcn,,0,0,0,,想要看到你(嗯。。。)驚訝（好厉害！）的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.03,0:22:58.86,opjp,,0,0,0,,回せ　回せ　回せ　回せ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.03,0:22:58.86,opcn,,0,0,0,,旋轉吧 旋轉吧 旋轉吧 旋轉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.86,0:23:02.32,opjp,,0,0,0,,地球はおっきなバスケットボール
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.86,0:23:02.32,opcn,,0,0,0,,地球就像個巨大的籃球
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.78,0:23:07.08,opjp,,0,0,0,,明日を信じていくよ!(ハイ！い・く・よ)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.78,0:23:07.08,opcn,,0,0,0,,相信著明天前進！（好嘞！走·吧）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.08,0:23:09.80,opjp,,0,0,0,,回せ 回せ 回せ 回せ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.08,0:23:09.80,opcn,,0,0,0,,旋轉吧 旋轉吧 旋轉吧 旋轉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.80,0:23:13.36,opjp,,0,0,0,,宇宙は大きな、バスケットコート
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.80,0:23:13.36,opcn,,0,0,0,,宇宙就像一個巨大的籃球場
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.69,0:23:17.13,opjp,,0,0,0,,あなたに届けたいな...(せーのっ)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.69,0:23:17.13,opcn,,0,0,0,,好想傳給你啊（1、2）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.13,0:23:21.53,opjp,,0,0,0,,パス!パス!パス!　受け止めてください!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.13,0:23:21.53,opcn,,0,0,0,,Pass！Pass！Pass！ 請接好哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.60,0:23:25.42,opjp,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.60,0:23:25.42,opcn,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.42,0:23:28.14,opjp,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! 弾み続けろ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.42,0:23:28.14,opcn,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! 繼續彈跳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.14,0:23:30.64,opjp,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.14,0:23:30.64,opcn,,0,0,0,,Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.82,0:23:33.86,opjp,,0,0,0,,小学生は最高だぜっ!イェイ!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.82,0:23:33.86,opcn,,0,0,0,,小學生最棒了！ YEAH!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.86,0:23:35.86,opcn,,0,0,0,,
