[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.0.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
Collisions: Normal
Last Style Storage: Default
Video Zoom Percent: 0.875
Scroll Position: 0
Active Line: 0
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 360
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Position: 3859
Audio URI: Y:\LK\ss\04.aac
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
Video File: Y:\LK\ss\kami02.avs
Video Zoom: 6

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: 注释,方正隶变_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00793E9C,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,7,10,10,10,1
Style: opjp,ＦＡ ポップＢ,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H008C3EC4,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.5,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: staff,黑体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00DA54FD,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正少儿_MOD v2,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H008C3EC4,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,2,0,3,10,10,10,1
Style: title2,方正少儿_GBK,23,&H009440CE,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: title1,方正少儿_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H008E49D2,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 人物介绍,华康少女文字 - Kelvin,14,&H00352762,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.55,0:00:40.64,opjp,,0,0,0,,起こせ！Big Halation
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.55,0:00:40.64,opcn,,0,0,0,,站起來吧！Big Halation
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.64,0:00:43.85,opjp,,0,0,0,,あの日の誓いを果たすため
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.64,0:00:43.85,opcn,,0,0,0,,为了實現那天所立下的誓言
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.98,0:00:47.02,opjp,,0,0,0,,開け！New Formation
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.98,0:00:47.02,opcn,,0,0,0,,展開吧！New Formation
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.02,0:00:50.57,opjp,,0,0,0,,視線の合図呼び合う
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.02,0:00:50.57,opcn,,0,0,0,,我們眼神交匯心有靈犀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.65,0:00:56.78,opjp,,0,0,0,,希望を載せて　放てArch
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.65,0:00:56.78,opcn,,0,0,0,,把希望附在手心 去吧Arch
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.20,0:01:00.03,opjp,,0,0,0,,いつもの通りね
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.20,0:01:00.03,opcn,,0,0,0,,我們一如往常
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.03,0:01:03.50,opjp,,0,0,0,,信じてる（任せて）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.03,0:01:03.50,opcn,,0,0,0,,相信著彼此（交給我了）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.54,0:01:06.62,opjp,,0,0,0,,胸に手を開けて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.54,0:01:06.62,opcn,,0,0,0,,手心貼著胸前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.75,0:01:09.92,opjp,,0,0,0,,引き寄せた平常心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.75,0:01:09.92,opcn,,0,0,0,,彼此信任的平常心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.25,0:01:13.13,opjp,,0,0,0,,叶えてきたこと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.25,0:01:13.13,opcn,,0,0,0,,我們成功的經歷
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.13,0:01:16.34,opjp,,0,0,0,,それぞれが覚えてる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.13,0:01:16.34,opcn,,0,0,0,,我們不曾忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.34,0:01:22.22,opjp,,0,0,0,,あの日秘かに泣いたことも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.34,0:01:22.22,opcn,,0,0,0,,那天偷偷流淚的事也是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.47,0:01:29.36,opjp,,0,0,0,,同じ夢見てるのはわたしたちだけじゃないんだよね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.47,0:01:29.36,opcn,,0,0,0,,擁有一個夢的不只是我們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.36,0:01:37.49,opjp,,0,0,0,,目の前に  現れた揺るがない瞳　火花散らして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.36,0:01:37.49,opcn,,0,0,0,,與眼前出現的這堅定的眼神對視 擦出火花
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.99,0:01:40.87,opjp,,0,0,0,,起こせ！Big Halation
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.99,0:01:40.87,opcn,,0,0,0,,站起來吧！Big Halation
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.87,0:01:44.29,opjp,,0,0,0,,開くスペースへ走り込め
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.87,0:01:44.29,opcn,,0,0,0,,朝著那空擋奔跑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.37,0:01:47.42,opjp,,0,0,0,,僅かなSensation
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.37,0:01:47.42,opcn,,0,0,0,,靠著那一點點的直覺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.42,0:01:50.96,opjp,,0,0,0,,背伸びしていた昨日へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.42,0:01:50.96,opcn,,0,0,0,,要是向著昨天還在逞強的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.00,0:01:54.21,opjp,,0,0,0,,別れを告げたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.00,0:01:54.21,opcn,,0,0,0,,道别的話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.30,0:01:57.51,opjp,,0,0,0,,笑顔を繋げて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.30,0:01:57.51,opcn,,0,0,0,,保持著微笑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.59,0:02:03.56,opjp,,0,0,0,,夢見た場所へ 放てArch
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.59,0:02:03.56,opcn,,0,0,0,,向著那憧憬的地方 去吧Arch
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.56,0:02:05.56,opcn,,0,0,0,,
