[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.9
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 360
Audio File: ?video
Video File: [HorribleSubs] SoniAni - SUPER SONICO THE ANIMATION - 06 [1080p].mkv
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 3
Video Position: 32928
Audio URI: [HorribleSubs] SoniAni - SUPER SONICO THE ANIMATION - 06 [1080p] - [2] .aac
Scroll Position: 0
Active Line: 0
Video Zoom Percent: 0.375
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00424242,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.8,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: title,方正稚艺_GBK,23,&H0041070F,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFMaruMoji-W9,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00676767,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.8,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正少儿_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00696969,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.8,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: EDJP,DFMaruMoji-W9,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H006C6C6C,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.8,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正少儿_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00696969,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.8,0,7,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.15,0:00:02.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}{\an8\fscx80\fscy80}譯制：大佐爬床去玩秋葉原脫衣魔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.09,0:00:03.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家 晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.79,0:00:06.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天我也十分的健康
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.12,0:00:09.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大學的前期測試也順利結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.91,0:00:13.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓人期待的暑假就在眼前了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.16,0:00:21.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣真的好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.50,0:00:24.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有點小
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.39,0:00:26.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,風璃 很可愛哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.52,0:00:29.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是被我選中的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.01,0:00:34.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它將風璃的魅力毫無保留地表現了出來
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.65,0:00:36.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就不說具體什麼魅力了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.64,0:00:40.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 就輪到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.72,0:00:44.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴真是大膽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.87,0:00:48.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夏天會讓女孩變得大膽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.23,0:00:51.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是夏天讓女孩變成那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.81,0:00:53.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還是女孩對夏天所起的反應
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.45,0:00:56.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是個很難講的問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.10,0:00:59.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 真有哲理
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.60,0:01:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.44,0:01:04.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最後是我們的尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.45,0:01:08.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 真是件可愛的連衣泳裝呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.24,0:01:13.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴看中的我還以為會是件奔放的泳裝呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.14,0:01:15.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.04,0:01:19.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會那樣想就是外行人的膚淺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.91,0:01:23.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼子的身材很好 藏起來才剛好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.04,0:01:28.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的性感隱藏在背後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.70,0:01:32.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正所謂藏頭露尾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.34,0:01:33.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.46,0:01:36.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一眼看去是可愛又清純的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.53,0:01:40.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其背後卻隱藏著妖艷女人的本性
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.36,0:01:41.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼一種理念
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.84,0:01:44.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 那個理念很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.84,0:01:46.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是氣質啦 氣質
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.94,0:01:51.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 明天可不只是去海邊玩而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.79,0:01:53.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同時也是「第一宇宙速度」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.47,0:01:56.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一次定期演唱會的宣傳活動
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.75,0:02:00.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有必要讓盡量更多的客人關注才行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.00,0:02:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為此這可是十分有必要的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.34,0:02:04.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但…但是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.93,0:02:09.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 你還繼續說的話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.56,0:02:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴她讓你穿上更難為情泳裝的可能性…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.78,0:02:23.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會穿這個泳裝努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.81,0:02:27.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 明天要在海邊大鬧一場哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.98,0:02:37.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前 讓天氣先大鬧了一場
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.14,0:04:24.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要一塗就能讓你體裡的脂肪燃燒殆盡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.82,0:04:28.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在意的地方塗上一點
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.85,0:04:30.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是終極減肥方法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.64,0:04:33.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脂肪堂的脂肪燃燒油
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.70,0:04:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給予所有女性無上的美
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.56,0:04:42.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個就是下個月要開播的廣告嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.11,0:04:45.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 謳歌
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.55,0:04:49.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然能接到在全國放送廣告的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.64,0:04:51.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.39,0:04:56.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回想起來一直以來都是在街頭當接待
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.12,0:04:57.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,促銷傳單的模特兒之類不起眼的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.27,0:05:03.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,時而甚至想要把經紀人滅掉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.94,0:05:07.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過 辛苦了這麼久終於有了回報
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.44,0:05:11.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌的時代終於到來了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.58,0:05:16.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜 真是太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.71,0:05:19.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌 真是太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.25,0:05:22.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要簽名的話就趁現在
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.33,0:05:27.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 這種大工作竟然會找我們這呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.60,0:05:31.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其實在街上我就有被問過要不要去拍廣告了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.14,0:05:34.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是說在全國放送的廣告的出演人物
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.03,0:05:36.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,靠街頭的尋找就決定了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.40,0:05:40.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說謳歌有如此的魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.62,0:05:41.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.24,0:05:43.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.38,0:05:45.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對了 索尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.84,0:05:50.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,後天謳歌會在脂肪燃燒油的體驗發表會出場
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.32,0:05:52.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的話要不要來看看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.26,0:05:56.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把朋友帶過來也沒有關係哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.06,0:05:58.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.35,0:06:01.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有問題 謳歌可是VIP待遇
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.14,0:06:04.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且發表會的地點…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.69,0:06:07.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是超豪華客輪哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.35,0:06:15.23,title,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\pos(248,81)\b1\c&H0600BA&}亡者的游輪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.56,0:06:12.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然… 請…請務必讓我去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.84,0:06:19.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.36,0:06:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能坐那種船的人果然只有名流呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.81,0:06:26.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且是讓人感覺理所當然的那種
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.11,0:06:33.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好寬敞
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.75,0:06:35.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好整齊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.72,0:06:38.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好豪華
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.78,0:06:42.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到了嗎 裡面還有溫泉和電影館哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.80,0:06:44.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有網球場和賭場
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.36,0:06:48.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大型餐廳和壽司店
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.11,0:06:52.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真期待能品嘗到什麼樣的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.16,0:06:56.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這世間如此的不公平
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.20,0:06:59.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是…這就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.84,0:07:03.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所謂的名流生活對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.49,0:07:55.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}燃燒脂肪油體驗發表會
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.49,0:07:55.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}主辦方 脂肪堂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.78,0:08:00.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇 大家都打扮得好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.30,0:08:04.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得我們幾個跟這裡很不相配
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.65,0:08:08.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.42,0:08:09.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我才該說抱歉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.32,0:08:14.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓各位久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.63,0:08:18.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始脂肪堂的新產品
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.47,0:08:22.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,燃燒脂肪油的體驗發表會
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.83,0:08:27.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,首先有請脂肪堂的CEO 上場寺株子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.72,0:08:32.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及出演廣告的 殺戮院謳歌
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.97,0:08:37.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌 好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.39,0:08:46.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛也已經介紹過 我是脂肪堂的CEO 上場寺株子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.95,0:08:49.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,客套話我就不多說了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.70,0:08:53.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始介紹本公司劃時代新產品
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.06,0:08:56.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使用方法非常簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.86,0:08:59.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只需像這樣 塗在想要瘦下來的地方即可
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.70,0:09:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這麼簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.71,0:09:04.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.66,0:09:07.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是一個月前的上場寺
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.33,0:09:10.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而現在在大家面前的就是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.92,0:09:14.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使用了燃燒脂肪油一個月之後的上場寺
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.54,0:09:18.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而站在這裡的謳歌 也是受益於燃燒脂肪油
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.91,0:09:23.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才能夠擁有這麼苗條的身材的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.13,0:09:25.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你說是吧 謳歌
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.46,0:09:29.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 全都是燃燒脂肪油的功勞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.80,0:09:34.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然謳歌本來就很苗條的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.57,0:09:38.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,燃燒脂肪油有多種類型
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.35,0:09:40.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,敬請各位回房後隨意嘗試
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.30,0:09:44.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果不介意的話 各位船員也請試用一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.86,0:09:49.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脂肪燃燒油在使用6小時後開始見效
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.73,0:09:55.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我期待著明天在這裡與變美了的大家再會
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.94,0:10:00.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 那個女社長
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.90,0:10:02.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可疑的要死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.88,0:10:06.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 難得我們能夠被招待到這裡來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.01,0:10:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可不能說這種話哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.52,0:10:11.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}用法·用量說明：
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.52,0:10:11.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}每天一次 取適量於手心進行塗抹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.52,0:10:11.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}使用6小時後開始見效
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.52,0:10:11.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}持續時間3小時
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.52,0:10:11.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}請注意閱讀說明 避免陽光直射
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.52,0:10:11.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}請保存於陰冷處
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.80,0:10:14.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使用6小時候開始見效 持續時間3小時嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.32,0:10:19.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妮子 你該不會是想塗這東西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.59,0:10:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…我也有不少介意的部位嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.44,0:10:27.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我勸你還是別塗了 這東西好可疑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.02,0:10:31.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 妮子還是這樣子最有魅力了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.52,0:10:33.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是…是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.00,0:10:35.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.30,0:10:41.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快到晚飯時間了 再不去的話就沒得吃啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.03,0:10:42.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那不可能的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.61,0:10:48.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即便是社長您 以一己之見拍了廣告
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.16,0:10:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還舉辦體驗發表會
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.54,0:10:53.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脂肪燃燒油依然處於試作階段
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.53,0:10:55.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,應該再多做些臨床試驗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.52,0:10:57.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,確保使用安全之後才能…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.03,0:10:58.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.83,0:11:02.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我這身體不就證明了其效果了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.31,0:11:04.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,效果也是有個人差異的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.73,0:11:06.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,某些情況下或許會帶來副作用
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.93,0:11:08.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,計劃還是會繼續進行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.11,0:11:10.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可是把全公司的資金
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.54,0:11:12.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全都投進到脂肪燃燒油裡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.32,0:11:15.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今已經沒有回頭路可走了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.66,0:11:16.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.30,0:11:20.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是愛操心啊 沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.17,0:11:23.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你所發明的脂肪燃燒油
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.59,0:11:26.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它是實現了所有女性
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.82,0:11:30.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望變瘦的願望的夢幻產品
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.40,0:11:35.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,靠它 我們將會在歷史上留名
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.43,0:11:39.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作為拯救全世界女性的美的巨人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.64,0:11:47.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我吃不下了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.50,0:11:50.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過…我開動啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.93,0:11:57.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在鬱悶些什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.47,0:11:59.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.33,0:12:01.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.38,0:12:03.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 沒什麼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.69,0:12:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是覺得能跟小鈴和風璃一起享受這麼棒的旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.50,0:12:09.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.18,0:12:11.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.59,0:12:16.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你那時候邀請我加入樂隊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.18,0:12:19.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你一直跟我在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.11,0:12:22.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…你這是在說什麼啦 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.93,0:12:26.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 小鈴在害羞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.17,0:12:27.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才…才沒有這回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.02,0:12:34.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.24,0:12:36.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會是什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.35,0:12:38.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難不成 那是小偷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.38,0:12:41.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 怎麼可能
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.75,0:13:10.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小小小小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.58,0:13:12.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.97,0:13:16.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那看起來簡直就是殭屍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.56,0:13:19.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個人是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.78,0:13:22.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.96,0:13:26.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個人去過脂肪燃燒油發表會現場
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.34,0:13:30.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不會錯的 雖然現在瘦了不少
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.95,0:13:34.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難不成 是因為塗了那種可疑的藥物才變成這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.61,0:13:39.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此消瘦過度 肚子過餓 才幹出那種事來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.01,0:13:44.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.21,0:13:49.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可不好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.93,0:13:54.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突破大氣式
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.75,0:13:58.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飛身踢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.41,0:14:05.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可別小看原本想當女子摔角手的我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.96,0:14:07.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.03,0:14:09.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 趁現在趕快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.47,0:14:10.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.58,0:14:12.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 怎麼會沒訊號啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.83,0:14:19.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼會這樣 連船員也變這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.07,0:14:22.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 大家都太想變瘦了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.89,0:14:24.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,風璃應該沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.87,0:14:26.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那聲音該不會是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.99,0:14:29.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.23,0:14:34.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我雖然很喜歡吃 但是我不喜歡被吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.68,0:14:36.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突破大氣式
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.17,0:14:41.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飛射身踢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.67,0:14:48.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.84,0:14:51.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,風琉你還好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.66,0:14:55.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妮子 我好害怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.57,0:14:58.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在這船上可待不下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.97,0:15:01.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們坐救生艇逃出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.58,0:15:08.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有了 救生艇
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.93,0:15:11.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請等一等
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.73,0:15:13.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請帶上我們一起走
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.74,0:15:15.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等我們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.02,0:15:15.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,索尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.01,0:15:16.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.08,0:15:20.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經按下了將救生艇退回去的按鈕了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.77,0:15:22.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點過來 索尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.79,0:15:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.82,0:15:29.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那邊有那麼多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.34,0:15:32.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼總是朝著我們來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.77,0:15:36.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這些人都瘦得太厲害了 肚子超級餓
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.32,0:15:39.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們是不是有人帶了吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.97,0:15:42.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃的嗎 我沒帶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.84,0:15:44.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也沒帶呀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.76,0:15:47.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一擔心肚子就餓了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.13,0:15:53.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,風璃 把零食丟掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.35,0:15:55.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.51,0:15:56.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別問了 趕緊扔掉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.04,0:15:59.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,性命和零食哪個更重要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.41,0:16:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然是一樣重要了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.44,0:16:05.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,索尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.94,0:16:09.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和索尼子的美好回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.43,0:16:14.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會永遠永遠留在謳歌的記憶迴路裡的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.61,0:16:20.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣 不要說得像永遠的離別一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.81,0:16:21.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.51,0:16:23.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.48,0:16:28.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來這邊 10號甲板的103室
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.07,0:16:38.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.68,0:16:41.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.51,0:16:45.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個 來到這裡就沒事了 放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.12,0:16:48.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這是造出了什麼好東西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.05,0:16:51.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都不得了了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.72,0:16:53.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上場寺也沒想到會變成這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.59,0:16:57.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種藥居然會有這麼大的個人差異
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.56,0:17:00.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,藥效正常作用的不就只有你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.31,0:17:07.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請問 有沒有把變得像殭屍一樣的人們變回原樣的方法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.10,0:17:13.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脂肪燃燒油是使用後6小時見效果並持續3小時
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.85,0:17:16.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是在發表會後立刻塗上的話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.35,0:17:18.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在半夜12點時應該會失效
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.05,0:17:22.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隨後大家就會變回原樣是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.47,0:17:24.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有點希望了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.67,0:17:26.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果沒變回來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.99,0:17:30.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那時只能在這裡等到救援人員到來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.77,0:17:33.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救援人員 要等到什麼時候才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.70,0:17:36.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,船隻現在停在海面上 手機也打不通
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.05,0:17:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裡連水和食物都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.42,0:17:41.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.30,0:17:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.64,0:18:01.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我沒事 你們快從這裡逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.33,0:18:08.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我寶貝的零食們
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.94,0:18:10.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你夠了 趕緊逃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.62,0:18:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.22,0:18:20.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下面 往下走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.05,0:18:27.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,躲那影子裡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.46,0:18:33.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚上11:57分
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.99,0:18:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果如社長所說的話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.97,0:18:39.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有3分鐘大家就能變回原樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.32,0:18:40.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但願如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.50,0:18:44.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,風璃 你已經沒有零食了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.76,0:18:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.23,0:18:48.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別說什麼肉饅頭的話還是有的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.24,0:18:50.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都說沒有了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.21,0:18:55.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出現了 往這邊來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.87,0:19:01.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼 明明已經沒有零食了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.47,0:19:06.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難道把零食吃光了 這次要吃我們…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.64,0:19:08.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.63,0:19:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要逃了 這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.83,0:19:23.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 現在什麼時候了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.89,0:19:26.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,過0點了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.27,0:19:26.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.05,0:19:29.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是會變回原樣的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.05,0:19:34.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有如風中之燭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.46,0:19:37.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 風璃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.73,0:19:39.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.34,0:19:43.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們「第一宇宙速度」一直以來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.43,0:19:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 從今以後也永遠在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.52,0:19:49.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去天國之後三個人一起玩搖滾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.18,0:19:53.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 不能放棄
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.03,0:19:55.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有放棄
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.96,0:19:58.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我去牽制住他們
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.26,0:20:01.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,風璃和尼子趁機逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.57,0:20:04.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.53,0:20:08.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 說要三人一起的不是小鈴嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.91,0:20:09.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.25,0:20:16.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不想放棄
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.76,0:20:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想和小鈴還有風璃在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.44,0:20:22.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永遠在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.62,0:20:24.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.72,0:20:26.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難道說
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.82,0:20:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直繼續搖滾樂隊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.93,0:20:37.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們在做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.82,0:20:40.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別做傻事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.09,0:20:48.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恢復原樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.89,0:20:59.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 風璃
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.21,0:21:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說呢 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.99,0:21:08.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,--------ED-------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.12,0:22:46.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多虧大家恢復了原樣
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.57,0:22:48.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們被成功救了上來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.00,0:22:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被發現副作用的脂肪燃燒油
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.56,0:22:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,理所當然的被中止銷售
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.39,0:23:00.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌的廣告演出如同泡沫般消散了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.25,0:23:04.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,於是要說謳歌后來怎麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.98,0:23:11.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我得快點回到事務所
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.20,0:23:15.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易謳歌的時代到來了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.21,0:23:25.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,主角行蹤不明可不是開玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.75,0:23:40.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{@\fad(1000,0)\pos(441,360)\c&H823DC1&\3c&HC1D8FF&\blur1}星雨
Comment: 0,0:00:00.15,0:00:00.15,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,==========================IN=======================
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.66,0:07:12.97,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}キミはキミに出来ること
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.22,0:07:15.63,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}僕は僕に出来ること
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.80,0:07:18.21,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}答えなんてなくていいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.36,0:07:21.12,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}新しい明日見つけてよ　Right Now！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.12,0:07:28.50,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}走れ走れずっと未来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.73,0:07:31.11,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}キミは僕のLucky Star！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.29,0:07:33.72,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}僕はキミのHappy Star！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.78,0:07:39.04,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.87,0:07:44.06,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah！
Comment: 0,0:07:41.88,0:07:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.66,0:07:12.97,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}你做你力所能及的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.22,0:07:15.63,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}我做我力所能及的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.80,0:07:18.21,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}沒有答案也沒有關係
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.36,0:07:21.12,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}去尋找新的可能性吧 Right Now！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.12,0:07:28.50,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}向著未來不斷奔跑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.73,0:07:31.11,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}你是我的Lucky Star！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.29,0:07:33.72,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}我是你的Happy Star！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.78,0:07:39.04,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.87,0:07:44.06,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah！
Comment: 0,0:07:43.60,0:07:45.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,===============================ED==========================
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.49,0:21:39.66,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}今の僕はもう独りじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.63,0:21:44.66,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}だって君が居いてくれる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.36,0:21:47.25,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}ナイトメア・バスター
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.62,0:21:50.18,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}闇を照らす言霊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.25,0:21:52.09,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}ナイトメア・バスター
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.29,0:21:57.24,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}あの頃の僕の心も解き放てくれたね
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.29,0:22:00.07,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}これからだ日も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.79,0:22:06.38,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}そばに居て 刀何時もの向き斬って　悲劇の渦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.68,0:22:11.13,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}行く手に広がる闇に切り開いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.78,0:22:15.80,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}傷つくこともう恐れないて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.32,0:22:20.57,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}握り締めてキミの手の温もりが今
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.80,0:22:25.50,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}覚悟を固め　無敵にするから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.97,0:22:32.41,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}君とならどんな今も塗り替えて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.50,0:22:35.66,EDJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}明日へ　共に走れ
Comment: 0,0:22:32.49,0:22:34.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.49,0:21:39.66,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}現在的我並不是獨自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.63,0:21:44.66,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}因為有你在我的身邊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.36,0:21:47.25,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}Nightmare Buster
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.62,0:21:50.18,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}照亮黑暗的咒語
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.25,0:21:52.09,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}Nightmare Buster
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.29,0:21:57.24,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}是你解放了我那時的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.29,0:22:00.07,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}從今以後的日子也是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.79,0:22:06.38,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}你在我身邊 刀刃向著那熟悉的方向揮去 這悲劇的漩渦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.68,0:22:11.13,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}斬開阻擋在前方的黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.78,0:22:15.80,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}別去害怕受傷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.32,0:22:20.57,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}現在握緊你的手去感受那份溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.80,0:22:25.50,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}我會堅定決心 變得戰無不勝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.97,0:22:32.41,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}和你一起的話什麼命運都能改變
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.50,0:22:35.66,EDCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}讓我們朝向明天一起加速吧
Comment: 0,0:09:17.10,0:09:19.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,==============================OP===============
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.53,0:02:44.08,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい響く　music
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.12,0:02:45.54,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい決まれ　posing
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.66,0:02:47.00,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい届け　feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.04,0:02:48.54,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}スーパーそに　let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.58,0:02:50.08,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい刺激　てんこ盛り
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.16,0:02:51.67,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい　どうにも　空回り
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.75,0:02:53.21,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい君とずっと　enjoy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.29,0:02:55.30,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}スーパーそに　let's goです
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.35,0:03:11.64,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}最近思い付きました
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.44,0:03:17.82,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}気持ち伝えるで大変
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.65,0:03:24.37,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}上手できたりできなかったり
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.57,0:03:28.08,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}難しからおくの出で
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.41,0:03:31.08,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}猛烈体当たりです
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.46,0:03:37.34,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}だけど人見知り　誤魔化して背伸び
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.55,0:03:41.22,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}足がガクブルで　開き
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.38,0:03:43.43,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}なお追ってあるがままGO
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.68,0:03:46.35,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}全開　爽快　大展開
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.43,0:03:49.47,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}なんでも直進ストレート
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.77,0:03:52.44,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}正解　毎回　無限大
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.48,0:03:55.56,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今日も元気にここにいます
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.94,0:03:57.44,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい響く　music
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.44,0:03:58.90,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい決まれ　posing
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.03,0:04:00.44,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい届け　feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.53,0:04:01.94,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}スーパーそに　let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.03,0:04:03.49,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい刺激　てんこ盛り
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.53,0:04:04.99,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい　どうにも　空回り
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.07,0:04:06.62,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい君とずっと　enjoy
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.66,0:04:08.70,OPJP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}スーパーそに　let's goです
Comment: 0,0:04:06.66,0:04:08.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.53,0:02:44.08,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情響徹吧 music
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.12,0:02:45.54,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情擺出吧 posing
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.66,0:02:47.00,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情傳達吧 feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.04,0:02:48.54,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}超級索尼 let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.58,0:02:50.08,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}非常刺激 興緻高起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.16,0:02:51.67,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}可卻又總是空歡喜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.75,0:02:53.21,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}和你一起 enjoy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.29,0:02:55.30,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}超級索尼 let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.35,0:03:11.64,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}最近想到件事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.44,0:03:17.82,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想傳達心意真是不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.65,0:03:24.37,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}可能順利可能失敗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.57,0:03:28.08,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}太過困難不敢上去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.41,0:03:31.08,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}可卻又撞了個正著
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.46,0:03:37.34,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}認生的我只好假裝伸伸腰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.55,0:03:41.22,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}兩腿都在發抖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.38,0:03:43.43,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}只好這樣追上去 GO
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.68,0:03:46.35,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}全力  爽快  大展開　
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.43,0:03:49.47,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}不管如何都是直球
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.77,0:03:52.44,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}正解  每次  無限大
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.48,0:03:55.56,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今天也精神的在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.94,0:03:57.44,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情響徹吧 music
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.44,0:03:58.90,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情擺出吧 posing
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.03,0:04:00.44,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情傳達吧 feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.53,0:04:01.94,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}超級索尼 let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.03,0:04:03.49,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}非常刺激 興緻高起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.53,0:04:04.99,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}可卻又總是空歡喜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.07,0:04:06.62,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}和你一起 enjoy
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.66,0:04:08.70,OPCN,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}超級索尼 let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.71,0:04:10.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
