[Script Info]
;  Script generated by Aegisub 3.0.2
;  http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2014-02-12 23:46:40
; // 版本: 0.74
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: Default Aegisub file
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00424242,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: title,方正稚艺_GBK,23,&H0041070F,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFMaruMoji-W9,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00676767,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正少儿_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00696969,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: EDJP,DFMaruMoji-W9,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H006C6C6C,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正少儿_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00696969,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.15,0:00:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}{\an8\fscx80\fscy80}譯制：大佐爬床去玩秋葉原脫衣魔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.06,0:00:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.76,0:00:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我也十分的健康
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.09,0:00:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大學的前期測試也順利結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.88,0:00:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓人期待的暑假就在眼前了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.13,0:00:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣真的好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.47,0:00:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點小
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.36,0:00:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風璃 很可愛哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.49,0:00:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是被我選中的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.98,0:00:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它將風璃的魅力毫無保留地表現了出來
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.62,0:00:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不說具體什麼魅力了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.61,0:00:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 就輪到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.69,0:00:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴真是大膽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.84,0:00:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天會讓女孩變得大膽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.20,0:00:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是夏天讓女孩變成那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.78,0:00:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是女孩對夏天所起的反應
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.42,0:00:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是個很難講的問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.07,0:00:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 真有哲理
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.57,0:00:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.41,0:01:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後是我們的尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.42,0:01:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 真是件可愛的連衣泳裝呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.21,0:01:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴看中的我還以為會是件奔放的泳裝呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.11,0:01:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.01,0:01:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會那樣想就是外行人的膚淺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.88,0:01:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼子的身材很好 藏起來才剛好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.01,0:01:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的性感隱藏在背後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.67,0:01:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正所謂藏頭露尾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.31,0:01:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.43,0:01:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一眼看去是可愛又清純的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.50,0:01:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其背後卻隱藏著妖艷女人的本性
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.33,0:01:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼一種理念
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.81,0:01:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 那個理念很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.81,0:01:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是氣質啦 氣質
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.91,0:01:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 明天可不只是去海邊玩而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.76,0:01:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同時也是「第一宇宙速度」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.44,0:01:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一次定期演唱會的宣傳活動
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.72,0:01:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有必要讓盡量更多的客人關注才行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.97,0:02:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為此這可是十分有必要的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.31,0:02:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但…但是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.90,0:02:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 你還繼續說的話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.53,0:02:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴她讓你穿上更難為情泳裝的可能性…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.75,0:02:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會穿這個泳裝努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.78,0:02:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 明天要在海邊大鬧一場哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.95,0:02:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前 讓天氣先大鬧了一場
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.04,0:04:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要一塗就能讓你體裡的脂肪燃燒殆盡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.72,0:04:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在意的地方塗上一點
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.75,0:04:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是終極減肥方法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.54,0:04:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脂肪堂的脂肪燃燒油
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.60,0:04:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給予所有女性無上的美
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.46,0:04:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個就是下個月要開播的廣告嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.01,0:04:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 謳歌
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.45,0:04:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然能接到在全國放送廣告的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.54,0:05:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.29,0:05:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回想起來一直以來都是在街頭當接待
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.02,0:05:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,促銷傳單的模特兒之類不起眼的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.17,0:05:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時而甚至想要把經紀人滅掉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.84,0:05:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 辛苦了這麼久終於有了回報
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.34,0:05:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌的時代終於到來了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.48,0:05:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜 真是太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.61,0:05:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌 真是太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.15,0:05:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要簽名的話就趁現在
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.23,0:05:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 這種大工作竟然會找我們這呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.50,0:05:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實在街上我就有被問過要不要去拍廣告了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.04,0:05:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是說在全國放送的廣告的出演人物
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.93,0:05:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠街頭的尋找就決定了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.30,0:05:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說謳歌有如此的魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.52,0:05:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.14,0:05:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.28,0:05:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 索尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.74,0:05:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後天謳歌會在脂肪燃燒油的體驗發表會出場
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.22,0:06:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的話要不要來看看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.16,0:06:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把朋友帶過來也沒有關係哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.96,0:06:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.25,0:06:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有問題 謳歌可是VIP待遇
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.04,0:06:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且發表會的地點…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.59,0:06:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是超豪華客輪哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.25,0:06:24.13,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\pos(248,81)\b1\c&H0600BA&}亡者的游輪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.46,0:06:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然… 請…請務必讓我去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.74,0:06:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.26,0:06:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能坐那種船的人果然只有名流呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.71,0:06:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是讓人感覺理所當然的那種
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.01,0:06:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好寬敞
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.65,0:06:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好整齊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.62,0:06:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好豪華
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.68,0:06:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了嗎 裡面還有溫泉和電影館哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.70,0:06:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有網球場和賭場
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.26,0:06:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有大型餐廳和壽司店
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.01,0:07:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真期待能品嘗到什麼樣的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.06,0:07:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這世間如此的不公平
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.10,0:07:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是…這就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.74,0:07:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所謂的名流生活對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.39,0:08:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}燃燒脂肪油體驗發表會
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.39,0:08:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}主辦方 脂肪堂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.68,0:08:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 大家都打扮得好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.20,0:08:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得我們幾個跟這裡很不相配
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.55,0:08:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.32,0:08:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我才該說抱歉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.22,0:08:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓各位久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.53,0:08:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始脂肪堂的新產品
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.37,0:08:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燃燒脂肪油的體驗發表會
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.73,0:08:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先有請脂肪堂的CEO 上場寺株子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.62,0:08:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及出演廣告的 殺戮院謳歌
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.87,0:08:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌 好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.29,0:08:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛也已經介紹過 我是脂肪堂的CEO 上場寺株子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.85,0:08:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客套話我就不多說了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.60,0:09:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始介紹本公司劃時代新產品
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.96,0:09:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用方法非常簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.76,0:09:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只需像這樣 塗在想要瘦下來的地方即可
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.60,0:09:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這麼簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.61,0:09:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.56,0:09:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是一個月前的上場寺
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.23,0:09:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而現在在大家面前的就是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.82,0:09:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用了燃燒脂肪油一個月之後的上場寺
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.44,0:09:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而站在這裡的謳歌 也是受益於燃燒脂肪油
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.81,0:09:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能夠擁有這麼苗條的身材的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.03,0:09:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說是吧 謳歌
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.36,0:09:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 全都是燃燒脂肪油的功勞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.70,0:09:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然謳歌本來就很苗條的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.47,0:09:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燃燒脂肪油有多種類型
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.25,0:09:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬請各位回房後隨意嘗試
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.20,0:09:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不介意的話 各位船員也請試用一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.76,0:09:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脂肪燃燒油在使用6小時後開始見效
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.63,0:10:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我期待著明天在這裡與變美了的大家再會
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.84,0:10:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 那個女社長
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.80,0:10:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可疑的要死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.78,0:10:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 難得我們能夠被招待到這裡來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.91,0:10:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不能說這種話哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.42,0:10:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}用法·用量說明：
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.42,0:10:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}每天一次 取適量於手心進行塗抹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.42,0:10:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}使用6小時後開始見效
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.42,0:10:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}持續時間3小時
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.42,0:10:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}請注意閱讀說明 避免陽光直射
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.42,0:10:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\an7\fs18}請保存於陰冷處
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.70,0:10:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用6小時候開始見效 持續時間3小時嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.22,0:10:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妮子 你該不會是想塗這東西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.49,0:10:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我也有不少介意的部位嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.34,0:10:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我勸你還是別塗了 這東西好可疑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.92,0:10:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 妮子還是這樣子最有魅力了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.42,0:10:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.90,0:10:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.20,0:10:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快到晚飯時間了 再不去的話就沒得吃啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.93,0:10:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不可能的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.51,0:10:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便是社長您 以一己之見拍了廣告
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.06,0:10:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還舉辦體驗發表會
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.44,0:11:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脂肪燃燒油依然處於試作階段
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.43,0:11:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該再多做些臨床試驗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.42,0:11:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確保使用安全之後才能…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.93,0:11:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.73,0:11:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這身體不就證明了其效果了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.21,0:11:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,效果也是有個人差異的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.63,0:11:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某些情況下或許會帶來副作用
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.83,0:11:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,計劃還是會繼續進行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.01,0:11:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是把全公司的資金
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.44,0:11:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都投進到脂肪燃燒油裡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.22,0:11:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今已經沒有回頭路可走了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.56,0:11:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.20,0:11:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是愛操心啊 沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.07,0:11:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所發明的脂肪燃燒油
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.49,0:11:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是實現了所有女性
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.72,0:11:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望變瘦的願望的夢幻產品
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.30,0:11:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠它 我們將會在歷史上留名
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.33,0:11:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為拯救全世界女性的美的巨人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.54,0:11:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃不下了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.40,0:11:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過…我開動啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.83,0:12:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在鬱悶些什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.37,0:12:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.23,0:12:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.28,0:12:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 沒什麼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.59,0:12:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是覺得能跟小鈴和風璃一起享受這麼棒的旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.40,0:12:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.08,0:12:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.49,0:12:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你那時候邀請我加入樂隊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.08,0:12:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你一直跟我在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.01,0:12:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你這是在說什麼啦 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.83,0:12:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 小鈴在害羞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.07,0:12:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才…才沒有這回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.92,0:12:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.14,0:12:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會是什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.25,0:12:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難不成 那是小偷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.28,0:12:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 怎麼可能
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.54,0:13:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小小小小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.59,0:13:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.98,0:13:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那看起來簡直就是殭屍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.57,0:13:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個人是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.79,0:13:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.97,0:13:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個人去過脂肪燃燒油發表會現場
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.35,0:13:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不會錯的 雖然現在瘦了不少
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.96,0:13:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難不成 是因為塗了那種可疑的藥物才變成這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.62,0:13:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此消瘦過度 肚子過餓 才幹出那種事來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.02,0:13:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.22,0:13:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.94,0:14:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突破大氣式
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.76,0:14:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛身踢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.42,0:14:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可別小看原本想當女子摔角手的我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.97,0:14:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.04,0:14:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 趁現在趕快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.48,0:14:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.59,0:14:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 怎麼會沒訊號啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.84,0:14:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼會這樣 連船員也變這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.08,0:14:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 大家都太想變瘦了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.90,0:14:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風璃應該沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.88,0:14:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那聲音該不會是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.00,0:14:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.24,0:14:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我雖然很喜歡吃 但是我不喜歡被吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.69,0:14:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突破大氣式
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.18,0:14:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛射身踢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.68,0:14:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.85,0:15:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風琉你還好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.67,0:15:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妮子 我好害怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.58,0:15:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這船上可待不下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.98,0:15:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們坐救生艇逃出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.59,0:15:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了 救生艇
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.94,0:15:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請等一等
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.74,0:15:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請帶上我們一起走
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.75,0:15:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等我們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.03,0:15:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,索尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.02,0:15:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.09,0:15:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經按下了將救生艇退回去的按鈕了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.78,0:15:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點過來 索尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.80,0:15:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.83,0:15:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊有那麼多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.35,0:15:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼總是朝著我們來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.78,0:15:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些人都瘦得太厲害了 肚子超級餓
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.33,0:15:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們是不是有人帶了吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.98,0:15:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃的嗎 我沒帶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.85,0:15:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也沒帶呀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.77,0:15:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一擔心肚子就餓了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.14,0:16:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風璃 把零食丟掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.36,0:16:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.52,0:16:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別問了 趕緊扔掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.05,0:16:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性命和零食哪個更重要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.42,0:16:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然是一樣重要了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.45,0:16:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,索尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.95,0:16:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和索尼子的美好回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.44,0:16:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會永遠永遠留在謳歌的記憶迴路裡的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.62,0:16:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣 不要說得像永遠的離別一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.82,0:16:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.52,0:16:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.49,0:16:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來這邊 10號甲板的103室
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.08,0:16:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.69,0:16:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.52,0:16:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個 來到這裡就沒事了 放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.13,0:16:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這是造出了什麼好東西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.06,0:17:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都不得了了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.73,0:17:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上場寺也沒想到會變成這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.60,0:17:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種藥居然會有這麼大的個人差異
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.57,0:17:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藥效正常作用的不就只有你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.32,0:17:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問 有沒有把變得像殭屍一樣的人們變回原樣的方法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.11,0:17:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脂肪燃燒油是使用後6小時見效果並持續3小時
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.86,0:17:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是在發表會後立刻塗上的話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.36,0:17:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在半夜12點時應該會失效
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.06,0:17:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨後大家就會變回原樣是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.48,0:17:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點希望了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.68,0:17:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果沒變回來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.00,0:17:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時只能在這裡等到救援人員到來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.78,0:17:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救援人員 要等到什麼時候才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.71,0:17:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船隻現在停在海面上 手機也打不通
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.06,0:17:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡連水和食物都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.43,0:17:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.31,0:18:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.65,0:18:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒事 你們快從這裡逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.34,0:18:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我寶貝的零食們
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.95,0:18:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你夠了 趕緊逃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.63,0:18:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.23,0:18:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面 往下走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.06,0:18:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲那影子裡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.47,0:18:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上11:57分
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.00,0:18:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果如社長所說的話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.98,0:18:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有3分鐘大家就能變回原樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.33,0:18:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但願如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.51,0:18:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風璃 你已經沒有零食了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.77,0:18:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.24,0:18:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說什麼肉饅頭的話還是有的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.25,0:18:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說沒有了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.22,0:19:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出現了 往這邊來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.88,0:19:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼 明明已經沒有零食了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.48,0:19:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道把零食吃光了 這次要吃我們…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.65,0:19:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.64,0:19:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要逃了 這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.84,0:19:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 現在什麼時候了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.90,0:19:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過0點了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.28,0:19:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.06,0:19:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是會變回原樣的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.06,0:19:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有如風中之燭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.47,0:19:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼子 風璃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.74,0:19:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.35,0:19:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們「第一宇宙速度」一直以來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.44,0:19:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 從今以後也永遠在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.53,0:19:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去天國之後三個人一起玩搖滾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.19,0:20:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 不能放棄
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.04,0:20:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有放棄
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.97,0:20:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去牽制住他們
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.27,0:20:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風璃和尼子趁機逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.58,0:20:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.54,0:20:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 說要三人一起的不是小鈴嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.92,0:20:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.26,0:20:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想放棄
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.77,0:20:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和小鈴還有風璃在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.45,0:20:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永遠在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.63,0:20:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.73,0:20:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道說
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.83,0:20:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直繼續搖滾樂隊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.94,0:20:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們在做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.83,0:20:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別做傻事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.10,0:20:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恢復原樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.90,0:21:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鈴 風璃
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.22,0:21:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說呢 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.00,0:21:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Comment: 0,0:00:09.01,0:00:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------ED-------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.18,0:22:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多虧大家恢復了原樣
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.58,0:22:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們被成功救了上來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.01,0:23:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被發現副作用的脂肪燃燒油
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.57,0:23:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理所當然的被中止銷售
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.40,0:23:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謳歌的廣告演出如同泡沫般消散了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.26,0:23:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是要說謳歌后來怎麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.99,0:23:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得快點回到事務所
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.21,0:23:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易謳歌的時代到來了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.22,0:23:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主角行蹤不明可不是開玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.04,0:23:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{@\fad(1000,0)\pos(441,360)\c&H823DC1&\3c&HC1D8FF&\blur1}星雨
Comment: 0,0:00:00.15,0:00:00.15,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,==========================IN=======================
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.46,0:07:21.77,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}キミはキミに出来ること
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.02,0:07:24.43,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}僕は僕に出来ること
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.60,0:07:27.01,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}答えなんてなくていいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.16,0:07:29.92,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}新しい明日見つけてよ　Right Now！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.92,0:07:37.30,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}走れ走れずっと未来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.53,0:07:39.91,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}キミは僕のLucky Star！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.09,0:07:42.52,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}僕はキミのHappy Star！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.58,0:07:47.84,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.67,0:07:52.86,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah！
Comment: 0,0:07:50.68,0:07:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.46,0:07:21.77,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}你做你力所能及的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.02,0:07:24.43,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}我做我力所能及的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.60,0:07:27.01,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}沒有答案也沒有關係
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.16,0:07:29.92,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}去尋找新的可能性吧 Right Now！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.92,0:07:37.30,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}向著未來不斷奔跑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.53,0:07:39.91,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}你是我的Lucky Star！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.09,0:07:42.52,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}我是你的Happy Star！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.58,0:07:47.84,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.67,0:07:52.86,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah！
Comment: 0,0:07:43.60,0:07:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,===============================ED==========================
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.73,0:21:48.90,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}今の僕はもう独りじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.87,0:21:53.90,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}だって君が居いてくれる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.60,0:21:56.49,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}ナイトメア?バスター
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.86,0:21:59.42,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}闇を照らす言霊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.49,0:22:01.33,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}ナイトメア?バスター
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.53,0:22:06.48,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}あの頃の僕の心も解き放てくれたね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.53,0:22:09.31,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}これからだ日も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.03,0:22:15.62,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}そばに居て 刀何時もの向き斬って　悲劇の渦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.92,0:22:20.37,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}行く手に広がる闇に切り開いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.02,0:22:25.04,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}傷つくこともう恐れないて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.56,0:22:29.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}握り締めてキミの手の温もりが今
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.04,0:22:34.74,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}覚悟を固め　無敵にするから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.21,0:22:41.65,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}君とならどんな今も塗り替えて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.74,0:22:44.90,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}明日へ　共に走れ
Comment: 0,0:22:41.73,0:22:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.73,0:21:48.90,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}現在的我並不是獨自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.87,0:21:53.90,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}因為有你在我的身邊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.60,0:21:56.49,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}Nightmare Buster
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.86,0:21:59.42,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}照亮黑暗的咒語
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.49,0:22:01.33,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}Nightmare Buster
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.53,0:22:06.48,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}是你解放了我那時的我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.53,0:22:09.31,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}從今以後的日子也是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.03,0:22:15.62,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}你在我身邊 刀刃向著那熟悉的方向揮去 這悲劇的漩渦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.92,0:22:20.37,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}斬開阻擋在前方的黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.02,0:22:25.04,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}別去害怕受傷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.56,0:22:29.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}現在握緊你的手去感受那份溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.04,0:22:34.74,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}我會堅定決心 變得戰無不勝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.21,0:22:41.65,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}和你一起的話什麼命運都能改變
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.74,0:22:44.90,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}{\an7}讓我們朝向明天一起加速吧
Comment: 0,0:09:17.10,0:09:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,==============================OP===============
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.53,0:02:43.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい響く　music
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.12,0:02:44.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい決まれ　posing
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.66,0:02:46.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい届け　feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.04,0:02:47.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}スーパーそに　let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.58,0:02:49.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい刺激　てんこ盛り
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.16,0:02:50.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい　どうにも　空回り
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:52.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい君とずっと　enjoy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.29,0:02:54.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}スーパーそに　let's goです
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.35,0:03:10.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}最近思い付きました
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.44,0:03:16.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}気持ち伝えるで大変
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.65,0:03:23.37,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}上手できたりできなかったり
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.57,0:03:27.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}難しからおくの出で
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.41,0:03:30.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}猛烈体当たりです
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.46,0:03:36.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}だけど人見知り　誤魔化して背伸び
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.55,0:03:40.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}足がガクブルで　開き
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.38,0:03:42.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}なお追ってあるがままGO
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.68,0:03:45.35,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}全開　爽快　大展開
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.43,0:03:48.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}なんでも直進ストレート
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.77,0:03:51.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}正解　毎回　無限大
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.48,0:03:54.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今日も元気にここにいます
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.94,0:03:56.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい響く　music
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.44,0:03:57.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい決まれ　posing
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.03,0:03:59.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いっばい届け　feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.53,0:04:00.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}スーパーそに　let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.03,0:04:02.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい刺激　てんこ盛り
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.53,0:04:03.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい　どうにも　空回り
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.07,0:04:05.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すごい君とずっと　enjoy
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.66,0:04:07.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}スーパーそに　let's goです
Comment: 0,0:04:05.66,0:04:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.53,0:02:43.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情響徹吧 music
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.12,0:02:44.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情擺出吧 posing
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.66,0:02:46.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情傳達吧 feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.04,0:02:47.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}超級索尼 let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.58,0:02:49.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}非常刺激 興緻高起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.16,0:02:50.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}可卻又總是空歡喜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:52.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}和你一起 enjoy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.29,0:02:54.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}超級索尼 let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.35,0:03:10.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}最近想到件事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.44,0:03:16.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想傳達心意真是不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.65,0:03:23.37,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}可能順利可能失敗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.57,0:03:27.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}太過困難不敢上去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.41,0:03:30.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}可卻又撞了個正著
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.46,0:03:36.34,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}認生的我只好假裝伸伸腰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.55,0:03:40.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}兩腿都在發抖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.38,0:03:42.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}只好這樣追上去 GO
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.68,0:03:45.35,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}全力  爽快  大展開
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.43,0:03:48.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}不管如何都是直球
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.77,0:03:51.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}正解  每次  無限大
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.48,0:03:54.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今天也精神的在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.94,0:03:56.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情響徹吧 music
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.44,0:03:57.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情擺出吧 posing
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.03,0:03:59.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}盡情傳達吧 feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.53,0:04:00.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}超級索尼 let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.03,0:04:02.49,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}非常刺激 興緻高起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.53,0:04:03.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}可卻又總是空歡喜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.07,0:04:05.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}和你一起 enjoy
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.66,0:04:07.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}超級索尼 let's go
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.71,0:04:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,


