
[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Audio File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][10][x264_aac].mkv
Video File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][10][x264_aac].mkv
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 2
Video Position: 31527
Video Color Matrix: BT.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.93,0:21:59.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由动漫国字幕组和轻之国度字幕组联合制作\N仅供试看,请支持购买正版音像制品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:02.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻译:栗花落&枪叔&Cosmo  校对:娜娜莉  时间:Rodax  后期:sora  MKV:乌贼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.32,0:00:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是今天转入这个班的鹰乃宫秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.06,0:00:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是刚来京都 许多事都不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.73,0:00:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若能详细告知就太好了 请多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.80,0:00:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个让人有些不爽的男孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.60,0:00:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次见到时我是这么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.96,0:00:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢 感觉笑脸都是勉强装出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.26,0:00:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在想想
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.43,0:00:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是因为你努力去适应新环境所造成的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.81,0:00:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之那时的我就是如此想的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.11,0:00:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时的我…自己这么说有些怪怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.31,0:00:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是与别人不同的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.43,0:00:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更何况从外表看来 我是让人无法接近的那种人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.62,0:00:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就结果而言不仅周围的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.58,0:00:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连大人们也敬而远之
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.90,0:00:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是只有你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.16,0:00:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猿渡~君
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.37,0:01:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.95,0:01:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然对猿渡同学做出那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.46,0:01:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是转校生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.21,0:01:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉 我没想到你被吓成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.06,0:01:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被素不相识的男生突然凑过来当然会这样吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.63,0:01:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么素不相识哇 还真过分呐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.05,0:01:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是昨天转学过来的…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.86,0:01:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹰乃宫秋人 名字我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.50,0:01:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但对我来说你依旧是陌生人这点不曾改变
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.57,0:01:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 但是都这样交谈了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.22,0:01:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不是素不相识的人了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.40,0:01:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去行吗 已经上课了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.02,0:02:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来猿渡君有逃课的特权啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.48,0:02:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该摊牌了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.83,0:02:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你甚至这样逃课陪我 肯定有某种目的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.34,0:02:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咿呀 虽说谈不上目的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.77,0:02:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想跟你做朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.03,0:02:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.60,0:02:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是盲目的收小弟跟班
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.93,0:02:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于集团的平衡会出乎意料的崩溃的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.40,0:02:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不啊 不是跟班而是做朋友啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.77,0:02:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见你时就觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.47,0:02:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是那种不管是好还是坏
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.40,0:02:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都能坦诚相待的好朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.59,0:02:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定会成为好朋友哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.99,0:02:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要朋友嘛 好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.54,0:02:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.52,0:02:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你的期望 我已经知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.58,0:03:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹰乃宫君 一起吃午饭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.84,0:03:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,课程跟得上么 想借笔记本可以随时来找我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.41,0:03:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 放学后一起玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.85,0:03:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们 容我稍微考虑下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.46,0:03:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 话别这么说嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.35,0:03:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是考虑到这点我准备了两本笔记本
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.98,0:03:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有事先走了 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.73,0:03:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猿渡君 稍等 猿渡君
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.64,0:03:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猿渡君！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.01,0:03:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊 我今天能和全班同学聊天了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.17,0:03:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 朋友变多了这不蛮好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.34,0:03:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你所期望的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.49,0:03:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是你做的手脚嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.87,0:03:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是做手脚什么的真难听
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.62,0:03:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是向大家传达你想要交朋友而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.26,0:04:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你误会了什么 我不是想随便交朋友的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.25,0:04:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想跟你…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.61,0:04:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前我就说过 我不想跟你做朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.57,0:04:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.31,0:04:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上课了 你回教室
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.78,0:04:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猿渡君 我不会放弃的！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.99,0:04:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样我也会采取相应手段的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.35,0:04:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为秋人同学做了便当 请吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.57,0:04:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 鹰乃宫 午休的时候来踢足球好不
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.27,0:04:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起挥洒青春的汗水吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.69,0:04:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹰乃宫君 请跟我一起进入文艺部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.71,0:04:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和你一起创作小本子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.63,0:04:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要人家和你一起回家也可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.50,0:04:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是因为喜欢你呐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.73,0:04:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹰乃宫君~
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.79,0:05:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.58,0:05:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咿呀 这个…这到底是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.49,0:05:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有事先撤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.19,0:05:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.26,0:05:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事儿还没说完
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.72,0:05:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你别走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.39,0:05:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猿渡同学 又是你搞的事儿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.47,0:05:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs30}就是就是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.55,0:05:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后宫是男人的梦想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.10,0:05:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说我没希望这种…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.40,0:05:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹰乃宫君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.32,0:05:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你逃的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.25,0:05:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家是真心的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.38,0:05:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.19,0:05:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有很好的素质
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.21,0:05:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.86,0:05:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 我说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.55,0:05:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为我的奴隶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.78,0:05:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说硬上是不行的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.39,0:05:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我像傻瓜一样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.81,0:05:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是自己筹划的事 反而自己却心神不宁了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.80,0:05:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你一点都不知道我的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.15,0:05:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二天接着的再第二天
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.52,0:05:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管我对你如何的冷淡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.71,0:05:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都丝毫不放弃 一直跟我搭话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.14,0:05:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不耐烦的我干脆请假不去上学了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.35,0:06:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家的话就不会看见你就行了呗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.28,0:06:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那只是在欺骗自己
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.73,0:06:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要为了那男生而心神不宁！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.83,0:06:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种蠢事怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.23,0:06:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然是找借口请假不去上课啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.56,0:06:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 在擅闯民宅被人发现之前找到你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.26,0:06:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实走运了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.87,0:06:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然若无其事的闯进戒备森严的这里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.02,0:06:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你那胆量与莽撞 有胜算么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.98,0:06:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 明知是私闯民宅也要到这儿来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.31,0:06:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来这是有什么目的的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.34,0:06:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找茬 我是来找茬的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.23,0:07:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确我缠着你是冒犯了你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.43,0:07:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但至少 我是认认真真的去面对你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.20,0:07:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若你也光明正大的拒绝我 那我会放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.34,0:07:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你则是利用不相干的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.58,0:07:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种拐弯抹角的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.13,0:07:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话我很受打击 很是生气
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.75,0:07:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我理解你的愤怒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.53,0:07:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以给你一个泄愤的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.54,0:07:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想一拳打倒我么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.20,0:07:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打倒这个把你的和谐生活弄得一团糟的我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.33,0:07:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先说好 我可没那么弱哦

Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.22,0:08:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 输掉了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.48,0:08:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么好笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.11,0:08:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这样一来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.47,0:08:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管谁说什么 我和猿渡君都已经是朋友了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.80,0:08:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 还有打架前说的那些话是骗人的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.16,0:08:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了能让你动真格才说的 抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.72,0:08:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴 能和这样认真的猿渡君争辩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.90,0:08:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都彼此打的这么尽兴
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.73,0:08:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的就只是做朋友了 没错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.34,0:09:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你漫画看多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.33,0:09:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说过了不会和你做朋友 你要我说几遍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.77,0:09:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是能不能和你做朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.88,0:09:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是早已经是朋友了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.54,0:09:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和猿渡君
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.73,0:09:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管从哪里看怎么看 我和你都肯定是朋友的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.78,0:09:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢 我也下定决心了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.10,0:09:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这样啊 这样啊 终于得到你的认可了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.72,0:09:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会和你做朋友的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.18,0:09:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…诶…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.81,0:09:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…猿渡君
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.85,0:09:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要什么朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.69,0:09:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是让我去填补别人留下的空白什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.66,0:09:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种人我才不想有瓜葛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.99,0:09:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要的东西 我真正想要的东西是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.30,0:09:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对那时的我来说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.22,0:09:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友之上的关系也就只有那个了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.00,0:09:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管发生什么彼此的关系也不会破碎的…知己
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.62,0:10:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是一副邋遢的样子 快去洗个澡 秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.72,0:10:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那换洗的衣服就放这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.98,0:10:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛巾就用这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.36,0:10:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.86,0:10:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说猿渡君 你要不要一起洗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.82,0:10:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也很想快点把身子洗干净吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.37,0:10:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底在说些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.11,0:10:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情怎么可能会…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.99,0:10:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 反正大家都是男人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.22,0:10:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去洗澡了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.80,0:10:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 请慢用
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.90,0:11:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实我的名字挺爷们的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.84,0:11:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时我的行为举止也确实总是很爷们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.91,0:11:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你真的把我当男生看待
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.89,0:11:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从一开始没能更像女孩子那样接触你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.09,0:11:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉我好笨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.91,0:11:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为时至今日的那份误解
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.06,0:11:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无疑问的从那时就开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.58,0:11:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我照看的时间就到这为止了 我也该走了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.98,0:11:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人 我总有一天会把这份误解给修正的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.53,0:13:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 已经可以起床了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.71,0:13:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 烧已经退了 也不咳嗽了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.89,0:14:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 从脸色上来看确实是恢复了不少呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.96,0:14:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那现在我就去洗个澡…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.57,0:14:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.96,0:14:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前哥哥必须做出一个选择
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.22,0:14:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选择
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.59,0:14:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 是非常 非常重要的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.03,0:14:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让哥哥选出这次照顾哥哥的MVP
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.85,0:14:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.90,0:14:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.08,0:14:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次我们之中是在相互竞争谁照顾你最周到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.23,0:14:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 懂了的话就快点选择我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.84,0:14:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说些什么 哥哥肯定是选择我才对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.30,0:14:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是亲妹妹用真爱来照顾的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.69,0:14:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这跟是不是亲妹妹没有关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.58,0:14:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最重要的是谁的照顾是最舒服的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.02,0:14:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我认为料理的味道也是重要的基准
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.98,0:15:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋 秋人 哥哥大人 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.68,0:15:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋 秋人 哥哥大人 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.58,0:15:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋 秋人 哥哥大人 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.96,0:15:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我知道了 稍微等会 现在正在考虑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.68,0:15:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就 会长
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.65,0:15:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 但是我啥都没有做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.08,0:15:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那种事 昨晚我发烧的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.92,0:15:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是会长给我在头上敷上湿毛巾的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.86,0:15:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 确实是有这么一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.40,0:15:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但除了这以外没做什么值得一提的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.51,0:15:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么也不错也是一种照顾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.01,0:15:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 如果是这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.52,0:15:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这份荣誉我就收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.72,0:15:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定收下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.50,0:16:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家也觉得这样就行了吧

Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.39,0:16:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋…秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.22,0:16:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.97,0:16:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不至于受打击成这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.75,0:16:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.38,0:16:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没能获胜确实是很遗憾的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.78,0:16:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起那个来说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.92,0:16:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很担心哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.45,0:16:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.30,0:16:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这次的奖励是在自己的房间中
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.74,0:16:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不受他人干扰 跟哥哥独处的权利来的！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.09,0:16:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？咦？！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.97,0:16:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那么一回事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.55,0:16:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为名字是银兵卫嘛 所以会被误解成男孩子啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.94,0:16:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs30}银球
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.11,0:16:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.64,0:16:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去保卫哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.75,0:16:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是妹妹的义务！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.32,0:16:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.58,0:16:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,授予奖励时
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.65,0:16:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了优胜者和秋人之外
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.45,0:16:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都要离开宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.30,0:17:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提出这样条件的不是别人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.44,0:17:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是你自己啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.22,0:17:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为我觉得自己会优胜的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.08,0:17:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 居然变成这样了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.85,0:17:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不知能否活着走出这道门
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.88,0:17:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.48,0:17:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.35,0:17:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等候您多时了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.79,0:17:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.97,0:17:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.80,0:17:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.89,0:17:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么今天像是变了个人一般呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.87,0:17:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惹您不舒服了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.86,0:17:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃不 也没到那个程度上啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.02,0:17:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.03,0:17:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先品一杯茶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.72,0:17:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粗茶而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.86,0:17:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.82,0:18:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚是尽兴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.65,0:18:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区粗茶 不成敬意
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.34,0:18:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知合不合您口味
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.42,0:18:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 非常完美的礼法
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.77,0:18:15.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不如说
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.68,0:18:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.84,0:18:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多别那样了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.22,0:18:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.87,0:18:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要太过于谦恭了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.49,0:18:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很难受
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.82,0:18:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是二阶堂家人的缘故
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.82,0:18:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里虽说是学生宿舍中的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.52,0:18:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是二阶堂家所有的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.61,0:18:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是那样的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.65,0:18:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 就是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.77,0:18:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.84,0:18:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.94,0:18:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长同学的右眼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.74,0:18:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才一瞬间好像闪了一下红色
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.82,0:18:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.82,0:18:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直戴着的眼罩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.14,0:18:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是姬小路秋人大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.86,0:18:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被您注意到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.29,0:19:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平常戴着眼罩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.33,0:19:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了隐藏这只眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.43,0:19:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这只眼睛中秘密藏有力量
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.02,0:19:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.48,0:19:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借由这只眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.06,0:19:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以随意操纵他人的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.43,0:19:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.81,0:19:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以改成我一直以来都是你的恋人也是能做到的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.77,0:19:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 请放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.48,0:19:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每行使这种力量 我的视力都会一点点降低
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.81,0:19:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.71,0:19:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.92,0:19:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不自觉的瞎用了几次
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.33,0:19:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此我已经受到了些许影响
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.95,0:19:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了今后绝不再用这种力量
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.96,0:19:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平时都用眼罩遮住它
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.73,0:19:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.68,0:19:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长的眼罩居然还有着这层意义
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.41,0:19:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 就是为了这种中二病的设定
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.36,0:20:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天才戴上了彩瞳的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.52,0:20:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.51,0:20:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.87,0:20:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种力量不可能真正存在的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.26,0:20:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说那个啥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.61,0:20:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 两人独处的时间才刚刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.36,0:20:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就让我们好好开开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.68,0:20:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真、真的吗？哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.44,0:20:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 真的什么都没发生吗？！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.05,0:20:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 与其说什么也没发生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.50,0:20:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先品尝了香茶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.61,0:20:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨论了眼罩的话题
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.39,0:20:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后不知怎的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.30,0:20:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教授了我插花的技术
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.21,0:20:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 我插的花
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.59,0:20:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟那个会长两人独处
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.72,0:20:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然这样就结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.37,0:20:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的可以相信你吗 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.08,0:20:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要怀疑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.81,0:20:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.46,0:20:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是亚里沙跟哥哥两人独处的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.46,0:20:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也会那样度过的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.64,0:20:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为亚里沙还小 不明白罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.82,0:20:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是会长还是秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.47,0:21:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不是会说麻烦的谎话的人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.17,0:21:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.21,0:21:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.52,0:21:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从在去会长的房间之前
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.40,0:21:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概敞开3cm的裤子的拉链
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.41,0:21:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍停留在完全一致的位置上这点来看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.13,0:21:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以得出什么也没发生的判断的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.01,0:21:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说这种事情在发现的时候就告诉我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.77,0:21:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.20,0:21:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就相信哥哥的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.42,0:21:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 那个会长居然
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.79,0:21:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是在打什么主意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.99,0:21:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事还用说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.15,0:21:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像平时游手好闲的流氓捡回流浪猫好生疼爱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.45,0:21:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,故意给他人留下好印象
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.40,0:21:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,类似于那样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.06,0:21:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是反差萌了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.04,0:21:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？是那么回事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.33,0:21:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多啦 被萌到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.40,0:21:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我也觉得那样的会长很有魅力啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.40,0:21:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打击！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.59,0:21:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实话实说 很好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.69,0:22:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那个说实话让我的肩膀都僵了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.41,0:22:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 怎么回事啊哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.12,0:22:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好失落 好失落
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.89,0:22:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次就请品尝平时的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.19,0:22:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.06,0:22:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.39,0:22:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.56,0:22:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.46,0:22:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉我好像被世界所遗忘了似的

Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.74,0:24:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内衣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.32,0:24:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没穿
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.88,0:24:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不穿内裤
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.40,0:24:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉飕飕
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.02,0:24:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加上
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.61,0:24:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短裙
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.19,0:24:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺激和
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.77,0:24:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兴奋
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.18,0:24:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.77,0:24:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.32,0:24:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差一点
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.77,0:24:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,边缘
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.38,0:24:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逼近
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.89,0:24:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那须原
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.39,0:24:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻飘飘
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.92,0:24:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴穴
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.51,0:24:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.06,0:24:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.58,0:24:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.14,0:24:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是要看
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.68,0:24:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心情
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.28,0:24:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正相反
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.81,0:24:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.32,0:24:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄控
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.79,0:24:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第11话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.36,0:24:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虚幻





