
[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Audio File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][06][x264_aac].mkv
Video File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][06][x264_aac].mkv
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 2
Video Position: 6031
Video Color Matrix: BT.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.93,0:21:59.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由動漫國字幕組和輕之國度字幕組聯合製作\N僅供試看,請支持購買正版音像製品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:02.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻譯:栗花落&枪叔&Cosmo  校對:娜娜莉  時間:Rodax  後期:sora  MKV:烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.26,0:00:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要理解我 秋菜 我有不得不做之事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.27,0:00:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋男哥哥請你告訴我 你到底在做什麼工作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.81,0:00:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事 不可說
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.40,0:00:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是只有一點請記住 我愛秋菜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.84,0:00:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.19,0:00:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是因為被組織所命令 是我自願前往
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.43,0:00:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了保護世界
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.61,0:00:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更重要的是為了保護我的妹妹…秋菜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.09,0:00:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.42,0:00:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凱旋門是迎接凱旋而歸的士兵們的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.25,0:00:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋菜 你也是我的 凱旋門啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.29,0:01:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰鬥之後的哥哥將凱旋歸到…我這兒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.41,0:01:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 並且我跟你將不再是兄妹 而是作為戀人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.21,0:01:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向世上之人堂堂正正的宣告
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.39,0:01:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我們相愛著」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.70,0:01:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是秋男在這之後過了好幾個月也未歸來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.23,0:01:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦苦等候秋男凱旋的秋菜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.42,0:01:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是秋男一直未歸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.10,0:01:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後來秋菜登上洲際列車
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.59,0:01:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前去她所愛的哥哥…秋男所在的極北之地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.28,0:01:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「禁忌之愛的物語 淚之香榭麗捨」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.94,0:01:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太出色了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.47,0:01:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特別是對秋男與秋菜的描寫就像是現實發生的一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.59,0:01:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這…這如果不是虛構的話！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.13,0:02:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 神在看著
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.91,0:02:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被看到也無所謂 不 不如說想讓他看著
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.73,0:02:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看我們有多麼的相愛！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.88,0:02:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 懺悔 懺悔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.51,0:02:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無懺悔！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.85,0:02:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人君到底是不是妹控 必須親眼見證！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.11,0:04:12.22,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥要對妹妹抱有野心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.97,0:04:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 秋子這丫頭 什麼時候做了這個抱枕
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.46,0:04:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 秋人的抱枕？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.52,0:04:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然做了親妹妹的抱枕 果然秋人君他是…妹控！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.26,0:04:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿勒 神野小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.79,0:04:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.85,0:04:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請用 雖說只是粗茶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.74,0:04:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.06,0:04:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 是姬小路秋人的同事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.46,0:04:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家後輩一直承蒙你的照顧了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.11,0:04:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我這邊才是 今天是來拜訪慰問一下的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.60,0:04:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個請大家不用客氣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.09,0:04:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.76,0:04:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.90,0:04:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.41,0:04:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶 銀銀 阿秋到底在做什麼工作？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.46,0:05:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個…我可不知道 這工作不是我直接介紹的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.86,0:05:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 你妹妹秋子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.26,0:05:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她去買東西了 一會兒就回來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.18,0:05:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是嗎 請吧 大家盡情享用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.83,0:05:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開動了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.33,0:05:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼神野小姐其實不是單純來拜訪的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.06,0:05:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 你怎麼知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.12,0:05:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因為你一直擺著一副擔心的不得了的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.86,0:05:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實關於秋人君 有一件事我想問明白
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.00,0:05:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍霍 我家後輩難不成幹了什麼糟糕之事麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.46,0:05:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,具體什麼事我還說不准
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.18,0:05:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無需說明我也能了解 神野小姐可是絕代美人吶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.22,0:05:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也難怪他會按耐不住慾望
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.64,0:06:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 反過來說神野小姐這等美人放在面前
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.53,0:06:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卻不心生邪念那才是失禮之事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.01,0:06:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟我現在第一眼看見你後可是異常性奮吶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.35,0:06:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果狀況允許的話
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.00,0:06:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「人家還是第一次」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.71,0:06:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「這以後我會無數次讓你體會到樂趣哦」這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.76,0:06:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我們會長就是這樣的人 別放心上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.22,0:06:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實在是神野小姐的表情太僵硬了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.78,0:06:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就用葷笑話活躍下氣氛罷了 一不小心就…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.35,0:06:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說怎麼看都是性騷擾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.79,0:06:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 這樣說呢 我想問大家一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.27,0:06:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家認為秋人君是不是相當妹控？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.32,0:06:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為有
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.26,0:06:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實有
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.17,0:06:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.91,0:06:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣吶 果然是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.97,0:07:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好了神野小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.76,0:07:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人是個妹控這件事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.38,0:07:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和熱力學第一定律一樣無庸置疑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.77,0:07:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾乎可說是世界的定理啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.08,0:07:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無需特地確認哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.40,0:07:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 正是如此 東邊妹妹病了他去照顧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.48,0:07:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是妹妹在西邊疲憊他也會跑去替她拎東西 之類的很多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.96,0:07:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊勒勒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.79,0:07:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對他來說世上所有的東西就分兩類
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.65,0:07:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是「妹妹」和「妹妹以外的其它東西」如此這般
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.96,0:07:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀呀呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.11,0:07:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣 果然是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.49,0:07:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然珍惜妹妹我認為也很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.78,0:07:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他是重度妹控
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.63,0:07:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾乎就快要跨越危險的界線了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.89,0:07:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咿呀 正是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.82,0:07:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 果然不管誰都是一樣的感受吶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.28,0:07:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是 真是有著讓人頭疼的性癖的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.11,0:08:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們說什麼呢 我可完全不是妹控哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.97,0:08:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.04,0:08:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你乾脆就這麼承認了如何
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.78,0:08:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從一般角度來看秋人不管哪裡怎麼看都是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.01,0:08:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超特級的妹控
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.51,0:08:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 果然果然果然是這樣呢 秋人君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.79,0:08:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然是個妹控呢 你就承認吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.87,0:08:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.20,0:08:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 有客人來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.57,0:08:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就這麼辦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.66,0:08:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很簡單的事 直接去問本人就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.34,0:08:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.36,0:08:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位是神野薰子小姐 是之前跟你說的有工作來往的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.98,0:08:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次見面 哥哥一直蒙受您關照了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.01,0:08:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡 我才是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.30,0:08:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神野小姐有些事想問秋子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.27,0:08:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想問的事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.45,0:08:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 我覺得秋人君是一個非常不得了的妹控
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.94,0:08:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子小姐也這麼認為吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.01,0:08:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我認為完全沒有這回事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.91,0:08:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人君本人是那麼的… 秋子小姐卻否定了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.04,0:09:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不這麼驚訝也…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.24,0:09:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如說 如果哥哥是個非常不得了的妹控
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.47,0:09:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我當作戀愛對像來看待的話
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.99,0:09:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就沒有比這更美好的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.90,0:09:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冒昧的問一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.88,0:09:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 請問吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.45,0:09:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子小姐難道說是一個不可救藥的兄控嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.40,0:09:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 正是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.83,0:09:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然回答的如此乾脆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.57,0:09:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄控是個性 是神賜予的禮物
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.22,0:09:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從我出生時就一直就只愛著哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.00,0:09:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說秋子小姐是把秋人君當作一位男性來看待的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.54,0:09:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.00,0:09:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凱旋門
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.74,0:09:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥原來是個妹控 一直把我當作一位女性來看待的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.70,0:09:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.86,0:10:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為哥哥應該更加努力的成為一名妹控
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.53,0:10:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.99,0:10:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是努力就能辦得到的嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.86,0:10:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.79,0:10:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成為一個眼裡只有我的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.16,0:10:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,積極跨越那道危險的界線
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.72,0:10:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.13,0:10:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 太欺負人了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.26,0:10:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為那是正常的反應
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.28,0:10:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.27,0:10:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 作為我的妹妹 我是愛著你的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.06,0:10:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比世界上的任何人都愛你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.43,0:10:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎 那現在就快結婚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.78,0:10:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.97,0:10:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 就作為替代 請在神的面前發誓永遠愛我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.03,0:10:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 說的意思是一樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.83,0:10:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.72,0:10:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 就退一百步…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.99,0:10:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既不會親你也不會抱你 也不會撫摸你頭的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.82,0:10:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然搶先把所有的選擇都駁回了 哥哥真是個過分的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.84,0:10:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為懲罰 今夜請夜襲人家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.77,0:10:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好的 那就這麼辦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.55,0:10:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今夜 不會讓你睡著的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.72,0:11:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 那個 突然這麼一說 人家心裡還沒有準備好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.69,0:11:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在馬上 就在這裡也行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.92,0:11:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.08,0:11:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和往常不同如此積極 咕嘿嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.80,0:11:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 人家還是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.93,0:11:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道能否承受的住哥哥的那激烈的…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.53,0:11:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 秋子還是那麼可愛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.34,0:11:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種說法來看 果然又欺騙了少女的純情
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.19,0:11:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你壞 你壞 你壞 你壞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.11,0:11:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎麼看都是兩個笨蛋情侶呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.40,0:11:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泡草津溫泉也治不好的病 指的就是他們兩個吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.40,0:11:36.34,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,註：草津溫泉，日本有名的溫泉，據說除了相思病，什麼病都能治
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.48,0:11:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人每次都這麼開心的逗他妹妹 我們也只能放棄了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.75,0:11:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥是妹控 妹妹是兄控 這可不好 非常不好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.54,0:11:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 別這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.52,0:11:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有點嬌慣過頭了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.71,0:12:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來我們會住在這裡的理由是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.30,0:12:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了不讓那對兄妹兩人獨處
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.16,0:12:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了不讓他們越過界線
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.43,0:12:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將便宜的汽車旅館的牆隔開入睡的秋菜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.12,0:12:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到妹妹不惜來到北邊的盡頭來尋找自己
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.71,0:12:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋男的感情就無法抑制般的膨脹著
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.61,0:12:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 來夜襲什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.63,0:12:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咕嘿嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.64,0:12:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和哥哥要分開住
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.76,0:12:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從今天開始你們就要分開住
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.66,0:12:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.27,0:12:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的革命
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.27,0:12:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(456,438)\fs16}Revolution
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.88,0:12:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全球規模的妹妹革命
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.43,0:13:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 不好意思 你所說的在不同的房間生活
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.59,0:13:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有些不理解
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.77,0:13:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如說至今為止才是不正常啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.89,0:13:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管關係再怎麼好 都到了這年齡了還在一個房間裡生活
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.71,0:13:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是件怪事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.27,0:13:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我和哥哥是相依為命的兄妹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.23,0:13:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相依為命的親人 時隔六年不見
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.76,0:13:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算退一百步講 你是個普通的妹妹的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.47,0:13:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是不能睜隻眼閉隻眼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.29,0:13:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你是個名副其實的兄控
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.58,0:13:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更何況還可能越過界限
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.73,0:13:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和姬小路秋人應該要分開住 知道了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.65,0:13:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 那個
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.30,0:13:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 我可是管理員
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.74,0:13:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有權利要求住在管理員寢室
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.27,0:13:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管理人工作的不都是秋人在做嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.83,0:13:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 對了 管理人也必須得另外僱人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.55,0:13:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今為止都是臨時讓姬小路秋人擔任管理人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.10,0:13:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但必須有個正式的管理人才是理所當然的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.98,0:13:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.10,0:14:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請聽我說 我馬上就能和哥哥一起住了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.65,0:14:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.88,0:14:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六年間每天都在說呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.54,0:14:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 正確的是闊別五年零一個月二十四天六小時三十二分
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.53,0:14:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你 秋子同學
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.25,0:14:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,願望成真了呢 恭喜
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.15,0:14:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.70,0:14:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在回想起來那真是接連不斷的苦惱和苦難
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.56,0:14:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天每夜 不但對哥哥的思念沒有消退 反而越積越深
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.03,0:14:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也不會從哥哥身邊離開了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.23,0:14:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在哥哥身邊 卿卿我我 粘粘糊糊的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.96,0:14:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粘粘糊糊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.90,0:14:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡納豆嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.72,0:14:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.27,0:14:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄妹果然不在一起是不行的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.51,0:14:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要在一個屋簷下生活
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.94,0:14:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要在一張桌子上吃飯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.86,0:14:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 和哥哥不管是身是心都要合為一體
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.97,0:15:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 我和哥哥是兩廂情願是大家都明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.37,0:15:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你們說什麼我都不會從哥哥身邊離開的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.67,0:15:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥也不會認同和我分開住這種殘酷的不符常理的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.04,0:15:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 絕對不會的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.13,0:15:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 也不是說我們要強制這麼做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.76,0:15:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬小路秋人 最後的決定就交給你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.62,0:15:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由你來做決定
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.32,0:15:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.53,0:15:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比任何東西都更珍惜秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.84,0:15:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.24,0:15:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我決定和秋子分開住
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.63,0:15:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕快開始搬東西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.14,0:15:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能請大家稍微幫下忙嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.28,0:16:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎麼一回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.98,0:16:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥這個叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.15,0:16:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子生氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.63,0:16:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,氣到快哭出來的那種生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.77,0:16:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.79,0:16:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那從今往後一輩子都不跟你說話了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.01,0:16:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄妹緣分什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.19,0:16:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不如說是我斬斷的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.81,0:16:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.87,0:16:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我撒謊的 說過頭了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.53,0:16:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才的是口誤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.78,0:16:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕不是我的本意
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.13,0:16:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥這個白癡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.76,0:16:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你欺負人家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.00,0:16:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能真的就這樣不再理我了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.53,0:17:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做的很棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.17,0:17:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上這個來搞妹妹革命吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.42,0:17:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.77,0:17:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.70,0:17:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個YES-YES枕頭
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.51,0:17:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論何時我都是YES的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.49,0:17:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.43,0:17:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥也肯定會被深深的吸引的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.29,0:17:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被這部電影…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.69,0:17:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.50,0:17:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,復合電影院的聲效真是不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.44,0:17:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟妹控很相稱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.66,0:17:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.53,0:17:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像跟剛開始交往的戀人一樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.51,0:17:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.91,0:17:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.83,0:18:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哭著睡著了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.56,0:18:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是醒著的吧 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.11,0:18:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 在睡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.04,0:18:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為沒心沒肺的哥哥狠心對待
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.31,0:18:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的我已經哭的濕透了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.93,0:18:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信哥哥一定會來安慰我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.29,0:18:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這裡待命好久了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.97,0:18:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能把那份努力用在其他地方嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.56,0:18:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的努力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.52,0:18:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都是為了讓哥哥疼愛我而存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.77,0:18:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可不是該毫不猶豫一口咬定的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.24,0:19:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我就是要毫不猶豫的斷言
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.40,0:19:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生都是以哥哥為中心的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.21,0:19:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人類都應該依照自己的本性而活
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.88,0:19:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這才是最幸福的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.40,0:19:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然你說得很瀟灑的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.63,0:19:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我才不會上當呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.98,0:19:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是呢 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.85,0:19:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 我會好好愛著你的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.60,0:19:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.78,0:19:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,經過一個晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.95,0:19:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有些明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.87,0:19:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我分開房間住的哥哥的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.21,0:19:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.40,0:19:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥是重視過程的類型呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.69,0:19:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡單到手就太無聊了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.96,0:19:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,困難越多幹勁越足
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.53,0:20:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.62,0:20:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.50,0:20:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,避開大家的注意搞夜襲的緊張感
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.48,0:20:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷偷摸摸配合上提心吊膽的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.35,0:20:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓愛意空前高漲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.75,0:20:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些我懂的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.72,0:20:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 大家能過來一下嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.16,0:20:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的管理人要來了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.15,0:20:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就現在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.07,0:20:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.94,0:20:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天才說 今天就來了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.46,0:20:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是辦事雷厲風行的女人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.93,0:20:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能別自作主張呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.45,0:20:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不承認不是身高150厘米以下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.65,0:20:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,體重30公斤左右 可愛的管理人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.43,0:20:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的話呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.71,0:20:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是個願意認真工作
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.09,0:20:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,值得信賴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.20,0:20:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同住在一個屋簷下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.89,0:20:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不會令人生厭的人物的話會很為難的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.39,0:20:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我的話呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.44,0:20:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可能最好不是男的而是女的就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.95,0:20:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂各位
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.11,0:20:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼自顧自的提條件呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.46,0:20:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那還真是走運呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.04,0:20:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然純屬偶然
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.48,0:20:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是現在要過來的管理人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.87,0:21:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿足了你們全部的要求哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.19,0:21:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還是出身自日本屈指可數的豪門
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.07,0:21:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還在國外的大學取得學分
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.88,0:21:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加上十歲時便在學會發表了論文
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.47,0:21:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所謂的天才啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.83,0:21:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種無可挑剔的人物真的存在嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.87,0:21:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還要來這個老舊的學生宿舍當管理人？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.65,0:21:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 她本人說想做的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.20,0:21:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該就沒問題吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.43,0:21:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 會長
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.92,0:21:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個管理人莫非是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.25,0:21:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說曹操曹操到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.27,0:21:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…初次見面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.37,0:21:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 確實夠可愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.73,0:21:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是年紀很小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.06,0:21:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不如說…怎麼看都還是孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.92,0:21:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小女不才
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.52,0:21:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從今天開始請允許我全力工作
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.13,0:21:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用多多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.81,0:22:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來介紹一下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.14,0:22:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位是從今天開始當管理人的…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.39,0:22:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊對了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.34,0:22:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對於姬小路秋人來說是很熟悉的人呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.25,0:22:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫鷹乃宮亞里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.44,0:22:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鷹乃宮？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.66,0:22:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是哥哥前不久還待著的家的…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.80,0:22:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多關照啊 秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.04,0:22:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 請多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.69,0:22:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.71,0:22:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這孩子跟阿秋到底是什麼關係呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.66,0:22:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 那個是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.32,0:22:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 亞里沙是秋人哥哥的…未婚妻
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.70,0:24:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙和
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.12,0:24:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥大人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.56,0:24:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有婚約的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.99,0:24:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結婚
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.43,0:24:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約定
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.88,0:24:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.32,0:24:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從前
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.78,0:24:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗澡也
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.28,0:24:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.63,0:24:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後背
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.19,0:24:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擦洗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.57,0:24:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙也
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.99,0:24:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.46,0:24:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擦洗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.92,0:24:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被褥
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.33,0:24:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一個
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.69,0:24:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥大人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.10,0:24:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,體溫
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.54,0:24:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺到
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.00,0:24:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡著
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.45,0:24:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.88,0:24:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一次
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.36,0:24:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在身邊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.83,0:24:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.26,0:24:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.71,0:24:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好開心
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.21,0:24:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.71,0:24:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄控
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.19,0:24:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第七集是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.74,0:24:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太「平」公主
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.23,0:24:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要來看啊


