
[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Audio File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][09][x264_aac](93E475CC).mkv
Video File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][09][x264_aac](93E475CC).mkv
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 2
Video Position: 35003
Video Color Matrix: BT.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.93,0:21:59.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由動漫國字幕組和輕之國度字幕組聯合製作\N僅供試看,請支持購買正版音像製品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:02.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻譯:栗花落&槍叔&Cosmo  校對:娜娜莉  時間:鎖定  後期:sora  MKV:烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.67,0:00:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 那還真是很棒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.39,0:00:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 待會兒要不要去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.47,0:00:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定 再邀請秋子同學吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.71,0:00:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 那麼一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.98,0:00:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她來這幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.94,0:00:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是相當的棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.43,0:00:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與其說光看著就感覺心蕩神馳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.17,0:00:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是心兒撲通撲通地跳那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.34,0:00:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看著哥哥時也是這種感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.92,0:00:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說你們在說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.72,0:00:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮎美同學在校舍後碰到了個 很可愛的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.95,0:00:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可愛的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.44,0:00:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 到底去哪兒了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.24,0:01:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.22,0:01:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經吃完了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.25,0:01:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉呢 今天能給你帶的只有這些
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.54,0:01:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦 下次會給你多帶點的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.21,0:01:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不知道是為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.96,0:01:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇見了受傷的你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.81,0:01:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一時間心血來潮想要照顧你 算你運氣好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.78,0:01:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是違反規矩哦 我和你處在不同的世界吶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.97,0:01:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說啊 你好狡猾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.40,0:01:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真沒想到你這麼不好說話 我要跟你絕交
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.19,0:02:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過雖說要絕交 但還是有必要最後為你餞別吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.18,0:02:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是 現在開始我要抱抱你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.28,0:02:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 這僅僅是例外的措施 這點希望你能銘記於心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.85,0:02:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這毛色不是很好嘛 但即使這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.14,0:02:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「今後和你繼續保持這樣的關係就好了」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.80,0:02:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種想法我可沒有考慮過哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.80,0:02:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 動物為什麼這麼的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.21,0:02:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是誰！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.93,0:02:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 是另外一隻嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.67,0:02:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也快來這邊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.63,0:03:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來是個怕生的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.76,0:03:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 銀兵衛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.73,0:03:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.04,0:03:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在這幹啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.37,0:03:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊這個…只是散下步啦 秋子你呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.09,0:03:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是被朋友帶來看看可愛小貓的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.06,0:03:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲花同學 鮎美同學 給你們介紹下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.81,0:03:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位就是我的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.55,0:03:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次見面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.77,0:03:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說從妹妹那兒聽了不少
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.76,0:03:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們好 初次見面 秋子一直麻煩你們了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.50,0:05:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 感冒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.44,0:05:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 昨晚泡浴池構思原稿然後就那麼睡著了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.79,0:06:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是很嚴重 發燒了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.25,0:06:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很嚴重 然後雖說是不情之請…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.35,0:06:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我知道了 截稿日延後吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.20,0:06:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常謝謝 真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.62,0:06:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日程表裡的時候還很餘裕 問題不大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.50,0:06:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 會議完了以後 我去探病吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.35,0:06:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不用了 不必費心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.27,0:06:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要小瞧病痛 安心養病 吶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.76,0:06:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我會注意的 那麼再見
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.65,0:06:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全心全意的照顧哥哥 現在只能這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.16,0:06:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然因為我的大意讓哥哥感冒了是我的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.14,0:06:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我應該深刻反省
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.83,0:06:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是反省的話什麼時候都行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.82,0:06:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在重要的是讓哥哥好起來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.31,0:06:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就讓妹妹我全心全意 專心致志的照顧哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.53,0:07:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先給我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.37,0:07:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那說法簡直就是只有你一個人看護他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.41,0:07:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也是很關心同住在一個屋簷下的夥伴哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.44,0:07:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不能放著生病的秋人不管
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.58,0:07:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就讓我們一起照顧他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.22,0:07:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 大可不必
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.71,0:07:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明我平時不斷宣稱自己對哥哥的愛情有多深
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.36,0:07:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在卻弄得如此的狼狽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.98,0:07:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會負起責任的 咱一個人看護就行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.64,0:07:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照你那種論調
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.26,0:07:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這六年間擔任秋人摯友的我才更有責任嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.25,0:07:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如說只需我一個人看護就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.14,0:07:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不哦 銀銀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.16,0:07:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是更應該擁有一個人看護阿秋的責任的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.95,0:07:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要說為何…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.50,0:07:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因為我和阿秋已經準備組成一個新的搞笑搭檔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.01,0:07:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,預定在搞笑界創造傳說了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.25,0:07:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事我可不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.42,0:08:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如說這種事我還是第一次聽說
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.52,0:08:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 亞里沙作為管理人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.47,0:08:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人哥哥感冒了我也有責任
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.62,0:08:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙也想照顧秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.19,0:08:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要連亞里沙也說些擅自主張的話
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.16,0:08:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是姬小路家的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.79,0:08:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借助外人之手於面子上說不過去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.93,0:08:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡就應該交給我一個人來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.55,0:08:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是專橫 這裡應該公平的讓我來才對
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.69,0:08:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎麼看最適合的都是我才對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.93,0:08:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 亞里沙也…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.62,0:08:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 果然還是由作為妹妹的我來…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.56,0:08:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們也是不是該適可而止一下了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.19,0:08:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.57,0:08:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在是爭這個的時候嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.73,0:08:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在最重要的應該是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.64,0:08:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盡快的讓姬小路秋人好起來才對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.42,0:08:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.04,0:08:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就這麼辦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.19,0:08:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家定好時間輪流照看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.52,0:08:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輪流？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.45,0:09:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 你們用自己覺得最好的方式來照看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.74,0:09:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的人不許多嘴也不許插手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.10,0:09:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們看如何
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.24,0:09:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 也就是說
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.96,0:09:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看是誰照顧的最好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.56,0:09:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一局定勝負
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.04,0:09:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並不是這個意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.12,0:09:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 也罷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.88,0:09:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們就盡情的去做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.44,0:09:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人哥哥 我是亞里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.45,0:09:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以進來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.48,0:09:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 嗯 請進
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.72,0:09:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.08,0:09:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可不行哥哥 快躺下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.51,0:09:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 也是呢 我知道的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.99,0:10:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些都是為了我而做的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.52,0:10:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 要治好感冒不補充營養可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.26,0:10:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請儘管多吃一點
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.64,0:10:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個叫做神仙粥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.53,0:10:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在香港是很平常的料理
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.54,0:10:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 哥哥 啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.50,0:10:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 雞湯裡加上了蔥和薑 很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.69,0:10:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讓哥哥高興真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.99,0:10:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他還有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.33,0:10:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有雞蛋酒 這邊是加了梅干的薑粥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.70,0:10:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是金柑加上砂糖
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.59,0:10:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是大蒜加上蜂蜜
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.36,0:10:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是乾燥的牛蒡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.34,0:10:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是加了花蜜的煎湯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.44,0:10:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是加了菊花的煎湯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.20,0:10:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是加了橙子的焙燒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.98,0:10:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是加了梅干的焙燒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.70,0:10:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是加了枇杷花的焙燒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.56,0:10:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是加了紅蜻蜓的焙燒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.30,0:11:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是加了蚯蚓了焙燒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.02,0:11:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有想到哥哥可能想吃些濃一點的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.31,0:11:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是肉味烏冬 煨燉菜 什錦火鍋 還有牛排
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.49,0:11:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有為了想吃甜的東西的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.76,0:11:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備了烤布丁 還有加了「蒙布朗」水果酥餅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.83,0:11:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有這個雖然不是吃的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.95,0:11:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了捏扁之後貼在額頭上的梅干
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.61,0:11:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沾了酒的濕布
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.82,0:11:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了塞進「菊花」的烤大蔥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.72,0:11:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是沾了大蒜的…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.91,0:11:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍…稍微給我等下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.42,0:11:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你剛才說了啥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.19,0:11:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沾了大蒜的濕布
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.74,0:11:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這之前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.89,0:11:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烤大蔥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.07,0:11:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再之前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.07,0:11:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沾了酒的濕布
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.34,0:11:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太前了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.29,0:11:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥真是的 要人家說那種話太羞澀了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.06,0:11:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙都盡可能的避開了的說
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.20,0:11:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還特意要讓人家再說一遍是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.90,0:11:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我並不是這種帶有性騷擾的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.43,0:11:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果是秋人哥哥的願望的話
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.41,0:12:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞里沙就再說一次
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.72,0:12:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK 已經夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.07,0:12:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道不是我聽錯了就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.07,0:12:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.00,0:12:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有那個烤大蔥想讓你用在其他地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.31,0:12:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用在其他地方？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.30,0:12:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不是用來插到「菊花」裡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.50,0:12:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也還有其他的效果的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.69,0:12:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.51,0:12:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.41,0:12:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說只是感冒 不過這還真是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.47,0:12:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超過預想的疑難雜症啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.13,0:12:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.38,0:12:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然得上了下半身會插上蔬菜的疑難雜症
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.04,0:12:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才沒有那種病呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.50,0:12:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次是你來照顧我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.70,0:12:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 既然我已經來了就可以安心了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.59,0:12:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼病都能立馬治好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.18,0:12:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,問個簡單的問題 你有照顧人的經驗嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.00,0:13:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真失禮呢 雖然在家務方面我確實是奇跡般的無能
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.10,0:13:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但只有在照顧人方面我可是很嫻熟的 是很有才能的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.14,0:13:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.08,0:13:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉啊 懷疑你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.43,0:13:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為經常手會斷掉 那種時候就會去照顧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.87,0:13:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊布偶的久納君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.72,0:13:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布偶？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.87,0:13:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 久納君雖然是布偶 但擁有著靈魂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.42,0:13:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以照顧它和照顧人類積累的經驗值是一樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.38,0:13:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事我覺得是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.57,0:13:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 怎麼都好了 那就拜託你高抬貴手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.37,0:13:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就讓我先睡一會吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.20,0:13:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那你就盡情的給我休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.13,0:13:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡到連呼吸都忘掉如同死掉那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.70,0:13:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如同撲進古代希臘神話裡冥府的神
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.54,0:13:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈迪斯的懷抱裡一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.14,0:13:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要拐彎抹角的說這麼不吉利的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.49,0:13:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 怎麼都好了 總之我先睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.05,0:13:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.71,0:14:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.44,0:14:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋 有沒有什麼想讓我做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.83,0:14:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼的話不用客氣說出來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.98,0:14:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如讓我給你擦汗之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.44,0:14:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 不過我沒流汗所以不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.44,0:14:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是下半身也是可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.23,0:14:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以都說了 我沒流汗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.75,0:14:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋 有沒有什麼想讓我做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.17,0:14:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有什麼特別想要做的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.09,0:14:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒必要那麼謙虛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.64,0:14:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如幫你擦下半身的汗之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.10,0:14:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你只注重下半身
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.48,0:14:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之我沒流汗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.49,0:14:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.90,0:15:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋 有沒有什麼想讓我做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.57,0:15:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說…沒有什麼特別想要做的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.32,0:15:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然謙虛是日本人的美德
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.84,0:15:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種時候的話依賴我也沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.38,0:15:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如幫你擦下半身的汗之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.04,0:15:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 對於你來說照顧別人就只有這個嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.51,0:15:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才沒有這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.14,0:15:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他也有各種
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.65,0:15:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,單傳的傳內不傳外的照顧方法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.72,0:15:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如說
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.12,0:15:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 那須原同學
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.13,0:15:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道是現在正在拚命的想嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.51,0:15:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 你居然都說到這份上了就幫你做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.62,0:15:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 我還什麼都沒說呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.59,0:15:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 難得一次 就讓你幫我一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.02,0:15:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.65,0:15:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.65,0:15:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就如同魔法一樣的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.63,0:16:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.88,0:16:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 要說那樣的看護也是可以有的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.86,0:16:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 請你閉上眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.59,0:16:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不能睜開
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.32,0:16:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那樣保持不動
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.51,0:16:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴也不能張開哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.29,0:16:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不我的注意力會被打斷的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.24,0:16:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？你…你在幹什麼？！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.33,0:16:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什麼呀 阿秋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.90,0:16:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？那是 我的台詞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.23,0:16:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明說了閉上眼睛 闔上嘴巴 不要動
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.53,0:16:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什麼要睜開眼睛 張開嘴巴還亂動呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.78,0:16:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.72,0:16:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因為你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.94,0:16:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我僅有的那麼一點點寶貴的勇氣…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.02,0:16:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更正
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.83,0:17:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是為了施咒而需要的某種太空能量之類的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.48,0:17:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經全部泡湯了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.44,0:17:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃不
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.34,0:17:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你剛才靠近我的臉想做些什麼的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.21,0:17:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要做些什麼已經不是問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.72,0:17:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討論那種已經消失的可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.77,0:17:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和怨歎打翻的牛奶一般毫無意義
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.16,0:17:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.33,0:17:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是想要親吻我對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.99,0:17:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說…說什麼呢啊 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.92,0:17:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家才不可能那麼做的 不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.34,0:17:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊啊 不僅跟平常的角色完全不同了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.50,0:17:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一人稱都和以前不一樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.50,0:17:35.01,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23}注: 之前那須原經常是自稱「わたくし」，這時候忽然自稱「わたし」，顯然緊張了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.38,0:17:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道說你現在…很緊張嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.88,0:17:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎麼可能呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.53,0:17:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種會錯意還真是煩人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.12,0:17:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 我突然想起臨時有事 就先走了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.27,0:17:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臨時有事是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.62,0:17:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是老套啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.45,0:17:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 到頭來都幹了些什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.09,0:18:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.75,0:18:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是誰在說我的閒話吧 開玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.52,0:18:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 醒了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.31,0:18:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 是秋子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.26,0:18:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼叫「什麼啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.08,0:18:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明可愛的妹妹正在努力看護你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.64,0:18:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.79,0:18:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.31,0:18:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未經我的許可 就讓我躺在你的大腿上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.80,0:18:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至於還摸我的頭 這可是滔天大罪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.19,0:18:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 你在說什麼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.87,0:18:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥不只熟睡著 而且看起來還很難受
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.59,0:18:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這個狀況下 我當然必須盡自己所能進行看護
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.60,0:18:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是這樣子罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.31,0:19:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬要說的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.56,0:19:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而應該說是露出破綻的哥哥不好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.01,0:19:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這麼一回事了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.90,0:19:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多多向我撒嬌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.82,0:19:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直向著哥哥的撒嬌
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.39,0:19:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且哥哥都會遷就著我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.46,0:19:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不經意間給哥哥增加了負擔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.75,0:19:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.94,0:19:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做的事情就只有這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.75,0:19:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還只有在這種時候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.93,0:19:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才能幫得上您的忙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.53,0:19:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.85,0:19:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你盡情向我撒嬌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.64,0:19:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 這樣啊 謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.35,0:19:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就不客氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.68,0:19:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.05,0:20:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子今後會永遠在哥哥身邊的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.50,0:20:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神野小姐 你還好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.66,0:20:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎地 突然感覺好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.04,0:20:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臉也很紅 不是感冒了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.96,0:20:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.65,0:20:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是秋人君的感冒順著電話傳染給我了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.79,0:20:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是這樣的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.35,0:20:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在秋人君應該痊癒了才對
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.02,0:20:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犧牲自己 治好作家的疾病
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.70,0:20:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這才是編輯的榜樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.32,0:20:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 這感冒對於我來說
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.19,0:20:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好似軍功章一般啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.09,0:20:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣都好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.39,0:20:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕快去醫院吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.16,0:20:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種程度沒關係的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.47,0:20:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有一堆工作沒做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.97,0:20:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為喵喵在 所以喵喵嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.59,0:20:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.41,0:21:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡得真香啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.03,0:21:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡得這麼沉的話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.56,0:21:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵醒他於心不忍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.20,0:21:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 該做什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.21,0:21:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難受的難以入睡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.43,0:21:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 肩膀要是不放進被窩的話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.22,0:21:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身子會著涼的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.60,0:21:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖別動 不會弄疼你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.72,0:21:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧 猿渡同學
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.29,0:21:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.68,0:21:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋…秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.40,0:21:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然讓你受了這樣的傷 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.47,0:21:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 雖然彼此彼此了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.56,0:21:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 原來是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.07,0:21:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢到了那時的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.97,0:22:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛認識不久 小學的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.64,0:22:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次敞開心扉的那一天的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.49,0:22:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真懷念啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.44,0:22:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話雖如此
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.32,0:22:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之後你始終不把我當做女性這回事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.34,0:22:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是力持異議呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.69,0:22:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.54,0:22:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聯想到我們相遇的契機的話
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.36,0:22:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是沒辦法的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.11,0:22:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是現在回想起來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.97,0:22:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.52,0:22:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就邂逅的情形而言真是最壞的那一種了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.72,0:24:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.25,0:24:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分別
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.67,0:24:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜悅
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.14,0:24:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲傷
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.65,0:24:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦悶
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.21,0:24:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難受
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.63,0:24:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撲通撲通
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.14,0:24:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡欣雀躍
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.65,0:24:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開開心心
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.07,0:24:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得意忘形
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.51,0:24:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萬歲
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.02,0:24:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垂頭喪氣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.37,0:24:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇跡
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.97,0:24:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶然
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.37,0:24:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不論是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.86,0:24:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.32,0:24:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意外的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.79,0:24:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變故
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.35,0:24:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.79,0:24:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會有
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.32,0:24:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,健康的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.79,0:24:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活著吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.30,0:24:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.79,0:24:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀兵衛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.16,0:24:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相遇的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.72,0:24:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.20,0:24:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.67,0:24:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄控
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.11,0:24:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十話
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.58,0:24:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀球
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.58,0:24:19.92,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23}標題捏他「銀魂」…
