
[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Audio File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][09][x264_aac](93E475CC).mkv
Video File: [DMG&LKSUB][Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!][09][x264_aac](93E475CC).mkv
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 2
Video Position: 31527
Video Color Matrix: BT.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B15BF9,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.93,0:21:59.13,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由动漫国字幕组和轻之国度字幕组联合制作\N仅供试看,请支持购买正版音像制品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.13,0:22:02.86,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻译:栗花落&枪叔&Cosmo  校对:娜娜莉  时间:锁定  后期:sora  MKV:乌贼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.67,0:00:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 那还真是很棒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.39,0:00:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 待会儿要不要去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.47,0:00:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定 再邀请秋子同学吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.71,0:00:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 那么一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.98,0:00:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来这干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.94,0:00:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是相当的棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.43,0:00:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其说光看着就感觉心荡神驰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.17,0:00:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是心儿扑通扑通地跳那样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.34,0:00:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看着哥哥时也是这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.92,0:00:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说你们在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.72,0:00:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲇美同学在校舍后碰到了个 很可爱的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.95,0:00:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可爱的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.44,0:00:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 到底去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.24,0:01:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这声音
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.22,0:01:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经吃完了么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.25,0:01:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉呢 今天能给你带的只有这些
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.54,0:01:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦 下次会给你多带点的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.21,0:01:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不知道是为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.96,0:01:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇见了受伤的你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.81,0:01:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一时间心血来潮想要照顾你 算你运气好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.78,0:01:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是违反规矩哦 我和你处在不同的世界呐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.97,0:01:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊 你好狡猾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.40,0:01:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没想到你这么不好说话 我要跟你绝交
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.19,0:02:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过虽说要绝交 但还是有必要最后为你饯别吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.18,0:02:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是 现在开始我要抱抱你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.28,0:02:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 这仅仅是例外的措施 这点希望你能铭记于心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.85,0:02:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这毛色不是很好嘛 但即使这样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.14,0:02:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「今后和你继续保持这样的关系就好了」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.80,0:02:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种想法我可没有考虑过哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.80,0:02:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 动物为什么这么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.21,0:02:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.93,0:02:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 是另外一只吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.67,0:02:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也快来这边啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.63,0:03:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是个怕生的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.76,0:03:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 银兵卫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.73,0:03:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.04,0:03:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这干啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.37,0:03:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊这个…只是散下步啦 秋子你呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.09,0:03:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是被朋友带来看看可爱小猫的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.06,0:03:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲花同学 鲇美同学 给你们介绍下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.81,0:03:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位就是我的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.55,0:03:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次见面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.77,0:03:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说从妹妹那儿听了不少
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.76,0:03:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好 初次见面 秋子一直麻烦你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.50,0:05:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 感冒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.44,0:05:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 昨晚泡浴池构思原稿然后就那么睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.79,0:06:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是很严重 发烧了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.25,0:06:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很严重 然后虽说是不情之请…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.35,0:06:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我知道了 截稿日延后吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.20,0:06:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常谢谢 真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.62,0:06:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日程表里的时候还很余裕 问题不大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.50,0:06:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 会议完了以后 我去探病吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.35,0:06:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不用了 不必费心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.27,0:06:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要小瞧病痛 安心养病 呐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.76,0:06:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我会注意的 那么再见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.65,0:06:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全心全意的照顾哥哥 现在只能这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.16,0:06:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然因为我的大意让哥哥感冒了是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.14,0:06:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该深刻反省
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.83,0:06:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是反省的话什么时候都行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.82,0:06:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在重要的是让哥哥好起来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.31,0:06:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让妹妹我全心全意 专心致志的照顾哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.53,0:07:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.37,0:07:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那说法简直就是只有你一个人看护他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.41,0:07:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也是很关心同住在一个屋檐下的伙伴哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.44,0:07:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不能放着生病的秋人不管
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.58,0:07:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我们一起照顾他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.22,0:07:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 大可不必
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.71,0:07:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明我平时不断宣称自己对哥哥的爱情有多深
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.36,0:07:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在却弄得如此的狼狈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.98,0:07:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会负起责任的 咱一个人看护就行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.64,0:07:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照你那种论调
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.26,0:07:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这六年间担任秋人挚友的我才更有责任嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.25,0:07:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如说只需我一个人看护就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.14,0:07:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不哦 银银
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.16,0:07:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是更应该拥有一个人看护阿秋的责任的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.95,0:07:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说为何…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.50,0:07:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为我和阿秋已经准备组成一个新的搞笑搭档
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.01,0:07:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预定在搞笑界创造传说了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.25,0:07:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事我可不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.42,0:08:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如说这种事我还是第一次听说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.52,0:08:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 亚里沙作为管理人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.47,0:08:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人哥哥感冒了我也有责任
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.62,0:08:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙也想照顾秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.19,0:08:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要连亚里沙也说些擅自主张的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.16,0:08:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是姬小路家的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.79,0:08:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借助外人之手于面子上说不过去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.93,0:08:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就应该交给我一个人来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.55,0:08:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是专横 这里应该公平的让我来才对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.69,0:08:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么看最适合的都是我才对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.93,0:08:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 亚里沙也…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.62,0:08:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 果然还是由作为妹妹的我来…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.56,0:08:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也是不是该适可而止一下了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.19,0:08:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.57,0:08:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是争这个的时候吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.73,0:08:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在最重要的应该是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.64,0:08:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽快的让姬小路秋人好起来才对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.42,0:08:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.04,0:08:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这么办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.19,0:08:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家定好时间轮流照看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.52,0:08:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮流？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.45,0:09:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 你们用自己觉得最好的方式来照看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.74,0:09:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的人不许多嘴也不许插手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.10,0:09:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们看如何
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.24,0:09:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.96,0:09:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看是谁照顾的最好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.56,0:09:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一局定胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.04,0:09:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是这个意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.12,0:09:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 也罢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.88,0:09:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就尽情的去做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.44,0:09:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人哥哥 我是亚里沙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.45,0:09:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以进来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.48,0:09:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 嗯 请进
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.72,0:09:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.08,0:09:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行哥哥 快躺下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.51,0:09:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 也是呢 我知道的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.99,0:10:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些都是为了我而做的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.52,0:10:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 要治好感冒不补充营养可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.26,0:10:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请尽管多吃一点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.64,0:10:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个叫做神仙粥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.53,0:10:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在香港是很平常的料理
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.54,0:10:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 哥哥 啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.50,0:10:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 鸡汤里加上了葱和姜 很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.69,0:10:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让哥哥高兴真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.99,0:10:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他还有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.33,0:10:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有鸡蛋酒 这边是加了梅干的姜粥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.70,0:10:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是金柑加上砂糖
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.59,0:10:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是大蒜加上蜂蜜
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.36,0:10:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是干燥的牛蒡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.34,0:10:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是加了花蜜的煎汤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.44,0:10:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是加了菊花的煎汤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.20,0:10:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是加了橙子的焙烧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.98,0:10:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是加了梅干的焙烧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.70,0:10:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是加了枇杷花的焙烧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.56,0:10:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是加了红蜻蜓的焙烧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.30,0:11:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是加了蚯蚓了焙烧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.02,0:11:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有想到哥哥可能想吃些浓一点的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.31,0:11:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是肉味乌冬 煨炖菜 什锦火锅 还有牛排
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.49,0:11:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有为了想吃甜的东西的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.76,0:11:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备了烤布丁 还有加了「蒙布朗」水果酥饼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.83,0:11:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这个虽然不是吃的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.95,0:11:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了捏扁之后贴在额头上的梅干
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.61,0:11:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沾了酒的湿布
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.82,0:11:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了塞进「菊花」的烤大葱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.72,0:11:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是沾了大蒜的…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.91,0:11:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍…稍微给我等下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.42,0:11:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才说了啥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.19,0:11:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沾了大蒜的湿布
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.74,0:11:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这之前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.89,0:11:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烤大葱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.07,0:11:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再之前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.07,0:11:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沾了酒的湿布
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.34,0:11:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太前了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.29,0:11:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥真是的 要人家说那种话太羞涩了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.06,0:11:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙都尽可能的避开了的说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.20,0:11:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还特意要让人家再说一遍是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.90,0:11:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我并不是这种带有性骚扰的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.43,0:11:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果是秋人哥哥的愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.41,0:12:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里沙就再说一次
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.72,0:12:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK 已经够了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.07,0:12:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道不是我听错了就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.07,0:12:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.00,0:12:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有那个烤大葱想让你用在其他地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.31,0:12:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用在其他地方？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.30,0:12:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不是用来插到「菊花」里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.50,0:12:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也还有其他的效果的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.69,0:12:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.51,0:12:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 秋人哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.41,0:12:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说只是感冒 不过这还真是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.47,0:12:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超过预想的疑难杂症啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.13,0:12:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.38,0:12:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然得上了下半身会插上蔬菜的疑难杂症
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.04,0:12:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有那种病呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.50,0:12:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次是你来照顾我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.70,0:12:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 既然我已经来了就可以安心了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.59,0:12:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么病都能立马治好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.18,0:12:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问个简单的问题 你有照顾人的经验吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.00,0:13:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真失礼呢 虽然在家务方面我确实是奇迹般的无能
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.10,0:13:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但只有在照顾人方面我可是很娴熟的 是很有才能的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.14,0:13:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.08,0:13:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉啊 怀疑你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.43,0:13:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为经常手会断掉 那种时候就会去照顾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.87,0:13:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊布偶的久纳君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.72,0:13:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布偶？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.87,0:13:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 久纳君虽然是布偶 但拥有着灵魂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.42,0:13:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以照顾它和照顾人类积累的经验值是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.38,0:13:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事我觉得是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.57,0:13:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 怎么都好了 那就拜托你高抬贵手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.37,0:13:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就让我先睡一会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.20,0:13:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那你就尽情的给我休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.13,0:13:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡到连呼吸都忘掉如同死掉那样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.70,0:13:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如同扑进古代希腊神话里冥府的神
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.54,0:13:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈迪斯的怀抱里一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.14,0:13:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要拐弯抹角的说这么不吉利的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.49,0:13:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 怎么都好了 总之我先睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.05,0:13:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.71,0:14:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.44,0:14:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋 有没有什么想让我做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.83,0:14:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么的话不用客气说出来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.98,0:14:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如让我给你擦汗之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.44,0:14:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 不过我没流汗所以不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.44,0:14:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是下半身也是可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.23,0:14:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以都说了 我没流汗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.75,0:14:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋 有没有什么想让我做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.17,0:14:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么特别想要做的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.09,0:14:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要那么谦虚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.64,0:14:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如帮你擦下半身的汗之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.10,0:14:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你只注重下半身
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.48,0:14:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之我没流汗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.49,0:14:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.90,0:15:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿秋 有没有什么想让我做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.57,0:15:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说…没有什么特别想要做的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.32,0:15:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然谦虚是日本人的美德
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.84,0:15:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候的话依赖我也没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.38,0:15:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如帮你擦下半身的汗之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.04,0:15:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 对于你来说照顾别人就只有这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.51,0:15:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.14,0:15:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他也有各种
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.65,0:15:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单传的传内不传外的照顾方法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.72,0:15:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.12,0:15:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 那须原同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.13,0:15:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是现在正在拼命的想吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.51,0:15:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 你居然都说到这份上了就帮你做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.62,0:15:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 我还什么都没说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.59,0:15:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 难得一次 就让你帮我一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.02,0:15:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.65,0:15:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.65,0:15:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就如同魔法一样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.63,0:16:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.88,0:16:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 要说那样的看护也是可以有的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.86,0:16:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 请你闭上眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.59,0:16:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能睁开
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.32,0:16:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那样保持不动
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.51,0:16:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴也不能张开哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.29,0:16:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不我的注意力会被打断的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.24,0:16:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？你…你在干什么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.33,0:16:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么呀 阿秋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.90,0:16:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？那是 我的台词
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.23,0:16:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明说了闭上眼睛 阖上嘴巴 不要动
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.53,0:16:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要睁开眼睛 张开嘴巴还乱动呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.78,0:16:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.72,0:16:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.94,0:16:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仅有的那么一点点宝贵的勇气…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.02,0:16:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更正
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.83,0:17:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了施咒而需要的某种太空能量之类的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.48,0:17:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经全部泡汤了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.44,0:17:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃不
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.34,0:17:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你刚才靠近我的脸想做些什么的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.21,0:17:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要做些什么已经不是问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.72,0:17:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨论那种已经消失的可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.77,0:17:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和怨叹打翻的牛奶一般毫无意义
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.16,0:17:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.33,0:17:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是想要亲吻我对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.99,0:17:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说…说什么呢啊 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.92,0:17:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家才不可能那么做的 不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.34,0:17:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊啊 不仅跟平常的角色完全不同了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.50,0:17:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一人称都和以前不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.50,0:17:35.01,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注: 之前那须原经常是自称「わたくし」，这时候忽然自称「わたし」，显然紧张了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.38,0:17:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说你现在…很紧张吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.88,0:17:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么可能呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.53,0:17:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种会错意还真是烦人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.12,0:17:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 我突然想起临时有事 就先走了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.27,0:17:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临时有事是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.62,0:17:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是老套啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.45,0:17:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 到头来都干了些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.09,0:18:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.75,0:18:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁在说我的闲话吧 开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.52,0:18:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 醒了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.31,0:18:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 是秋子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.26,0:18:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫「什么啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.08,0:18:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明可爱的妹妹正在努力看护你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.64,0:18:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.79,0:18:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.31,0:18:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未经我的许可 就让我躺在你的大腿上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.80,0:18:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至於还摸我的头 这可是滔天大罪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.19,0:18:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 你在说什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.87,0:18:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥不只熟睡着 而且看起来还很难受
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.59,0:18:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个状况下 我当然必须尽自己所能进行看护
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.60,0:18:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是这样子罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.31,0:19:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬要说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.56,0:19:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而应该说是露出破绽的哥哥不好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.01,0:19:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么一回事了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.90,0:19:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多多向我撒娇吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.82,0:19:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直向着哥哥的撒娇
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.39,0:19:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且哥哥都会迁就着我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.46,0:19:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不经意间给哥哥增加了负担
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.75,0:19:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.94,0:19:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做的事情就只有这样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.75,0:19:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还只有在这种时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.93,0:19:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才能帮得上您的忙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.53,0:19:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.85,0:19:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你尽情向我撒娇吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.64,0:19:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这样啊 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.35,0:19:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就不客气了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.68,0:19:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.05,0:20:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋子今后会永远在哥哥身边的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.50,0:20:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神野小姐 你还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.66,0:20:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎地 突然感觉好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.04,0:20:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸也很红 不是感冒了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.96,0:20:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.65,0:20:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是秋人君的感冒顺着电话传染给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.79,0:20:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.35,0:20:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在秋人君应该痊愈了才对
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.02,0:20:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牺牲自己 治好作家的疾病
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.70,0:20:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是编辑的榜样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.32,0:20:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 这感冒对于我来说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.19,0:20:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好似军功章一般啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.09,0:20:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样都好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.39,0:20:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快去医院吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.16,0:20:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种程度没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.47,0:20:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一堆工作没做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.97,0:20:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为喵喵在 所以喵喵嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.59,0:20:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.41,0:21:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡得真香啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.03,0:21:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡得这么沉的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.56,0:21:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵醒他于心不忍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.20,0:21:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 该做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.21,0:21:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难受的难以入睡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.43,0:21:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 肩膀要是不放进被窝的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.22,0:21:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身子会着凉的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.60,0:21:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖别动 不会弄疼你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.72,0:21:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 猿渡同学
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.29,0:21:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.68,0:21:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋…秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.40,0:21:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然让你受了这样的伤 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.47,0:21:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 虽然彼此彼此了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.56,0:21:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.07,0:21:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦到了那时的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.97,0:22:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚认识不久 小学的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.64,0:22:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次敞开心扉的那一天的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.49,0:22:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真怀念啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.44,0:22:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽如此
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.32,0:22:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之后你始终不把我当做女性这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.34,0:22:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是力持异议呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.69,0:22:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.54,0:22:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联想到我们相遇的契机的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.36,0:22:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是没办法的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.11,0:22:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在回想起来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.97,0:22:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.52,0:22:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就邂逅的情形而言真是最坏的那一种了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.72,0:24:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.25,0:24:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分别
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.67,0:24:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜悦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.14,0:24:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.65,0:24:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦闷
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.21,0:24:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难受
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.63,0:24:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扑通扑通
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.14,0:24:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢欣雀跃
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.65,0:24:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开开心心
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.07,0:24:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得意忘形
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.51,0:24:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万岁
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.02,0:24:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垂头丧气
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.37,0:24:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.97,0:24:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶然
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.37,0:24:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.86,0:24:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.32,0:24:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意外的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.79,0:24:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变故
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.35,0:24:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.79,0:24:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.32,0:24:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,健康的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.79,0:24:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.30,0:24:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和秋人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.79,0:24:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银兵卫
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.16,0:24:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相遇的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.72,0:24:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.20,0:24:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.67,0:24:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄控
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.11,0:24:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.58,0:24:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银球
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.58,0:24:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs20}标题捏他「银魂」…
